Welcome to Psyche Awakens, a show in the panel verse where tarot, truth and raw conversation meet.
We explore boldly, we disagree intelligently and we protect the circle.
Here's how we roll.
House rules.
Debate ideas, not people.
No doxing, slander, hate or threats, ever.
Bring receipts, claims need sources or timestamps, no rumour relays, signal discipline, mix muted
and less called, no spam, no derail, the mods are the guardians, warning time out, ban,
no negotiations mid-show.
This is Psyche's channel, Psyche's Rules.
He keeps it safe, sharp and on topic.
Use common sense and be respectful to everyone and you will be fine.
Contribute or be entertained welcome if you're here to sow chaos hang out. There's a place for you here, too
Now welcome your host psyche see a storyteller and your host eTruth first shadows second
Let's get into it
from the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls
this is Psyche Awakens, crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes
thundercrack
you smooth mystical
yo welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight
truce get told he goes unfold, we stir the soul with a tea surf cold
The spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopin'
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
Slythe be awake and step in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
Slythe be awake and don't look away
Your shadows talk and it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
Christine's mad about crystal Tony's just full of it
Braun's chicken struts around but it's looking like a lunatic
Sweet pea is gone sour beat has bitter Betty
Welcome to the Psyche Hater's Club
Where the jealous gather up
Begging for attention, thirsty and stuck
One club I'm happy, I'm not part of
Go hate yourselves
Yeah, go hate yourselves
Bronze chicken pluck those feathers
Welcome to the...
7 in the morning. I heard a bang on the door. Yeah, apparently someone has put it out that
I am apparently selling a lot of scrap metal or something. I don't know. But yeah, some
Yeah, yeah, hold on. Do you hear me? Hold on. I need to get my microphone, right?
Hola!
Okay. Yeah, they decided to do another, you know, Hater's Club meeting.
Oh shit, shit, shit!
Oh my god.
Okay, hold on.
Hmm.
Okay, I don't mind if...
I don't mind if they play clips. Oh shit.
Okay, I'm gonna get it up.
I don't mind if they show clips because clips people can judge for themselves. They can always like, you know
Put their own spin on it. I'll take off but you can put their own spin on the clips, right?
Yeah, they won't be yeah, the police are already involved so
They're very interested in this very interested, okay
Have a little time
But it's like, oh, well, you know, the people that I asked to be there, and I didn't ask
anybody to defend me or anything.
I just let them know there'd be a meeting of the club.
Yeah.
And let's see, no, I'm not Patrick.
I'm not.
Apparently someone was texting them saying, oh, I'm just asleep or I might be sleeping inside. Just knock really loud, you know
Or keep knocking or my I don't know my grandfather's asleep. He might have to knock really loud
So it was just very loud. So I just started going down when it was like when I started and I just let them talk to them
And everyone was very nice. I
That's why it's like I didn't want to
Until I had enough information. I didn't want to contact authorities because I didn't want
It's not their fault. It's not the pizza lady. Not the Mexican pizza lady's fault. It's not
It's not anybody's fault
Except the person that's doing that, you know
Luckily, I think one of the people they took all the fertilizer went down all the fertilizers are gone
Gosh, that was like 20 bucks a fertilizer. I had for my garden. It's gone
Someone stole the fertilizer
But um, it's okay. It's okay
Yeah, I don't mind that they play the clips. I don't mind if they tell the true stories, you know, their opinions
It's like, I mean seriously everyone there has been
No timed out. Oh my gosh, but they're but let me see. Hi Jesus
Hello Jesus. Yeah, I was not a shirt. It's a I'm in my room in my robes today
I'm in my, I'm in my whole robes. Okay. Hey, Ziggy. Oh, is it you there? Ziggy, what's up? I've missed you
Yeah, I'm in my leg. This is like the cold meeting, you know, it's like
You know, because we're like a cult or if you want you can call yourself whatever but
My full robes. Hi, Megan
Time let's see not sure what you need to be forgiven for much less punished for I'm punishing you
Oh, you want to think you're punished? Well, I mean
I know
You because you were kind of like
You know on my side a little bit. I don't know the one one thing that kind of irritated me was
Not about you. I'll remod you and everything
He-man on the other hand she was just like laughing about being unmodded so she can continue to be unmodded
And so the rest of the people are unmodded
There's several. I think about five or six, but I'll get you back
Okay
Standard
Everyone says it yeah
And it's like, I'm not like, like crying.
Did I ever cry about it?
I don't think Bita is like, oh my God, he's crying.
And then Bita said, the only reason she cried
is because I was around.
Like I have this presence that makes her sad or something.
I don't know.
Like, do you guys just break out into tears
when you see me sometimes?
I just need to like figure out like, well,
now I'm being blamed for Bita's like, you know, breakdowns.
That's a good song.
Oh my God.
But anyway, um, yeah, if she was there, you know, she was there and it was like, I didn't tell some people to go over there, right?
I said, just, just to watch or to, you know, just, if they wanted it on my back, they could, but I didn't say that.
I just said, oh, they're having a meeting over there.
But it turned into everyone told me that I told them that she's like three or four people. I told three or four people.
So, yeah.
Yeah, and so, you know, and it's like they were just having a like, okay
Well, I know I have a few things, okay
So a few things that were said because I didn't watch the whole thing because it was just like they knew I was watching because you know
And so they kept like trying to like direct stuff at me
So I was like I got tired after a while especially that like exiled one and bronzeward
Okay, anyway, so yeah
The few things that were said I just want to correct on the record. Okay, I've been doing caro since I was eight years old
I have, you can go back to my Etsy page,
Meta Psyche, hold on a minute,
it might be PsycheAwakens.etsy.com now,
I might have changed it.
But I'll get the link back up.
But you can see, since in 2020,
like my review started then.
So because Exile, the one was saying,
oh, my wife knows some, I saw a Tarot reader
and she saw on this episode where,
you know, he didn't know anything about Tarot.
Um, and he was asking, you know, and then that's how he got interested. Yeah, that's just stupid. Um,
I don't know like where that comes from. I don't know who he's talking about. I was in a lot of tarot card readers streams at one point
because i'm a tarot card reader and but
I don't know. He had some idea that I just I just figured like I don't know even when I started the show December
I started as terrible. I have like over 50 decks. I can show you my my room too. I can I have like hundreds of books
So obviously it's been a lifetime thing. It's not like
Just like oh, I just picked it up as this and I take it seriously in but they're like, oh, he's not good
and then beta said also that I
You know traveling gypsy and page who I introduced beta to both of them
Through my show, right? She said it that I was saying I was upset that she was promoting them
Do I I guys I promoted Bronzeberg when he after he started all this?
I mean, I put I let him type his name in
Thing in the chat like I is a link or had somebody else type his link in the chat, right? I did and so
Like I'm all about promoting people I didn't like when Bita was like, oh don't go to psyche go to them
Yeah, and that's what she did several times. She said it several times. Just so probably annoy me, right?
But so I want to correct that one and then I want to talk about like he like when he said the two psyches thing
Like I know he doesn't understand like, you know
Like mythology and stuff like that. It's okay. He thinks I psyche is just a psychological term psyche actually comes from the goddess psyche from mythology
Who really inspired me for the name of this channel and to start this channel, right?
I do believe in the Anima and I do believe like Psyche is like she's a soul and so it's an Anima
And that's why I do believe that I have a feminine soul too, and it's like what's wrong with that
I don't know, but it's like he's there like saying oh, I'm saying I'm a herma for a diet
I want a sex change or something like that. I don't know. It's just so stupid
And then oh, that's weird. That's weird. Well, okay, if you don't understand it then
I don't know. I can't explain it. Yeah, he's a nutcase
Oh, my God. And then he's like, oh, and every time you go live about me, I'm going to go live. Okay, good.
Because I'll just further show who's on my side who's not very helpful in determining that because so many, you know, I had, you know, so many things, a lot of stuff happened today.
Yeah. Hi, guys.
Don't let Yumi block Patrick. I will not. Okay, I will tell you. Okay.
I will tell you me, Mason's not a mod anymore,
so hopefully they won't cause problems anymore.
I'm gonna thank Alex, Alex came up there,
Alex did a good job, Alexander McQueen went up there
and I don't think, yeah, but I don't know.
That's my time. That's why she gets upset is because people, you know, don't
If you antagonize her then she's gonna start saying stuff that I don't want in her to say about like politics and stuff
Let's like keep the politics out of the chat. I don't want to talk about
foreign wars and that kind of stuff because it's really not for monetized channels to discuss unless
they're like a news channel or something. I don't know anything about them really enough to discuss
them. I'll discuss domestic issues once in a while, if it's like timely, if I can have a conversation
about it, but I just don't want...
antagonizing people or politics that's really easy to do and it's like people
you know she so so she gets kind of offended okay so let me just put on my
back screen hi I'm sorry if I didn't say hi to anybody let me say hi to
everybody. Jamie's Cowboys, Alexander McQueen, Patrick, Time, Ziggy, Jamie's Cowboys,
Yeah, I mean, it's like and I'm not gonna even play their stupid show. It's like, you know, you can go watch it if you want to
I encourage you to actually if you want to see like a bunch of
Bunch of you know assholes
But I'm gonna take the higher road. I'm just gonna like stop. I'm just not gonna be addressing them
I was gonna write a song maybe a song about Bronzeberg, but I figure I'm so uninterested in Bronzeberg
I don't know anything about him if you know to do it just I mean it's like I could just be like you know petty about it
But I don't and plus I don't know ways to it would take three credits to I'm generate a song
And so I'm not gonna I'm waste three credits on him. I'm gonna write
Continuing my positive songs and stuff
You know, I'm not gonna be playing
I'm gonna retire the the beat is biscuit. I'm gonna retire everything. I'm a beat. I'm just not gonna
I'm not I'm gonna I'm gonna stop saying her name. She's
She's a relevant to me now
My tattoo stands for
Burger King grill I
Might get it changed because I'm a McDonald's fan now, but um
Yeah, it always did it was just like I just told you to that to make her feel good
But you know it's like it's gonna turn into an issue
Okay, let's see here. We go. Welcome to the madness Alexander Empress Janet. What's up? Hold on
Janet was here earlier. Hi guys, and I'm sorry if people are getting dragged into it, too
I know JDogg is getting some shrapnel and like they're discussing some other people. Oh my god. The worst person was LES
He's like oh
And he's like, oh, he thinks he's going to start a community.
But then it's like, he listened to ghosts,
or he put me backstage for a long time.
Oh my god, cry me a river, Elias.
Oh my god, noxious motherfucker.
First of all, it's like, do I want you in my community?
No.
If I have a community, do I want everybody in it?
I want friendly people, cool people, smart people, not
Some wigger like you know trying to like I don't even know. Okay. I'm sorry if I use the wrong word, okay, anyway, yeah
Yeah, and then oh yeah Christine. Oh god, you know
Samman has fucking Christine's photograph up with a pookie in her mouth and says crackhead Christine
And she goes over there. She has no problem with Samman putting her picture up with a crack pipe
Which could really upset her her work. I would think but okay
Okay, okay, she would be mad at me for crystal saying the name Christine. She could have been calling talking about Christine
Christine Ritchie or something like that Christine, you know from Phantom of the Opera. Who knows she's the first name Christine
So like nobody really you can't nobody could report that or anything like they'd say what Christine is she talking about?
There's nothing there's nothing there, right?
Okay
But Zaman put up a put up a crack pipe in your mouth and then it's like oh, and you see still fine
I think he gets you thought that was funny, right?
That was funny. It's just just for anything to do with me is this like offensive. I don't know
Crystal all of a sudden has some credibility on my show and also. Oh, oh look at poor poor Mason
Like you know they understand like sense of humor. I use a kind of appreciating sense of humor at times where I like say
you know pretending I'm really thirsty and stuff by the way I can have I can get laid I can I
don't want a boyfriend first of all but if I can get laid I don't want to go meeting like random
people on stuff so it's like and I'm Sagittarius Venus which is like I like people kind of from
You know, I'm not like, but it was like, oh my god
She's so thirsty and sad and trying to get a boyfriend. It's like, you know, I'm I'm self-partnered. I'm fine with my
Myself. I'm perfectly happy
I could find a boyfriend if I wanted to.
Actually, I had a significant other for a few months
and it was just hell because I'm too independent
to want to date anybody.
Also, it went from, now I'm invested with fleas
to now I have lice and ticks as well,
just so you guys know.
So you really, really want to be careful
because they can get through the camera lens
and everyone can, so they just know
I have mice and fleas, right?
Yeah, it's a little bit of sex selective outrage, huh?
Yeah, it's got here. Hey, what's up? So anyone want to come up on the panel and have a talk?
I don't know. Didn't anybody see the stupidity?
Stupidity and it's like, oh, and he's not trying to get clout off my name
But yet he's like so excited about like doing these like hate episodes. He's like it's response to me what?
Actually, they watched the the haters club video and he's like, you know, I don't his interpretation of it was pretty stupid, but
Yeah, okay, so anyway the haters, but he seemed like he liked it. He was like, I think I look good
He's like I look like well, I'm glad you like your bronze bronze feathers bronze doesn't look like a fake kind of gold
You are very fake
and so
Yeah, also I do have some like, you know, Bronzeberg archives you can see how he just kissed my butt
When he came to the show and begged for like, you know clap and I actually I was stupid enough to like, you know
Let him advertise here. Yeah gay bird. Yeah gay chicken
I mean, it's like but don't insult birds like birds in general. Just like, you know, give it to like some dumb
Dump that bird that we'd like to eat. That's bronze chicken
Name is gay bird. Okay, gay bird
Yeah, I mean, yeah, it was very creepy over there and oh my gosh, and there's this woman named Katie
Now, I don't know if you know about Katie
Katie was
Jamie's friend and then
She had some kind of falling out with Jamie. She was really cruel about it
You know, I went through a lot of stuff like and then
But she would talk shit about beta and then she's already going on beta's panel is sitting there quietly not saying very much
And she's just a follower. It's a pure follower
Just goes wherever wherever the wind takes her, right? Yeah
Oh, I have bed books too, yeah, I have bed books too.
Even though I don't even sleep in my bed, I sleep in my couch.
My couch is filthy, dirty, I don't mean everything's just
the best, there's just shit all over the floor.
I smell like cat piss.
OK, yeah.
But and do I say have I ever said this about any like do I like go after people and not also he's like
And you did so I was broke. No, I did not say you were broke ever
I said brought and they're like what he's broke. I was trying to say bronze bird
You can go back to the beat of streaming watch it
You can see very clearly that's what I said and then be the same. He said you're broke. What are you talking about?
I don't know. It's financial situation. I don't know. I don't care. I don't know anything about him
Maybe change it into broke bird because your feelings were broke. I broke your feelings. Okay, and now I now you're just
And then then it's like I think the chat might have gotten like offended about like, you know
I said where they gather the jealous gather or something like that and they're like, what are we jealous of now?
I was talking more about
You know him I should have said, you know, he's the he's that but he's like he's like no what's what was going on?
Hold on with what Jamie?
But Jamie can, you know, I'll be exposing the messages.
Since Bita has no problem exposing like my messages, right?
And then Bita is saying, oh, I exposed her message.
You know, what?
The message where you said, just the heads up to you.
I have a heads up.
You know, I take care of the heads around me, my heads.
My friends, my friends' heads, heads involved.
I'm gonna give them a heads up too.
Shouldn't have said anything to me
Are we on great terms? No and plus you expose every message that I sent you
After that the whole cat situation you had no problem exposing those exposing me on several streams be the never had a problem
Okay, keep saying her name again
Beato joins tonight. Don't let her run the panel. Oh, she she won't be joining
She won't be joining
Yeah
Unban me you phony. Why would I am ban you Rodimus Prime? I saw you there tonight
Want to preach your costume go get one
It is preachers it is like a costume, but this is actually real this part of it
You can see this is a symbol for Saturn a chemical symbol. It's in my path. So
Yeah, oh
My god, and she calls me a phony. Okay. She calls me a phony
I go I'm I've watched back the old streams because I thought like she kind of turned on me
She never turned on me
She was always like passive aggressive about the insults except like when she said like I should get run over by a
Train on one of my stream buzz. It's I was just kind of shocked. I think but uh
You're banned again. Well, if you don't shut up, you're gonna be banned in this account, too. Uh
Uh-oh easy. No, no, no
Don't be outside that but yeah, and then and then um
Yeah, then Alex just mentioned the name of the person that is threatening to
strike my channel again and
I'm sending putting ads in the paper about scrap metal delivery or pick up here at my house and having people bang on my door all day
blah blah blah
Oh, and he's just like a fuck and he has a channel all about me all clips
I could have this channel taken down today. It's like I'm just like I don't have I don't feel like
She's just filling out a form, you know
It's like there's a long form for privacy complaints, but
You know he's just using my show I could take it all down
It's like they're just all his entire what his entire page is just me his entire page
You can see a allied master computer. It's everything's very insulting, you know, just of course take it with a pillar of salt
Yeah
Yeah, I'm done and that's not doxing saying somebody's first name is not doxing. How is that doxing?
Saying somebody's first name. Did you say a last name?
Giddy, how's it doxing isn't Chris isn't summer always the one saying it's not doxing if it's just the first name
I don't know. I'm kind of confused because then all of a sudden it was doxing tonight. They're saying right
Yeah, I
Don't know. Yeah
Alex did a good job. They did let Alex up
They let Canada dry up Canada dry actually did I'm not I don't care the Canada dry was there because he didn't have say anything
But he did not say one thing about me. All I did was to say Christine was a
wacko
Yeah, the first name isn't doxy, but so
Unless there's just one Benjamin in the entire country or something like that or the world. I don't know isn't Benjamin kind of like a
Common name. I don't know. How would you how would anybody know anything from that?
Plus I can share anybody's name offline. I do have his name because
He did false privacy complaints. So we had just a minute. So
Easy go on the panel and make fun about psyche. Oh, what do you do?
Yeah, I do see a guy didn't see easy to like, you know, he went money for 20s and then money for 20s
Like well, no one's over psychies anymore. How many people are here now? Oh 52. Okay. Nobody's over at psychies anymore
You know and then you know easy was like, oh, yeah
And then the psyche let people slander me blah blah in this chat
Well, you were a mod for a long time easy and I knew you could have like hid people and stuff, right?
I had nothing. I didn't slander. I don't slander anybody. I don't and it's like it happened in chat
I don't always read the chat and so it's like
All I just I just would ask just like a block somebody in chat if they're bothering you or you are my you you were a mod you
Mod now
Yeah, you're a mod now. You can still blog people in chat. So you're not going to be slandered over here
If you're being slandered by a mod, mods are not supposed to slander, so they're not going to bother you. I don't understand
Yeah
So yeah, I do watch them and then stage is that stay turned slander is foreplay. Oh, is the foreplay stay turn mods block stay turn please because he's just like, you know, an idiot. Okay, stay turn. Yes, I don't want to see those people. They're not allowed in the, in the, in the cult, they're not allowed, not allowed to cult meetings.
We can actually just sacrifice them. Let's do some sacrifices of some people.
They come in the chat and they get banned. That's gonna be a sacrifice from now on
Easy you're a mod and so
You have you're allowed to if there if someone is in your name isn't black and
They're slandering you go ahead and hide them. Okay
That's what I said, that's my word, okay, so that's it
Yeah, hi Steph and Shawn what what what what what what what what in the butt what what?
We're gonna what what what we're gonna
See I guess
But I don't I really don't care how many they keep if he goes on all year about it
It's like I think that they had basically maxed out on the on the number of psyche haters
Like though there's nobody new or anything over there. It was just the same thing
Yeah, they'll be walking the plank burned at the stake. Let me see. It's my hair wet. Yeah, it's wet
I take a shower before every show now, you know, I used to
See, I used to like stream so much that I didn't neglect my like maybe my hygiene or maybe my cleanliness here
And it's like but you know people are allowed to like
Improve you know just because like you know my house was messy one time
Hey, we were we ever had a messy room and it's like is that are we supposed to be defined by the messy room my nails are clean
Remember the whole thing about my nails for months and months and months. Oh his nails are filthy now
It's turned into like I'm some
Insect-ridden person and then as for Levin cats. Yes, I had a few litters of cats
I can I'm sorry. I can't keep a Levin cats, but they'd be happier if I had all Levin cats
Would they be happier about that?
That'd be a little expect and they're supposed to be all indoors and stuff. I mean is that realistic so of course
I had to pare down my number of cats
Okay, I mean it's like I didn't do anything bad to them, right? It's like
Fortunately
Most of them, you know
Or fine I did have one cat unfortunately
But it's like it's acting like I'm doing horrible things to cats and stuff. Okay, so let's see what you guys say
Sike, what up, psyche?
How are you? I'll be up here. I'll be up here a lot, but
Due to the mod situation, which was just saying I don't block people unless you say so
I can't like really like I mean no cuz then then then then what about all the trolls to start attacking me then I
Look bad from blocking everybody like you know
You care about looking dad to the trolls though. It's like they're gonna they're gonna say
trolls and
After your comment section is attacking me
Pretty much like and here's again. Oh, he likes trolls in his chat pretty much. Everybody here has a trolling site
Even I will admit to have a trolling side. We can like let it out at the right time
I think like most people here are like, oh, do you got a priest outfit on right now? Yeah
You fucking killing me with that one, bro. I swear to God just realized by the white collar
I swear to God through the whole conversation you was talking. I'm looking at your glasses and shit. I didn't realize the white car
I'm gonna take
Now I see why you named it cult of psyches. Yes
Well, I don't care who got problems you I support you I support be the support a lot of people a lot of people
We just got to stop hating on you and Alexander struck my dick from the back stay turn
You may fucking gay blow kisses that fuckers like you all do you want and it's like he stay turn is using your shit on his page
You can strike him. I know I can't I can a lot of people other people are including KZ who's like
bitching at me every time about like, you know, after he slanders me to Elisa then he wants to like, you know
be on the panel sitting with his burping microphone and
To clarify what Alex said about the video that I uploaded because nobody would have knew if I didn't upload it
I was in the back of psyches live
Oh backstage on the backstage and Mario
state turned God and J.T. was sitting there
applying about taking down Psyche's page in 17 minutes.
I just recorded it and posted it.
So, Alexander, get your facts right and stop blaming me.
yeah i mean it's easy easy and i are cool we've had our ups and downs sometimes i always told
just like i always told you straight up yo i'm gonna record this i did this and fuck what they say
i don't give a fuck how they feel i bought you a fucking speedo so fucking what oh my god the
world's gonna end i thought my psyche has perished beatles the world's gonna end let's cry about
it today and tomorrow
And then like someone named the loot those are the no it was the nobody or the loser
Let me see it was nobody
Who is like want to be his friends, but he was like oh anybody that donates any man that donates the psyche is
Is a gay man like I mean it's just like that is
No, I can have my wife come over and they should take again mom matter of fact, I go live while fucking
Fucking so I'll show you how fucking game out
Yeah, I'm sure I know I know easy's not easy's married and you know, you know a lot of guys will like laugh
You know, it's like it's kind of funny. Like you those are kind of funny. Oh, we have. Oh, we have good times in the chat
Hello
Okay there, buddy. I'm fine. How are you?
I'm fantastic. I'm cooking a salmon with noodles and not some black pepper and garlic. So it's good
Sounds good. So good times like you know, I know like, you know, you don't you might not like me that much
like at least like
you know, you're pretty straight up about it and
You know, I don't know if you you were the one behind crystal coming over and then saying the Christine stuff or something like you
Some people thought that you're her handler or something like that or but um, you know, I know
No
To respond to that you have to get to me nigga good times you you you were you a two-time troll jumping over the fences
Like straight like that. You're a two-time troll jumping over the fence
No matter where you at you're gonna jump over the fence and play both sides of fields
Easy I didn't blame you shit Ed. This is the thing I hate about YouTube when people get the things max stop
and then they say Alex get your facts right
I didn't blame you I told psyche that stay turned wouldn't do that. It was some Chinese fuck in the background
That you were up there. I didn't say you said you took a shit down in 17 minutes
What the fuck happened he's any near stream probably
No, it's still active. I don't know what's happening. Yeah, I know I know what's happening
He's shutting the stream off you moron
But yeah, you you playing both sides of the field good times and you know you is you playing beaters
And you playing over here and you playing over there and he calls in disruption within the community. So
What's your top?
Wow drop this loser, bro, he's gonna pull him by me or drop the n-word on your
You can't accept confrontation you can't accept feedback or confrontation
You can't you can't accept what you have done. You live in denial
I'm your fucking river good times like Justin fucking Timberlake you bitch
Yeah
Yeah, good times and what was he he was gonna ask me if I was schizophrenic
No, but I know what kind of mental illness you have good times because you obviously are not all there
So I know oh shit. I know good times. You know, he likes his life
You know, what was he passed out on that time that you know, even go watch this fucking jumper you fucking Luigi crackhead
Yeah, and no charisma easy doesn't play all sides. I didn't see easy on fucking our gay births panel with all of them
He doesn't play all sides easy to the size. No, I true. I chose psyche. I was like he's cool
He's not for a boy and he's cool with them, but he doesn't do that with them
I don't understand. I don't fuck with them. I watch it, but I don't fuck with them. I've been told like
You know I've been told that I was a kind of cool gay guy too because you know for brown bruise. Oh, you know
He's like this gay guy that is like sassy and like and beat is like I've never been a gay guy that like was so sassy
I mean, jeez. I mean, how you judging gay guys? How you judging gay guys? Why you judging the gay guy?
sassy
Gay guys, okay, so like what gay guys and gay guys simple. Why are you judging him as a sassy gay guy?
Now you're taking the two fall
Some people got a little more flaming. They're like, you know the back in the 80
Yeah, we get sassy and all types of shit with the haters, you know
And you drive away like yeah, didn't you say you want me to suck your dick and then
Joke and then is like he's defending Chris
Hold on, we'll get to
he's
You know a little passive aggressive shit into it like Alex did like a little bit, but he's getting better man. I think he's
Know a charisma, so I'm gonna give him that
Everybody
Was like a big, you know, he don't he gave me some great gifts and stuff like that. He's going to master rehab
Yeah, I think he likes me and stuff, so
I am a preacher
Ministers license I do I'm like I'm a I'm a I'm registered minister. I can get my certificate
Yeah, you should black you should buy time brown bird and everybody. I hate trying to get a gay religion
Hmm bad times there is
You're not sure is whatever whatever that is. It's crazy. Oh, we don't call psyche the pre-psych
The Reverend
Almost dox you almost dox you can I say your name?
No, not not Alex's
Can I say your name? I just wanted I wanted to make
Nah, why?
You guys said it a thousand times, psyche.
Yeah, exactly. Mine too, everybody.
So, whatever.
Yeah, I just said it.
We're gonna have to get over this shit, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I could call me Martinez, Alex.
It's okay. That's my name.
That's my last name.
But y'all never get my first name, bitch.
Mr. Martinez,
holla at me.
Like my feet turn mr. Crestful remember when he was it he was like
Yeah, I thought it was Crestful so bad. That's why I was sitting there laughing. That's how much you don't that man
That's why easy's my name and no shit exactly
Man, I'm good
Mason is that you
But there's a fuck though. What's the point like who cares right like I don't get why that is so important. You know what I'm saying?
But you know, I didn't have any new but I meet people every day and I'm like a I'm this person like and then I think about it like you
Oh my god. Oh my god. They got me. I'm gonna put a soap on a rope. Oh my god
They have absolutely no new material. They just said the same stuff. They said the last the first you know, I'm saying Alex
Fuck that. I don't care if you said that shit. They're gonna say go hurt me
Martinez, oh my god
What's so amazing
Why are you actually showing your feet psyche? Why are you showing your feet? Like?
Oh you feel on the screen for two minutes. Yeah, I think he needs to jerk off
Yo, imagine I suppose that roll up and he's got the fucking
I think
Amazing the drum was gonna jerk off to your feet. That's why he asked yo easy picture psyche pulls that robot
And he's wearing your speedos now. That's escape my man. God awesome sauce
That's a million dollars that man got up right now ripped that shit off and started dancing those Speedos Wow Wow
Wow
That's that's lightning in a bottle
Well, it's in a bottle. I mean, it's like you have a shit. I get provided speedo. I can't fight for buying somebody something
I couldn't have fun. Oh
Man a pair of speedos
A thousand and a million excuses at the end of the day the man wanted it simple
It was funny as fuck bro. Thank God you did that my man won bulls out number one one was bulls almost popped out
And he almost won't bother himself
I don't know why he took a shower in them shits.
Don't rubbob me, don't rubbob me unless Psyche post his stuff.
Yeah, he took a shower for us in them puppies.
Yo, we had Sam and Heldo in the shower.
We had Harry dying his ass off.
Oh, it sounded like a ho.
Yo, everyone's fine.
It sounded like a ho.
I'm sorry, Psyche.
I said the wrong word.
He sounded like a bad boy.
And you know what's funny?
You know what's funny?
Psyche sounded like a bad boy.
How much confidence it takes to do that how much
You got fucking balls of steel for that one. Exactly my man. I seen that from day one
That's why I laugh when they're like, yeah, he's under the covers. I'm like, shut the fuck up man
It's the most confident person on the planet. What's like you what do you want though?
What do you want to happen? What do I want to happen? I don't want anything to happen
But they're making fun. Well, they were saying Mason is like, you know gay now and like, you know, I'm sorry Mason Mason
Do you want to see psyche speedo moment?
So did you see that Mason? Yeah, the speedo. Oh my god. So I can where's your speedo? It's in my bedroom. Do you want to see him?
So I can never saw your speedo. You never saw go get him
It was different different me you want American flag speedos
I gave it to him
He said he's gonna do a fourth of July special so I guess it was next year not this year. That was the best
Love that whole thing by the way. I was like, oh my gosh. He'll eat cool easy is in both of them
And they're so funny and psychosal confident like and everybody
Yeah, but now they use it against them
Brown bird everybody
Was loving that so much. It was so great. The whole shit
For another reason I did it for all of you
Correct
Cuz you know how we are like you get the humor like I'm gonna make them left you you like making people laugh like me
You'll also have a comedian side of yourself. Oh
Shit
You know, he's got a cross in his hand
My man's a priest tonight. What the fuck he's exercising the demon out of at a brown chicken
He's gonna speedo the demon out of you, all right
Holler be thy name
Yeah, I want for our father. We hope Mary's and one speedo bulls popping up my man
Is knock knock knock knock it's cock-cock-cock. Let's go
Because I almost changed the name of the the channel to church to the church of Cupid
that would be C. O. C. cock was a cult now
We got to change our needs to
Peter club
What is it? That's the boner and everyone has a number number two
You can be number
It's like you what happened to Goddy
Um, what happened to God?
You know God he was only here to troll you because of Bruno, right? I
Don't know Stephanie. Um, he was
Yeah, well, thank you. Let me tell you before God he got here. He was on TPP
Chilling with Bruno in them and then they was hating on me being here and then God he popped up
Okay, so that's how we show it. Okay, that's fine
You know and gaudy night gaudy says he came to troll and stuff
But then he says he like he just had he liked my show
He said it straight up. I came to troll yeah because Bruno sent them
He doesn't work for Bruno easy does it? Well, you know Mike Bruno like hates me
But he follows me on tiktok and probably watches the show too. He's one of those silent watch
I'm following you. I'm trying to see if I'm following you first. Oh, I don't push that's the only reason
He's only following you cuz I he cuz he's following me. Yeah easy easy
You want to be you want to be haters club? That's the one on number three look under my name
Mr. Haters Club my paves
So I can say you turn it to a priest now, right? Well, I've been a priest
I'm in our day minister as the most in our day minister since like 1997 or 1998
And so I can show you my certificate and stuff. Do you want to see it?
I mean, it's like I do have so like you so you're really a real priest like you've been a priest before. Oh
I mean, I'm a yeah, I'm Reverend. Yeah, I'm a priest
Like you can show me. Yeah
See this is why I don't know if they're trolling or not easy. I'm a priest of Saturn. This is a set that means Saturn
I'm I'm a priest of Saturn and
Yeah, and I'm also he's a priest all right
Yeah, and so yeah, I will bless you Mason. He'll bless you bless him bless him with the balls
He's got a big boat by the way, I don't know what the hell when he had those speeders on right the boat is big
The cup the cup is the cup. I'm like my man. It's holding the source again. I have
Alex I'm reading the chat. They always skinny guys got to like 12-inch cocks for some reason they going crazy in the chat
Forgive me for the proud sin. You're mason. There you go, man
$25 or more on a private chat and you get more I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America
You get donations for the
Super chats. You know my man is holding the speeders on to the priest outfit. It doesn't get better than that, bro
So, you know, you know better than that
Ain't no better than that bar
Yeah, okay, there you go. I have a goal and I'll do it. He about to drop it like it's hot
Mason
It's on repeat about the bees me is over. I key
Sike, what did you do that? Did you get anything?
No, I'm you know, I got some donations and some nice donations that day. I definitely did
I'm happy you still enjoy them. I'm happy you still get to have the
Today that this is the funniest one you understand it's still even getting better
I'm dead it's a wrap
In Spanish right in Spanish me talking to my gig cuz I said oh yeah, but oh um you want to Puerto Rican speedos in Spanish
And he said oh, yeah
Let me get it in Spanish
You like I got you
I got you christmas. This christmas. I'm gonna go to go. I'm gonna go to tis house
We'll drive back up to new york and go to tis house and buy to my
Here you go fucking motherfucker
I'm gonna laugh my ass off. Oh
My gosh, now someone's getting the
I've never heard Macy's Hawaii, bro. No more questions Macy. This is the this is the some messages exposed
This one said he sent me that they're linked the other day
He says don't play my copyrighted content blah blah, which is what I don't really talk about
John I'm reporting every time stamp that you're playing you'll not be able to appeal this because it's my copyright and our GCMA law
a scam and send you $2 right now to the fully show the speedos back for Mason
for mason to jerk off to you later don't worry about it psyche mason's gonna jerk off to you later
he's gonna replay this video he's gonna clip it he's gonna turn gay they start just saying i turn
mason gay and stuff like that goddy goddy mason's gay shut the fuck up mason you saw those ass cheeks
Yeah, Alex. Tell them how you had them in the bushes. Tell them how you had them in the bushes
Let's turn the picture man
And pretend it's bad
Okay, then I'm just gonna give it to him. It's gonna give it to him good on the side of the highway
Leave him there for dad and getting my corn bounce like oh you're lucky. You're lucky. I'm on
That's going on here think about it. Oh, yeah psyche think about this
Who is one of the first people to hate on you um to make money? It was God. Oh
I got
I wasn't I was in a group with
Oh, that's why I knew because I put I put it in the okay
I thought I was writing a page, but it was actually do I know God he was one of God
He was one of the first people to hate on you making money
Yeah, so I said they're coming. Okay, so I wrote okay, so here's what happened
Here's why because she was saying three or four people wrote I wrote to page and I said I've put the link and I said
They're coming they're criminally harassing me by the way by the way sending people by my house asking for scrap metal hanging on the
knock on the door they saying
for
For
Fertilizer and pizzas trying to strike my channel and then but Bita was in the group. She was in the group chat and then she goes
Um, and then she said, I hope you're feeling better. Oh, and then she said, I hope you're feeling better day by day
You always brighten my day when I see you in the chat
Love you sis and then because she thought it was page two and then I said I understand she's sorry page
I thought this was a message that from you. I'm removing myself out of this chat
I was only made to be there for psyche when he's hurting catch you soon sis
It was only made for to be there for psyche when he's hurting. Oh my gosh
Oh and how about beta you need them, you know, definitely psychiatrist
and then uh page and be those are your best friends as far as i know they're the good ones bro
you just gotta stop gg who you get who's my best friend
It was your best friends and when I fell in love with an illusion. I liked an illusion
That was an illusion. She was oh my in my in my opinion
It was in my opinion when I first got here. You was
I was like so dedicated to her because I but it was it was the illusion. I felt rid of the math both of them
So both of them and they were
Myself isn't that sick? I fell on myself because she was but I don't know what's happening right now and
And you know buying the Speedos when I bought the Speedos
Yeah, guys was like getting back like up on fuck everything and that shit brought back y'all for a little while and then
the haters, the haters separate each other again.
And ever since then.
Well, I told her a million times
and it's like, she wouldn't listen.
So she can be, she can be with those people.
Also, she's like, oh, well, psyche just waits for me
to get like over a hundred people in my room.
Then he came over.
I never even, she always has like a lot of people
in her room.
She's had like almost a hundred people in her chat
since I met her.
So it's like, there's, you know,
sometimes there's less of us.
I don't, I'm not worried about numbers
as much as she thinks.
And it's like, what?
It's like, I don't know.
They think I'm some like money hungry.
Well, I mean, I don't know.
And then, oh, she's like, oh, so we heard it.
OK, I'm sorry, bro.
Like, I believe one day.
Oh and summer summer summer, too. I don't know why I'm like I love summers. I'm sorry. No matter what
Let me say it. I'll talk
Yeah, this is your page you say what you want, but I agree with someone no matter what
Me me me myself
I'm the new summer apparently some of herself said I'm the new summer because she was once had a good heart
She said and like, you know, try to see the best in people once
And now that's, that's apparently what I do, right?
So it's fine if I'm the new summer, I'm the new summer.
That's what you see the best in people.
You try to, I do too.
I do too.
Summer, you know, I just want to tell you easy, here's what I did.
I'm making this new, like this new, like a community kind of thing where it's like,
you know, it's kind of like where people can have their channel and we'll say
when they're live and stuff.
I own the community and I wanted to like, and so when I was like, I had it already
and it's like, I can show you because I'll be like fixing it.
I'm both of her channels on there. Um, you know, and I was like excited to show her
Yeah, well, but then she doubled down on like talking shit on me and so I mean it's like and she's like
Oh, I don't have the I lost five people
I don't have the energy to defend you and then she but she has the energy to be there and fucking
Disparage me. What is it?
My defense is she don't need me to defend her. She does a lot of good for the community
I've never had a fucking problem with her
Yes, she has a wild mouth when people attack her talking shit about me that gets a credibility
No, no, no, I'm not saying you psyche. I'm saying in general
She has a wild mouth when people attack her and she's her defense system
I never attacked her. What is attacking her? Let me break it down like this
put yourself in someone's shoes and what she said about her life and understand why she's so
defensive when she's defensive. Yeah I know it was to a point but then it's like when I
told her I was like you know
Well, that's don't say anything. I mean, it's like, it's not anything nice to say, but I can't have my mind when you
What when you when you think somebody's a bad person put yourself in their shoes and see life through that try
Very ignorant and misguided that whole group. It's like it's like they're just sad and it's like I don't know what's wrong with them
They're definitely why just even even the bad ones. I tried to put myself in their shoes and see life
How'd they see it?
Who cares better you tell them my shoes you want to be woken up and like seven in the morning
So I'm banging on your door and relentlessly asking for scrap metal and they're just laughing about it
And they don't care
You're not here. Oh, well, he's like that's recently though. That's recently. I didn't know about this guy
Last thing I remember was a pizza. Everybody's
Fucking God now this is the new thing scrap metals
Scrap metal. Yeah, and oh my god
Ten people came by looking for scrap metal. I mean whatever it's like, you know
I just go down and say no
I don't have scrap metal but I was trying to like take a nap and it's like when they're just bang on my metal door all day
It's like it's annoying plus
He has my fucking my front door on his on the page and stuff like that
But he had the person take a picture of and stuff like that. It's all through Craigslist instead. It's just just stupid
You know so
Um, yeah, I've had enough of like, you know, I'm like, I'm like, what's, and with like, oh, okay. Well,
But it's like then coming today again doubling down on it. Okay
You want to now you're now you're putting
My question is what you're going to do about it if they keep on persistently doing it and doxing you and doing this
What you're going to do about it
The police are already involved
There you go. I have his name if you want to fuckers think is a joke once the police get involved
Don't you need don't you know, it's called data trail, which is no matter
What you do?
No matter what you do location is at your residence
Location of where you was that location of where you logged in that location of this location of that and all your
alternative accounts
We'll be there's the name there's the name of the backchats when you check it out
They don't know they don't know they don't know
There's no funny games until you send in the chest out and your study says what you here for online trolling
Plus he admitted to doing he admitted to doing it on the last show
And so I have that clip of him saying that he did it and it's like
Now he's saying he didn't do it, but he did say he said it the other night and he's and he talked about the doorknob
I got a message that he was in
This is how he tells you well, I'm here for rape and I like guys. Oh
Yeah, I mean, it's like well sometimes they do send over like some some gay guy
I'm here for rape and I like guys
That's when the shit got real, right? You hear for you hear for all our children
Well, I'm here for raping God. I'm raping guys. What the fuck?
Don't repeat that. Come on
Don't say that. I'm sorry. I said the wrong word great. Uh, I got a speech impediment
Again, don't say I know and I got a speech impediment. I'm sorry
Well, don't say it like I will ask you and then you said it again. It's like stop
Um, I'm on a summer here summer. Okay summer's asking for the link. Wow. Okay. It's about time to get a
That's my own. Yeah, I'll defend them even when she's not here. She know the deal
Okay, well summer doesn't need to be defended when she's on here. She can talk to defend herself. So yeah, she always talk to herself
But I'll see you in a little bit
Okay, I
Like to do things one-on-one
Yeah, you can defend her from the chat if she's defending, but I'm not going to attack summer
No, I know I respect summer too. It's like I've always respected her work and I've always been nice and kinder. Yeah, here we go
Hello
Hello, so you guys haven't said anything Mikey?
Well, I already said it. Did you hear it? I can say it again
First of all I never said you were the new me
You don't realize you're being fucking played and that and I don't need to go over it again and again and again and again
Everything I've said I've said to your face
Time when are you gonna take accountability?
Accountability for what the continuance bullshit you do what like what what I do
Bullshit, you never do anything. It's like you never do it. It's all of us all of us every one of us
All everybody that now and even the fucking chick the one chick used to hang out with all of us are wrong, right?
We've all done bad things to you, right?
Yes
Y'all have you're smoking up. You continue to do it. You're smoking up like really you're smoking up. Yes, you do. Yes, you do
You have what do I do? I do you psyche. We fucking support. It's your drunk fucking junkie ass. Oh my monkey ass
Okay, well today, you know after I said, you know, it's like well you could at least like you're like
I don't have the energy to okay, so that's fine
But you have the energy to insult me and you have the energy to say I'm writing dicks and blah blah
Yesterday that I even poke my head around I haven't been around but you're so fully yourself. You don't know that
Okay, well talk about full of yourself. I mean summer is like, you know, calling the kettle black, huh?
I was like, please. Yeah, you're full of yourself motherfucker. You're full of yourself too. Okay, and I didn't call you a monkey. I called you a junkie.
Okay. Oh junkie. Well, that's a lot better. Okay. I'm a junkie. Okay. Yeah, that's what you look like right now.
Okay. Well, you look like a bitch. Okay. Bye
Okay, good
Bye
Did you just give the yep, you just did a
Definitely
Yo, I wanted that bitch so bad bring that dumb bitch back up. I was just literally typing in the back chat
God forbid he lets me up and then bye. Oh
Fuck that bitch
The fuck she comes up here. What is she a mom?
Manipulating YouTube minds bullshit out of here with that dumb shit. I
Don't know I was always respectful to her. I mean it's like
Respectful to her the fuck. I was not just respectful to you. What just happened? No, and
Everyone's just writing dicks, you know, I'm just about writing dick
She came up here and just attacked you like an animal like a fucking bitch and heat
Bring them back up and leave it with me, bro. Okay, bring her back up and leave it with me
See what happens that bitch is gonna go cry and rip a fucking head off
Bring that dumb bitch back up
He gives two fucks what you're talking about Alex. Go fuck yourself. You're fucking you don't even like gay people
That's the funny thing about this like you're being played like a fucking idiot and it's fucking hilarious to watch
The poor boy has mental issues, bro
What are you gonna do?
This bitch has seen five bests in a week.
You said pictures to his house. Why don't you tell psyche that again?
I just don't want to send the pieces there now, bitch.
What the fuck are you talking about, you stupid things?
Shut up. Shut up. Go suck a dick for money, hooker.
You call yourself a mother? You call yourself a mother when you're 10 kids right now, bitch?
Oh, your 10 kids must be so proud of you. They're so proud of mommy, the hooker.
Your 10 kids must be in racial 10 kids, bitch. You can't even raise one kid.
You haven't raised one kid, bitch, but yeah, you can't even raise one kid, but you can't even raise one kid, bitch.
But you don't take care of your kids, no one lets you know where around your kids.
Nowhere around, bitch.
You're a bitch.
Alex, how does the butt up?
Great
Shut up mother use you're not a mother of ten nothing if anything you don't fucking mess that crack and hook a bitch
Nobody
You're living behind the fucking scenes talking about fucking kids and shit the fuck out of you that dumb shit
You motherfuckers ain't right shit
You live behind the scene, you live behind the scene, you throw a bunch of rocks
Shut up dick, you know nothing
You live behind the scenes, you hide your hands and throw rocks
I'm your bitch
You've been following the ghost for three years
Yeah, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad ass game, it's not a bad
Alex was Isabella Alex
Alex was Isabella Alex bring that hooker back up. Where's that dumb bitch talking about ten kids
I'm done with all you motherfuckers bullshit. You heard it's a wrap
My PD runs the show you don't ever forget that I am in bed
Tomorrow you're lucky. I like you a little
Martinez your Martinez suck a dick David
David who's Isabella fuck up. I don't fucking know dick and who the fuck is fucking what?
Bring that bitch back up
That's stupid hooker back up so I can smack her off the planet again
You're fucking insane yo bridge that hooker bitch, bro
Hold on hold on hold on easy ones and now hold on my piece. I was reading this so this bitch bosses and now easy
but we're only just chilling two minutes ago on psyches where we are right now now you're trying
to dox like bullshit you and you're completely wrong by the way so i'm laughing my ass off
so summer controls you
Easy your mind is so puny that this bitch just turned you on me for no reason because we were just chilling my boy
I see a stick that I haven't seen in my life.
Bro, for a soft slide, and everybody's got a stick.
Look at you two little minions.
You're her little puppy dog.
Look at you, that bitch has you like little puppets.
You guys are little puppets.
She's got strings and she runs you like little puppets.
Ha, ha, ha.
Fuck out of here, bro, you little puppets.
You're a puppet of summer.
And we just proved it tonight.
We just proved it tonight on this panel that Summer can control little puppets, you understand?
Because these two guys are trying to attack me now over Summer.
She dropped the biscuit in handling heat and she left the little chihuahuas up here.
They're little puppy dogs!
Yo, I heard him saying there's some money for 20s.
The thing is
He said, when the good guy he likes, I win.
I got him then.
Because you know what, there's to you piece of shit.
Hey, guys, look, it's about a couple of years back up.
Where's that garbage?
Where's that hook?
You take your Tony Montana, bro.
You take your Tony Montana.
You're a big, you're a big, you're a big, you're a big,
you're a big, you're a big, you're a big, you're a big, you're a big, you're a big, you're a big, you're a big, you're a big, you're a big, you're a big.
You think I don't remember you coming up on TGP. You look crippled. He is 6'9", by the way.
Smash is literally 6'9", crippled.
He looks exactly like his picture, by the way.
He looks exactly like his picture. Yeah, you camped up many a time with me, my boy.
You're exactly what your picture looks like. You are slow from the boonies. You're sitting on a couch like
that's all you bring to panels you don't have a brain you can't even hold the normal conversation for two seconds
but you don't even have a brain, my dears
try to stick the landing with your hand
he's gone he's gone talk to yourself cripple boy talk to yourself
yeah yeah that's right bitch because you don't want to smoke dude i know i see your skinny little
fucking two-inch wrist i see you fucking came up with those two-inch wrists and skinny little
80 year old grandma hands
Go go store another line, bitch
And psyche maybe you shouldn't ban me for sticking up for special needs fucker
What mason's special needs you're gonna call mason retarded mason is perfectly intelligent. I've heard him. Okay. I
Had a hide people in the chat, so he's not that
You're calling me so you're calling people retarded. Do you have his uh, are you a psychiatrist?
Do you have his uh his diagnosis? I just want to find out
What you're sticking up for mason and i'm not okay
Okay smash
What so i'm what am i am i abusing mason what tell me
Yeah, now Mason is gonna ask 10,000 questions. I know it'd be very good. Yeah, but uh
Psycho Rooney, Psycho Rooney, sorry if I ruined the party my man. What happened everybody?
What happened in summer easy was smashed when they go
Because
You know, it's like they're not being real with me. It's like I'm not like, you know
The fucking garbage, bro
That's why they were my best friends for a long time and then it takes time and then you see people for who the fucking really are I
Know you less than them and I consider you more of a friend than them you understand that
Okay, look at all that Alexander mayors, you know for a month you guys are best friends because people can read character and real people
These people are fucking bullshit garbage
Fake
We'll doubt you in a second
Drop of a hat. They'll drink they'll bring up, but you know anything to hurt like it's so weak
They just oh, oh
There's that right once you got
Throwing out bullshit. They think they have but and the funny thing is they're so retarded
Fuck them fuck them fuck the oil of them, bro
Easy's running from the law right now. He's on the run
You have a family on the run on your panel by the way, you know that he knows it
He said it the other day on money for 20s. Go watch it. He's like even if the charge gets to a simple assault to the good
This mother is one of my tent murders. Like
Easy is wanted for attempted murder on the Eli and he's on the run and he said it too many times. I'm in Florida
in the Bronx
The whole project once he's happy like bounce to Florida. He's on the run
Okay, do what you got to do with that
Who I mean, it's just crazy. I mean, I was gonna like it's gonna discuss it like normally like not sure
But you know, okay, that's how my bed. I don't like to you know, getting people's business man, but when they push it
They're gonna get it. Just like I like master
Yeah, I mean, it's like our master's gonna get it man because he's not the first you think you're the first person
He's done it too. He's like a master of doing this
They brag about sending me newer and people searching for metal and all this garbage
They brag about harassing and stalking people
Understand we have to put an end to that right now
Like Trump like step up like it enough is enough ice. I'm gonna flood the town with fucking tanks
Like we have to stop this shit
In the stands, what are you gonna live there forever thing down because I'm moron and be on a come
Nobody nobody
Yeah
Huh, I mean it's sad. It's sad. Now. It's like another friend, you know, but it's like
Are they they're not gonna sit there? They're they're my mod and they're gonna sit there and like just like
about sight they will say it to them once but when I went up there for them again
They don't give a fuck about actual you morons. You don't know who I give a fuck about you
Don't know my feelings inside who I consider a friend or not because summer says
Summer said man share about me. He's not a cop. Yeah, I am you stupid
thinking no things
And they say it and like expect people what they're insane
Literally insane
Yeah, I mean
I
Don't care about you summer. Okay. I came home by psychic and you trust me bitch trust me in that
I believe that so never go up and talk shit. He doesn't good, but so you trust me
Action speak louder than words action speak louder than words
Yeah, so she hopes my show gets taken down it's like obviously not that great
and she calls me a junkie and sweet like that
Little girl little girl the little girls go
Oh, well, it's it's like, you know, it's sad. It's uh, you know, I'm sure there's gonna be some more more of it, you know, but
You know
Sometimes, you know
Things have to be shown
Does it demonstrate to me and it's like, okay
They want to do it that to me. Okay
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, okay. Well, anyway, I think I'm about over that and you know, it's like what it's like
How much more can you slander me? I mean, it's you're sitting there fucking all this upset on the show tonight and
It's like
Right. It's like all this with all that was said, you know
To be part of that, you know, and there's people in the chat too that I was really disappointed and seeing there and like, you know
I know stuff
I know someone reported to be that like what I our conversation private conversation
I heard last night that person was supposed to be a friend. I just expressed my opinion
And then it's like, you know, be the nodes and then he's gonna say oh well, he told Alex this and that I mean
It's like she's threatening, you know legal action for like nothing, you know, it's like whatever
Whatever I never did anything to them. They just got they were just mad over like how I ran my show
How I choose to run my show and it's like expecting me to like like
Listen to like just like oh and this and this and this I mean
It's like all the people that she's saying over such great friends aren't over there
You know, it's like so what it's like if they're gonna be like such they're gonna be just like such easily easy enemies turncoat
Then it's like they weren't friends to begin with they're just like
Followers, you know, it's just like they just want to they're just going to like work
I just like okay
This is like kind of like where they think it's like the popular crowd now and it's like I'm disparaged and it's like and it's like
I'm this big loser and that it's like they're all so cool and perfect and it's like talk about me taking responsibility
Did anybody say no one's even allowed to say anything? Well, it's like, you know
He did like Canada dries to say something about Christine because Christine's name was brought up as like some paragon of
Good in the world, but you know, whatever
It's just like
Hmm
Well
I'm over it. Um, I'm not schizophrenic. I'm not crying. I'm uh,
You know, I'm being
Criminally her oh, he's gone being criminally harassed actually criminally harassed. Oh, who's that? Is it God back there? Oh God's back here
I'm sorry God. I miss you
Yo, so pal step how are you doing?
I'm good. You having a bad night?
I didn't have a bad night. It was just like an interesting day, you know
The scrap metal people coming over then it's like, you know a second meeting of the psyche haters club
just like spreading lies about me saying I I
Learned to tarot like a month like a month ago or something. I don't know. It's nothing you can do about that, man
So I don't even bother don't don't listen to it. That's all
You're gonna send yourself into a fucking vortex of misery if you keep listening to it
Well, I want to see what's being said, but you know what? Yeah, but I mean how many times can you hear it?
You know, it was the same shit. You're right. So I was like, okay
It's just gonna be another one of those, you know, what do you want?
What do you want out of this? You want to be positive and spread your message?
You want to wallow in misery with people fucking hate on you
You need to get it out first. What did you say the other day go hate yourself?
It was a some song or some shit like that, right? Go hate yourself. It's perfect
Just tell them to go hate themselves. They should if they choose to hate you. That's their business
Yeah, I mean there's some good people over there. Don't get me wrong
You know, I don't know there's something they got offended by something you did or whatever
That's their business man. I'm not gonna get into it, but hey
Don't let it fucking gets you man
I know how they get to me. I'm fine. I'm not crying. They're saying it. They say I cry and stuff. I'm not crying
I'm like I know I know how you feel you you thought of these people as friends and they thought you as friends
So this is how it is both sides are feeling the same fucking way and nobody fucking wants to man up and say that's what's going on
Right well, you know, it's like
If they want to hate me they can hate me it says it's like, you know, of course, I'm gonna be hated
And every everybody that has any kind of audience or follow it's gonna have detractors and stuff like that
So it's it's fine, you know, but I am a
Kind of like okay. Wow. It's just like because it's like it's just like so yeah
I shouldn't watch any more because it is just like so slanderous and
But also they had the guy that they you know, they all listen to Tony or whatever. He's up there
You know, he's the one that's doing all this stuff. Oh, yeah, why shouldn't you say his name? Oh, yeah
What was his fake name? So it's not his real name, so
Um, yeah, and then she in summer says she hopes my channel gets taken. Okay. Well, and she's gonna be laughing at
She she thinks it's so funny that alex is fooling me, of course alex is annoying
But it's like alex is he's not a bad guy and that's what I said from the beginning. It's like ice and then
Yeah, I don't think I don't think I was in the summer. She said I don't want your channel taken down
She I don't think she wants anything bad to happen to you. Yes. She's mad. She's just mad at you man
and then um, and then you know and
Unless she's just mad, but it's like she could have
At least like said one positive thing about me, you know, even though it's like not the audience for and they're probably wouldn't like it
You know, she could say that mean but yeah, of course, she doesn't have to it would have been nice
I said just like I told her yesterday and she's like I don't have the energy to say something nice about you
I guess she only had the energy to say something bad like right because uh, she has certainly had the energy for that
She certainly had the energy to go on there and you know talk shit about how stupid I am and
um you know how just like it's some some fool I'm just fooled by everybody and I don't and
every little thing so I'm but it's like these people are some people are still in the room
and stuff and it's like I can't prevent that but I'm gonna prevent them from
Talking in the room, and it's like what is that like anybody that doesn't agree with me? No
It's like you can disagree with me, but it's like if you sit there and fuck in or just are just negative trolling me
Why does that? Why do I have to put up with that?
It's like we don't I don't come into mold you into somebody I like I come here because fucking just somebody to hang with
Somebody cool to talk to about stuff. Yeah, you know, you don't give no bullshit to people
I really get it you get a little caught up in this you get a little caught up in this don't get me wrong
I've seen you get caught up in this you kick me off for bullshit or whatever reasons
It's a new day the next day
Yeah, what can be good the next day, but it's like you're a different kind of person
You're like a cool person like I didn't see you over there
Saying shit about me and it's like you know, and it's like
you could have, you know, you could have
I'd be over there talking the biggest shit about you if I could have
Did you just miss it? You just missed the, uh,
I would have fucking shit on you all night
I know you would I would have spent an hour just talking about your dirty fingernails. Oh my gosh. Yeah
They're filthy look
Disgusting there isn't I'm just listen. It's very simple everyone just accept him for who he is man. Don't fucking judge him
I know
Shit on the back. That's it
He's doing this and this to straight men like straight men can you know straight?
Don't straight men rule the world like straight white men rule the world those those aren't straight men
those aren't fucking straight men that you do anything.
Straight, right?
It's like, so, for some of those guys.
And so, I mean, God, it's like,
I'm just, I trigger people because,
maybe because I am out or because I am,
but wait, wait, straight men need all this protection.
It's like straight men can defend themselves.
You know, I think everyone can defend themselves.
So I'll defend myself from no one.
But,
You know, but if I see if I see somebody if I see one of my mods or something like that in trouble
I will go defend them and oh when you do when you do that gay shit. I just look fucking leave
Oh, come on. God, you when you when you and Alex were up here gain it up all you the last two days
I just fucking left. I'm not gonna complain about it. I just leave
Yeah, just leave. I mean, it's like
That's the thing if you guys want to
I wouldn't hit on you. I don't want to listen to it. I wouldn't hit on you
But no you couldn't you are a good friend and you are like someone that
You know, I do appreciate you you tried one time. I told you I'd cut your throat. I
Cried no, no you tried you tried to
But I know you wouldn't do that right no, no never okay. Well, thank you
What's this about scrap metal though that strikes me as weird?
Yeah, well they just like put an ad that says I'm giving away solid scrap metal or something and so
So they come knock on your door. Yeah, and then they say oh well
He's asleep inside or like my grandfather's asleep or something
Oh fuck knock really loud and stuff and so they were just banging banging banging banging banging. Oh shit. Yeah
That's fucked up. Yeah, I started going down and like
telling them and they would pull up in a truck and they'd look all confused and stuff and say oh
I'm talking to you on the phone right now or something like that. I'm like, no, it's not me
You know, you need go spend 200 bucks and get a camera for downstairs. Just put a camera
I mean, there's cameras here. There's cameras here, but they can't do I mean, it's like
Yeah, but something you can see you don't have access to them
I have access to the camera, but it's like, yeah, watch so I can see but I know who it is
It's just like people that are confused that are being told like to go here
Um and ask for scrap metal. It's not their fault. It's I have to I had to find out where that guy lives and then contact
The police in his area and then yeah, that's crazy. I have his name. So it's the same person. Yeah
See the one with the Louisiana number
Well, that's just the bacon. They think it's just those are just text now numbers. It's like, um, but yeah
he used a text now number and
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah people are bored
Yep, it's a super lame super
Yeah, they're bored
Dude just do you do it fucking you like to do on the panel do your tarot or whatever talk about whatever you want the stuff
You do with Alex, you know, you have a good time just do that. I know she can't be here every day
But you know do stuff like that. I
will
I mean, I'm yeah, but gosh, I'm taking my show back over and it's I mean my shows
I mean I have my show like my problem is this like I
Like to sometimes I like I should be like the front and center of the show
But sometimes I would like you know get in the background and stuff. I'm sorry. I'm not looking at chat really. It's just like I see
I will look at it again. I'm also like a little bit distracted right now
But I love you most of the people in chat. I love you. It's like gosh
I hate I don't like to like even dislike anybody, but it's like
I can only be pushed so far turn the cheek other cheek so much. I'm not crying. I'm sure that there's gonna be another show about me
I'm just gonna be blocking his
His channels. I don't even see and I don't even know it's not my business what other people think about me. It's just my business
To be myself, you know
So it's weird people get caught up in group mentality on this stuff they just go crazy
Yeah, I've seen a million times
Yeah, I mean that's what it is. It just seems like it's like a bunch of like people like looking for like a group and it's like
Oh, they can hate bond over me and stuff and
So they can
Yeah, well, there's some good people in the middle of it. I just don't understand they get caught up in the shit
Right, but it's like, you know, they're so easy. I mean just people are such a sheep and it's like you and like Bronford has it to be mouth
It's like
But I didn't do anything to him. I mean, it's like really as I asked him or like she's like you need to take responsibility
I said take responsibility for what what for like and then did she have any answer? No
She'd have any answer. I mean, it's like for all this stuff like what what the clapping system or you know
I mean, it's like all she was like literally because of the ghost thing because and they're saying I still think ghosts is
Tony
And then Tony, and then he's like, oh my God, he's so dumb.
No, it's like, I don't think Ghost is Tony.
That was Alex saying that.
I did one night, you know, I did maybe think that just
for one night.
What, is that like a sin to like, you know,
think two voices are similar?
And they are, they do have similar cadences, I must say.
Ghost and Tony?
Yeah, they have a little bit of a similar cadence.
And so, yeah.
And so, yeah, maybe one night, but then I saw him
and I know the difference.
Yeah, I just like I have so many good people here
And I like you know, he man was right when she said oh, he's surrounded by good people
I do have great people around here
I'd like you and but I think Alex is a great person
I'm not like fooled by people and it's like maybe I have had a problem with Alex at certain times in my life
and you know, but
You know, I'm uh, I like him for the most part and that's your boy
That's your boy. I mean they got accepted that you like the guy you want him up here
Yeah, I mean it's like that's the thing. They're not gonna come up here while he's up because he's gonna yell at everybody
Nobody wants to hear that. Yeah, I know I know I know that's why he does it
He wants to be alone with you. He does it to be alone with you. Everybody knows that
That's fine. Alex. You want to be alone with psyche? That's fine. Nobody's gonna interrupt you guys
Yeah
People just gonna accept psyche for how he is
Some is one of the best people on here.
If you don't like me, it's like,
how about just like, don't watch my show.
It's like, why are people so like, just into hating me?
It's like, I don't do hate streams.
It's like, you know, I do like response streams sometimes,
but it's like, do I sit there and say,
let me find every single person that hates this person,
or like, you know, have like, you know,
big like banner, everyone come in here,
and then, you know, the bash psyche, and then, you know,
and then,
Look, it's the ultimate crime to talk about people on here
If you talk about somebody and they heard you say something about somebody or somebody told them you were talking about them
It's the biggest crime in the world
Yeah, what are we fucking talking about me? Can't you my name are you fucking mom?
Everybody's fucking hot up about hearing their fucking name mentioned about some shit or it's all we do on this fucking shit
Yeah, people don't realize all we do is talk shit to each other well get over it and I was like
I'm happy to talk so I'll talk I'll talk some people will talk some shit people don't agree with me and stuff like that all the time
It's like when a certain
Slanders things and it's like you know, that's what it is. It's like you're not built for this shit, man
You're not built for slander
Well, it's like like me me. I can take slander all the long
Does anybody like I'm like lies being told about it. I love it
Oh, God, he is just some disgusting cover person with like, you know, he's a fat fuck in a wheelchair that motherfucker
I love it. I love it. I can keep saying it. I love it. I feed off it
It's not true though. I mean, it's like doesn't matter though
It doesn't fucking matter. They want it. I mean, it's like, okay, like, you know, a wheelchair is like, but it's like talking about things. I don't know. It's just like, it's just like, I feel very, you know, ganged up on and stuff. I don't know.
To like, you know help help people like be happy and it's like people are like, oh, he doesn't even do chair
We're just like, okay. Well, whatever like I
I'm not in the best mood to do it,
plus I don't like push it on people.
I'll do it on TikTok the whole time I do it on TikTok, right?
But it's like.
You wanna do it for people that appreciate it.
Right, I don't, yeah.
And it's like half the people were asked,
they were wasting a time and stuff like that
when they're like trolling,
asking for a readings and stuff like that.
And or they don't appreciate it.
And it's like, and I mean, it's like, so what?
It's like, and it's whatever my show is, it's my show.
Like worry about your own show or you don't have a show
or people that have shows, like worry about your own
like, worry about yourself.
Like, how about like, fix your life?
Like, do you have a perfect life?
And it's like, just me that needs to be like,
you know, put it in the corner and like, you know,
it's like, everyone has things they can fix about themselves.
Why are they constantly projecting their shadows onto me?
And then it's like, I'm supposed to like carry it all.
And it's like they're all these perfect people, right? It's like and they never done anything wrong and it's like
I mean, it's like it's just like that's the attitude. I told you before man
I told you months ago your show became a nexus point for all the trolls
Everybody just flocked over here
And interacted with each other and then all of a sudden you offended them all and most of them left
Fender the trolls. I mean, I mean, that's yeah, that's what it seems like, right? Well, yeah, I guess so it's like
Um, but how do I I mean, I don't even know how do you offend a troll? Like what do it dude? It happened
I don't know how you did it, but it fucking happened. Wow. I'm pretty amazing if I can do that, you know, it's like
Wow, I can actually troll trolls like oh
but uh, oh
Gosh
And uh, yeah, well how about
I'm not gonna fucking not gonna worry about it anymore. Yeah, don't worry about it, man
Play some videos
If you like me you can like me you don't like me
Yeah, just watch somebody else like it goes somewhere else
I'm not I don't need to be it just constantly like what what is it about like these people just loving to attack though
It's like, you know, it's just like
Like they want you to die be humbled. They want you dead. I am I have like the littlest ego
It's like, you know, I have a little bit of an ego just to be on but what you want to be humbled
I need to be like crawling on the ground. How about you need to be humbled bronze bird?
You mean you're the biggest narcissist I've ever seen in my life like how about you need to be humbled like but I do
I say that no, but you know if you think I need to be
You guys just could ignore each other at this point. Okay, you're just gonna go endlessly
Well, you know, he won't because he gets so much attention from doing this. He was like, so let him do it
Let him do it. If that makes me
But they don't listen you can't you can't stop them. It's what I'm saying
Just
Just do what you like to do man. Do the ai videos play with the ai dudes and uh, just do you
You'll have your people over here
Will I mean I have good people here. I have like a I'm a good show, okay
I'm gonna play some videos and stuff. I'll play some videos man. I'm gonna leave early and like
You know
I'm like really like it doesn't even matter if I lose my channel at this point. It's like what why are you gonna lose it?
Well, because he's saying he's gonna threat he's gonna strike over the AI song summers summer says oh, I can't wait to see that
You know, it's gonna be great. You are gonna lose a blah blah
I mean, it's like even just put that out there and she was a mod at the time. She's just mad at your man
That's all well, I mean, you know, there's no reason to be mad at me
She was the one on another show bad mouthing me. I wasn't on another show bad mouthing her
I've always been kinder and so I don't know if it's like talking about taking responsibility
How about take responsibility for your actions? Okay?
How about we all take responsibility for our own?
Why am I taking responsibility for everybody's actions?
I'm the only person that has to.
It's like, just doesn't make sense.
Doesn't make fucking sense.
I'm just very confused about it.
Like, it's like, what?
It's like, Q makes us a homeless guy in his tent.
And it's like, people are more forgiving of that
than they are of, you know,
Me, like, you know, it's hitting on me.
I mean, it's just stupid.
It's like, gosh.
That was fucking amazing.
I still can't get over that.
Yeah.
He maces the guy right in the face. He fucking basically hate crimes the guy. Yeah, and then he runs away
He runs away. Please Lord forgive me for I have sinned. Please Lord
Please forgive me Lord for I have sinned against you. Yeah, please and then he runs to the bus stop and fucking VB fucking
Basically runs him over with that 1987 truck that she has
The fuck the whole thing was like a fucking like a scene out of Grand Theft Auto
Yeah, I'm so fucking bad
It was very interesting, very interesting, but it's like, but yeah, but he's I don't see people saying people starting live
I mean, that's like they played the clip there, but they're like laughing and it's like oh my god
Some people are shocked, but it's like
Ah, you know, forgive him, you know, forgive him, you know, it's like, oh, he's a he's, you know, he's much cuter than me or something like that.
He has great hair. It's like, so he's fine. Nothing. But it's like me. It's like, you know, I'm just like some dirty F-A-G-G-O-T.
So, you know, I can't get away with anything, right?
Yeah. Words hurt, man. Some people, some people can't take it. I don't know. They don't care.
Yeah, definitely don't care about me. I don't know. I don't know but um
Well, it's like, you know, of course, I mean most I mean
I would have thought a few people there that I saw you know, it's hurtful when it's like
People are you think are your friends and stuff like that?
Including some people that were mods and stuff like that and it's like and I've never never ever had a problem with them in the chat or anything
And it's like but they're over there and it's like and then people are telling me to stuff that I tell them
And it's like and then she's reading all my messages and it's like I I never shared all her messages and it's like and then I
don't know so
I mean, I don't know. I'm not I'm just like I have no need to do that
But okay, look at it. No, that's how she wants to play and I can play to you, but
whatever it's like not I mean it's not worth my time energy or grief to to to
look into it anymore or to give it more energy than it deserves and so I'm over
it so I'm good I'm good maybe you're just hungry man go eat something well I
have McDonald's already and yeah that would put make anyone depressed eat
McDonald's every day I know it does it does not something the best food for you
Yeah, but it's all I can enjoy right now, so.
I mean, I actually, I'm gonna probably go buy like a bunch of
cups and noodles or something for the week, so.
Cups and noodles are good.
Yeah.
No.
They're okay.
You fry an egg and put it in there, it's even better.
Sometimes I do, but eggs are kind of expensive now.
Eggs are very expensive, yeah.
Oh, people are asking for the link.
Okay, Mr. Link, who's asking for it?
I don't know, Paulo said something and then I think Time said something.
Okay.
So I mean, it's okay. I mean, it's like really it's like and also I'm also like my house is cleaner than it's ever been
And I also I had I've admitted to like and plus I've been on on the camera every day
And so you can see that you can see how dirty I am or you can see how dirty the house is, right?
Like and or it's like, you know people to pick pause and like zero. Oh my gosh, just in this I mean, it's like like it's like
Like I'm living in some hoarded out
We've we've seen
They say I'm like I'm like a homeless person
Oh please man come on
Why are they making fun of homeless people first of all?
But I'm actually in a in a home that is like mine
So it's like
I'm sure they live in worse fucking conditions than anybody
I mean, it's like who knows it's like I don't I'm not here to judge people and it's like it certainly I wouldn't
Certainly if somebody had HIV or somebody was homeless
I wouldn't be sitting here like making fun of them on my show like I'm some wonderful person
It's like that would kind of like I feel that would be kind of like
Picking on somebody that is already having a hard time. It'd be like picking on somebody in a tent. You know
Yeah, that's not cool you don't want to pick up somebody in a tent
I mean, I don't know what Q's problem is the guy was spooning with this guy in the tent for like a week and a half
And then all of a sudden he got mad at Paula. What do you got to say about all this Apollo?
One moment one moment, please. Sorry. Oh shit. Oh, I'm gonna wait for you. Okay. Go ahead
Fucking old man. He comes up here unprepared. Oh, you had to change this picture. You had to change this picture
Everybody look at it. You had to say Apollo. Yeah, that fucking fake. What was that fake name you had earlier?
Is that the one you use at the other fucking panels you go to? Huh?
Which one the one you had before this what was that shit you just had nothing nothing forget it forget it delete it
What's going on say to me and I said I already said this thing she had to say to me on that on that show cuz she knows
I was listening. Oh, there's guys
You were talking this whole time
Crystal hi
Oh my god, I can't believe it's crystal. Wow
psyche, please
Psyche, you know, you're fucking grown-ass motherfucker. Yeah, thank you crystal
And it's like some of these people try to play some weird game like like we don't own them in real life
Like you know what I mean like they don't play real life games and fucking own them
I guarantee you or you know why because they don't have a bill to fucking buck
They don't have a build-a-book. They don't have they don't have nothing a fucking
Contain do you even say hi to people crystal?
God you fag oh
This person portrays himself to be another person that is beautiful
Um, you know what it's sacrilegious. I hope he rots it. He's gonna rotten hell before we will
Yeah, 100%
100,000% you're gonna be rotten in hell in the next one year. Oh
My god one year. Oh, yeah, that's all you got left buddy. That's pretty long
Yeah, you think you got one year left
Are you gonna be there? I think I should I think I should run before she she take notice of me. Oh
Apollo you're fine you're probably fine
Please please I'm innocent
This is where I call you I think that your piece of shit to Apollo I hope you right now
That was quick there we go
Wow
Like the wind, huh?
Yeah, because you know because he said really disgusting things about children
Really Apollo
Paula knows it. It's all on video
I think I'm gonna I think it's better. I'm gonna hide you can have a it's all yours. You're good. Thanks. You can have a I got
Oh, so you think it's okay to say that
Regular I got this pal
Psychies the Cardinal I'm the God and crystals the whore Babylon
Oh, yes, you would my my body is clear. Oh, yeah, okay. I would never
Guarantee you you guys will die and rock your boyfriends here ever touch me your boyfriends here calm down
My boyfriend like I have one he's right here next to you Arthur
You know, it's good time. Have you guys ever seen Arthur in real life? Is he showing his balls?
Is he showing his balls? I don't need to.
I'm wearing shorts, asshole.
You're fine, you're fine, you're fine.
He did, uh, stick up for me, but, uh, no, Arthur and I are, like, not, uh, no, uh, I don't know.
Do you even know where you are?
I don't know. I love Arthur. I love Arthur, dude. I love that guy.
Do you even know what day it is?
Do you know what day it is God because you know what you are hey, do you know a actually hey listen?
Do you know how much you're in the jungle baby to pay your taxes? Oh my gosh
I've been doing taxes. Hey, do you know that?
Do you know that I want you know that I know what you know and I know
You know do you know that?
Did you know that you knew before you knew it?
But you know what I know about you is that you don't have a degree and you're not shit and you're not like me
I'm God. You're not. Yeah, you're not like my people. Yeah, you're not like my people. My people are God
I'm God. You're not don't need my people can be our
Okay, I'm God. You're not yeah
You can't be god. I'm god
It's okay crystal
It won't happen. It won't happen because i'm god. Hey, hey, I hope you're deep
rex
every single time. That's right.
Let's not wish bad on people.
Okay. Let's not wish bad on people.
It's okay. I can feel good and bad.
Can I tell you something?
I love Chris. I'm running.
I think she's pretty and I like her personality.
See?
Everyone's into drive, please.
See, that's how I go, psyche.
Yeah, whatever.
Oh, good times. Tell him.
Tell him what?
Right.
Tell him that you want his Jeep to rack.
I
You feel why he wants me how you feel how you feel why wouldn't you want him to his teacher actually he wants me
Nobody wants you to get that
We
Good luck with that
You ain't got shit
Yeah, we got every part of your information. Oh good
Oh good
and you're gonna fucking pin his ass yet.
Oh yeah, every day.
He's been telling me it's real bad.
Every day.
I'm doing it right now.
I'm fucking doing it right now, right 20.
Good times.
I have it on record and I'd like to listen.
He's being really ridiculous with other people, and I'm gonna fucking make sure that I'm really ridiculous with his other people.
You know how that works. Good times. You know how that works?
I'm listening to you, woman.
So, you know how ridiculous it is when he does shit to me
Well, he will die
God can't die crystal don't be stupid. This is a cult of Gotti dummy high priest
With your own words, bitch. I said with your own words, bitch. You're condescending faggot
You're condescending you're gonna die. God is never gonna forgive you because you're a fucking faggot
It's so damn naive so so you're saying that you're on you're on site stream
Which we all know he's homosexual. I don't have problem with that
But not now you're talking about people are good get a die and go to hell cuz they're a faggot
No, no, no, no, no, it does not because okay. Yeah, don't say the word
And that Christmas no, no, no, you got double standards. You let her say it. Yeah, because I don't really
Over and over. Oh, let's all just say it
I say that I say that because
The way that he's saying that he wants to kill me and rape and grape and all
I never heard him say he wants to do any of those things. I'm not even gonna say the words
I saw it
Well, I have it on video I have it on video that he said it I'm thinking it right now
Actually, it's not that it's not right here. He didn't say it on other fucking videos
This guy's trying to grate me and fucking do
And I got it on video
Grape so we're gonna we're gonna make sure that we get him back
I can't wait, you know what guys I still think my great videos by you know like men like men like I'm big
We're gonna make sure that guys get him back. You know, he's not gonna be able to attack a woman
Do you understand what i'm getting at? How far can she go? Let's let's keep listening
Do you understand what i'm getting at? He's never gonna be able to attack a woman again
Is that the worst that could happen?
That's for factual
Crystal you're the best. Maxwell factual. I got a special place for you, crystal
Well, I got a special fate place for you. It's in um, it's in man. Hell. Oh
Prison where you fucking deserve to get great. Oh, is that what you think about? Yeah
That's what I think about you. That's what I think about you. That's what you did
Crystal you did to me. You sick faggot
And you're going to help and and not only are you going to help I'm gonna make sure you get wiped your family gets wiped at this
Promise you I
Love this
What's next gonna make sure he's gone
Hey, hey listen good times it'll take us it'll take us two poopies
Shit and did she say poopy?
Yeah, a poopie.
Crystal, you're an adult.
Two poopies.
I think you don't have kids.
No, I should have a kid if she ever dates me.
Never.
No, I would never have a kid.
And I would never have a kid, especially with good times.
I have a good genetics.
I don't know what your problem is.
Good times, but I do love you though.
Well, we go back and forth.
I love you too. Don't worry about it.
When are you two going to hook up?
Well, according to Chris Marie, never!
Well, you could always grape her.
No!
Are you sick of the head dude live you could do it live on stream. Oh my god. I'd be fucking sick
He just bust into a kick the door down in the house and just do it
That'd be almost as epic as you reporting you to FBI. Do you not know anything about FBI and good times?
I do yes
FB I
Dude, dude, you're you're like you're saying some weird shit motherfucker. All right
Like I thought I thought Crystal was trolling. No, I'm listening to you and oh dude
It gets really dark. I can't believe it's coming out of your mouth, dude. This is where it gets dark
No, I want to listen to Crystal talk about how creepy you are. All right. Go ahead crystal
No, she's she's talking the FBI right now. She can't talk
Are you stupid?
Good times.
Yes. I'm here.
Code.
Which code?
I can't tell you the code or it's gonna be too known.
But yeah
I thought you I thought you're having a freak out and then I started listening to this other guy and I'm like oh my god
He's actually fucking crazy
No, you know, I you know what one that is for me
Well, it's my same month for everybody right? Oh, yeah, but you know, it's it's the most important month
Yeah, she's doing it again
Yeah, I told you
Yeah, she goes by Crystal Marie
Yeah
I don't know who you are.
Yeah, you're all set, Crystal.
You don't even know anything about me.
Just say where you are.
I'm gonna have fashion week, all week.
You fucking...
Yeah, fashion my ass.
Okay, ha ha, he he.
Yeah, I just walked for fucking fashion people, okay?
You can't even walk straight.
What are you talking about?
You fucking wobble all over the place.
We don't know shit.
Well, I walk.
I've seen you walk.
I'm sorry, I'm trying not to laugh, but...
That's a fucking flamingo.
You're walking.
I've seen you walk.
I'm sorry, I'm trying not to laugh, but...
are you calling her flamingo that doesn't make any sense
well you ever see her legs?
I've seen Crystal, she's a normal MBA
I've seen her too
yeah my legs are not skinny at all
I have thick legs. You're fucking retard. You're fucking retard. I have thick ass legs. You see that I'm hard to bag it.
I don't have fucking stupid skinny legs.
Okay, you're like a stick figure. Okay, whatever.
So where are you seeing fat women? Where are you seeing them?
At least somebody with some meat. She's all bones.
No, she's not.
Trust me, dude.
No, no, trust me. She's just to go ahead show them. I don't think you've seen you lately
This guy's a retard
The truth is very retarded
You know you want to like defend yourself in a certain sense, but you know like what do you do like you can
Keep redoing like the same old retard shit, you know good times
You know what I look like in this motherfucker. I know what you look like you're not
Storker, what a genius fuck bro. Don't lie to yourself
If you like them skinny, hey, that's you. That's you if you like them. Yeah, they're fake, but that's fine
They don't match you they don't match you though. They don't match
You sell like your game never been with women before yeah, I know good times. I know because you know exactly how that sounds
No, he sounds stupid as fuck. This is where he starts defending his crystal. Let's go in on him. Let's go. Let's go
Let's go. I will I'll see Chris. I'm waiting before I ever seen you on camera
No, you know what this guy looks like he looks you know
He's fat and he's white and he's old as fuck. He's old as fuck good times
He's way older than you. He's older than
And then and then he lives and then he lives with his parents and his parents every bit of his bills, right?
and he lives uh like nothing you say can fucking affect me he works hey hey hey good times i'm
listening to chrysal hey he thinks that he's cool because he has a jeep i give him that he thinks
that he's cool did he have that girls have jeeps he thinks that he's cool i heard what she said
she said it women have jeeps
No, actually is a thing like women are and jeeps
cheap cheap
Yeah
Crystal speaking facts like women are into jeeps. Okay, and he is so fucking judgy because he is a jeep bitch and
He got his jeep taken away
Because of blackout Andy said that he didn't pay his entrance
Walt
Isn't he like a level five sex offender?
No, but you are these are your friends crystal. No, but that's you you're these are your friends
I don't know why you want my name in D all of a sudden he changed the subject to talk about sex offenders
What is he doing?
Well what I'm wrong
Do you see how he is?
Am I wrong?
I don't know Chris
No he's a sex offender
I don't think I'm wrong good times I think you know I'm right
You see what he is?
He's a sex offender
You don't want to admit it
You people are surrounded by weirdos and sex offenders
Yep that's what he is
He is an hate criminal
He is a level
um 20 sex offender he listen these are your friends these are all your friends good times good times
this guy uh is trying to commit little children to do bad here we go with the kids now what is he
trying to do jesus christ what's with you and kids he's trying to get kids to do uh sex it can you
Drown yourself
He's trying to do sex crimes against us and
Letting little children and men little boys do his crimes for him. So he won't get charged himself. I
Would not be surprised if his son is a sex offender
He's a fucking
Child abuser. He's a bad person
Crystal you want him to rot in hell good time. I'm asking God. This is
This is why God
This is why God, you know answer the question crystal were you abused?
absolutely not you were definitely not you were definitely you were don't lie to
people you were definitely abused hey you are definitely abused by listen don't
get a lot about it there's no need to yell there's no need to yell about that's
what happened to you people can be sympathetic
this guy is definitely his mother and his father definitely sexually abused him I can
definitely tell him I didn't say it to trigger you I didn't say it to trigger you
Can you guys not tell you sound like somebody who's actually he has he has zero dollars in his bank accounts
Um, he lets I love her imagination though. You gotta love that. Hey, listen good times
he's letting
He uh, he's going by what these he wants. Okay. Who said I would let me let me let me let me let me let me
I keep my money
Can you block the guy? Can you just remove him or something?
I could leave if you ask nicely
This is this is Larry
Fucking what's his name psyche stream? You could ask me to leave nicely. Oh, okay
Listen good side Papa. You know how I am
We've known each other for a thousand motherfucking years.
This motherfucker is trying to play me.
And guess what, Papa?
He's about to get played hard.
He's about to get his whole family played.
He's a papa.
He's about to get his whole entire life played
because he tried to play too hard.
well, no, he's just playing back and audio,
which is for, it forces me to leave.
He won't be, he won't be, he won't be.
He won't be, he won't be, he won't be, he won't be.
Stop saying what, David.
Crystal, do you want to pop over my stream in Ramble?
Oh, why don't you call me, sir?
All right, you'll come over in my stream,
I'm gonna go live here.
Okay.
All right.
Well, I got another beer right here.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Sometimes about to get something tonight.
Good work, kid
You take care of that. You take care of that. You graped that. You graped that when you get the chance.
You rape that all you want. Hey, hey, listen, I think you threw it at me.
Good times can have you, man. I don't care.
You're rapey, dude. Nobody wants to talk to you. We're never going to talk to you for hours.
We're never going to talk to you rapey.
Go ahead. Bye-bye.
Hey, good times.
Bye-bye.
Love you, too. Oh nice
They found each other see who says you can't find love and chat
Don't make that fucking face just go just go take take your bitch old man
Making faces I did them a favor now look at them that together
They'll be talking about me for an hour
Should be talking about grape
And he'll just sit there and be like, yeah, yeah, uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
It's the Gotti show now, motherfuckers.
This is what you've been waiting for.
So I don't know what the fuck is going on between all your people.
Driving psyche insane.
He's driving you people insane.
I don't know what's going to fucking end game to all this.
But I mean, don't you guys get sick of all the crying?
He did this to me. She said that about me blah blah blah. It's the same old shit
There's one thing if you don't know anything about me. Just know that I hate fucking repetition. I
Hate watching the same shit over and over again. I
Have left so many communities over that shit
Same bullshit
This one bitchin about that one that one bitchin about this one
then rinse and repeat and do it all over again it's fucking boring and maybe you
guys get off on it both sides but fuck it's it's not fun to me but I'm coming
here to fucking laugh and fucking crack on people but you guys all take it
serious I'm talking about both sides
You got people crying about every fucking little thing
It's one of the first things I witnessed when I came here
That's like why are they always fucking crying? It was who was it?
Who was it was that fucking ugly bitch Amanda always crying about some shit? Oh,
Psyche they came from a group. I saw them. They're a gang
They're in a gang
What the fuck yo Psyche you better watch them they're in a gang
So much for that bullshit, huh Amanda?
The gang is still here
And now look it's the fucking gaudy show
Cry about it bitch
Whoever has a problem with a cry about it
Because you know I don't give a fuck
But if you guys want to keep doing what you're doing have fun
I'm not gonna get involved just do you
Have your four-hour marathon streams about
He did this to me or she did that to me and
Whatever wallow and misery. What do they say?
misery loves company
We'll do it
In the meantime, I'll just be somewhere laughing about it all. Oh
Yes, you do Amanda you care you care more than most
That's the problem you care more than most because you're miserable
When I hear you talk Amanda, I think oh my god this woman every fucking day she needs to get up
It's like if death came and knocked on your door you'd fucking jump you'd be like, oh, thank you finally finally you came to get me
You're not a happy person Amanda admit it and you'll say it's because of all the problems in your life you're sick
Or the dog sick or somebody else is sick
We'll have an excuse, but the truth is you're just not a happy person. I
Don't know what it is. I think it's because God made you ugly or something like that and you can't get over it
But you need to
He's killing you on the inside
People are usually a reflection of their inside
Look at um, I'm gonna give you an example
Look at fucking page. Okay, you know page everybody loves page
Very pretty girl very nice very sweet
But she's a reflection of her inner self
She's beautiful on the inside so she's beautiful on the outside
same thing with Alexandra
Very nice person very sweet woman
Same thing
But you Amanda
Oh my God. All you exude is hate. Hate and misery.
And that's one thing to be so hateful about yourself.
But you try to spread it on other people. You try to spread your hate to other people. It's horrible.
And then you donate like 2.99 to psyche and you're supposed to brainwash them to do what you want.
It was so fucking embarrassing
It got you know what it got you it got you angry because you ended up fucking leaving cuz he didn't give a fuck what you had to say
Remember that one
Shit it's too easy
This is why Alex does what he does he comes up here you fucking shits on everybody
And he fucking laughs at you all
Yeah, so what he's an asshole he fucking yells and everything like that who cares
But fucking you all hate him because of it. He loves it. He loves being hated people give him what he wants
Just wants to be alone with psyche, that's it he'll admit it too
My first came here it was that guy
Michael Leguizam, whatever the fuck his name is used to come up here and used to fucking sit up on the panel
He'd shit on every woman that would come up here. Like you could you see it?
You'd shit on he hated women
Because he had that fat girlfriend remember that he said he had he was with that fat girl and
The way he would talk to say Apollo the way he would talk to psyche like like they were boyfriend and girlfriend
You know and and Michael was the girlfriend
And he'd be all sad that psyche wasn't paying him attention, but you guys all you remember that shit
And then one day he said fuck it
I'm not gonna come to psyches anymore because I think people would time them out people would kick them off the pound for like 25 bucks
Whatever it was
So you started going to beat us and beta just beat a fucking shit on them over there
I think I went there one time the whole place was shitting on this guy
Which you know rightfully so because the thing you did to Tracy
money that he took. I don't know if you know this stuff, Apollo. But they, they fucking
sure this guy. Now I didn't know how I didn't know about his depression. This guy had like
mad depression. And I guess you this is what he would lash out at people because he was
depressed. That and the fat girlfriend that he had. But you know, he killed himself, right?
He killed himself over all that shit. Yeah. Yeah, people don't know about that part.
Fucking drama
Overall the shit that was going on in his life this included. Oh
You think that anybody would fucking say oh my god
This guy killed himself. We treated him like shit blah blah blah. No, nobody gave a fuck
I mean the guy was an asshole, you know
If you really know he's really dead don't make up a rain
I'm not making fun. I'm proving a point. My princess. My princess. Oh my gosh. Get away from me.
I'm just here to talk to my big bro, Gotti. It's about time. I worship the floor you're walking on.
Can I kiss your feet? These are my two. Don't even touch me. You're fucking weird.
Hell's wrong with you. You're not allowed anywhere around my feet. Don't don't don't do it man. I'll kick you off my show
Body will kick you
Where's psyche he's taking a nap in the background
He's recouping
I love his priest outfit today. Yeah, that's cool. I didn't get to tell him that was really cool
Yeah, it looks really cool. Yo, what's up, Gotti?
Sub-Ziled
Okay
Nah, bro. I ain't in my fee fees, bro
It's like psyche was laying troll bait for like two and a half months
And I just finally bit in on it when my bro Bronzeberg decided he was gonna bite in on it like fuck it
You know is the energy he was begging for
Had he just left well enough
What why does it have to go on for so long?
You know it goes on for way too long
That's what I was saying originally like had he left it alone after his first two three live streams
But two and a half months before we even responded, bro
But he just kept it going
You guys, you know, it's I'll say the same thing to you guys you don't have to listen
She doesn't listen to you guys, you don't have to listen to him.
That's what God was talking about, that's what God was talking about, right?
He said that, she said that, blah, blah, cry, cry, cry.
But the thing is, you know, I come over here to see other people too, like you, Gotti, you know,
this is one of the only places I see you around, brother man.
I try to keep it small circles, you know, I can't be everywhere at once.
Like some people want me to be.
Yeah, yeah, there's a lot of people that are actually
You know genuinely in their feelings, but as you could tell by the tone of my voice
I'm not in my feelings, bro. I do this
Every day across hundreds of channels, you know I'm saying I'm just a man
It just takes away from the fun, you know, you have a channel you want to have fun on your channel
You have a good time doing what you want to do. I don't know. It's people get have a good time with the drama
It doesn't sound like it man. Well, I actually it's always the same. It's always the same drama
He said that he said that was Apollo. I actually come from a drama community
There we go. What do you where do you think I come from?
Yeah, I know I know I'm very much aware who you used to hang around with yeah, dude
I what I said, honey, it rings true man. I I'm sick of the fucking repetition
Yeah, I mean it does get old and I take my break sometimes but I have my
It's new face is new people, you know new names, but it's the same story over and over again
Yeah, yeah, it's been that way for many many years around this bitch, too
This the same the show different actors
You know the story about me being in a wheelchair. Oh
Yeah, yeah, I heard you me tell it once. Yeah, what what did you hear?
Your old man you're in a wheelchair and you have eb
Yeah, I have eb2
That's a new one that's good I like that one
Yeah, she added that one
But did she tell you why I have it?
No, no, she didn't have a backstory. It's because of her fucking face.
That is a horrible man. Horrible, horrible man.
It's because I saw her face.
Ever since then, it just fucking, it just fell to pieces.
He looked at her, at her hairline.
Yeah, that fucking hairline.
Like the never ending story.
so she's got a hairline of a 55-year-old man, huh?
Yeah, she does. You haven't seen that shit.
What's up, Kazoom?
Hey, nice to meet you.
Oh, it's two good hairlines.
Wow, Kazoom and Yumi got the same hairline.
What's up, Yumi?
Oh, shit.
Kazoom, welcome to the panel.
Oh, thanks.
Welcome, welcome.
Yeah, because I wasn't sure if any more people were going to be able to be added because I don't see I don't see him here
So we honey here. We got everybody here now. It's a full show
Uh-huh, cuz no sees me all over the place. He could tell you I troll hundreds of channels, bro
Look at this. Look at what money's look at look at that fucking look at money got some dirty as fucking thing in there
Did you see that and that's your life for me?
That's your life, man. Yes. That's my entertainment. Not my life
Cameras with those dirty fucking nails man
I
Can you give the room a little positive message?
Yeah
No, you don't know anything positive smile a lot
Okay, maybe not
Well, you got the kazoo does voiceovers for a channel that often speaks about trashies
Yeah a lot of a lot of a true crime stuff. Yeah
No, but because I'm myself is a very positive dude. I'll say that
Right on I
Try to get hold of it. Do you throw pennies to Kazoo?
Can I what?
Do you troll are you a trolling your trolling panels? No, I'm not I'm not much of a troller. No, oh, okay
Because anyone here is coming from from the same community drama drama drama
Drama drama drama shut up a bottle. That's what you like
And you guys providing it thank you
of the
Say it by someone who comes from a drama community
Yep, so says I should know the birds of my feather exactly
That's the point you all you all point is if the finger of each other and none of you are different you're practically
twins
All of you to putting all look at him. Look at him. He did that. He did that and you all are the same clone
But see the trick to it is I don't do it first
Yeah, right, that's why you don't this payment, right
Han shot first have I talked shit to you without you talking shit first
My point exact didn't ever talk to any shit to you. What should I do? I don't even know you
Now you come up on panels talking mad shit talking about all of you all of you
Yeah, all of you is very broad when you're talking to a whole panel Apollo. You're talking to me, too
Okay
But only you
Get offended by it obviously
These guys are so fake, and will play the holy, the whole merry,
oh, I didn't do nothing, I didn't do nothing.
But they're jumping from panel to panel to create drama.
And when the finger pointing back to them, oh, I'm innocent.
Like Gotti said, Gotti said it 100%.
The same shit over and over and over if there is no drama the create drama over nothing
I'm sorry Paulo. I had to drop down because I was so offended
Okay
You got me there
So what's new church anything else you
You want to talk about other than confronting Psyche about some silly shit?
I actually said that I would have a conversation with Psyche if he wants to.
Okay, okay, let's start one then.
So that's kind of like, well Psyche's not here.
Oh, well there's someone that's managing the people coming in and out, approving and all that.
But he isn't here on the panel though. You're right. I don't know why he's not here on the panel, but I
Don't know. He's probably taking a breather time to be stressed. Which would probably be the appropriate a steps, you know to take
Imagine Kazoo you have a bunch of people with no own life
bashing you for days for weeks
24-7 you're gonna be stressed too, right?
Yeah, yeah, there's there's been there were some recently some a bunch of people talking badly about them and and it was
Not that great. So
Yeah, yeah, and it's been two live streams with a lot of Apollo tell it
We've just been doing it again and again and again. It was a reply to like you and a half months of shit being said
It's all about the team right about a creator this family of mine
Anything for the Hughes or the godly algorithm?
Well, I mean it's bringing everybody's views up in our honesty
Yeah, that's what drama brings it brings views. I
Know I know obviously
Anyone is talking about conversations, but no one has one and
As soon you start a conversation and you wouldn't get bored it search for another panel to have a
I don't know if that's necessarily true, there are sectors that have conversations and that's all their followers are there for is conversations and their numbers tend to drop when there's drama.
It just depends on the crowd.
Since you have more experience than me, since you have more experience than me, can you point me at one where really people have normal conversations?
I mean, I know of some that have debates.
I know a number of ones that people debate subjects on, but it's not necessarily just
a regular conversations.
But I do know of some that just have, they just hang out like a scum TV.
He usually just has people hanging out.
Harley dad has just hangs out, people just hang out, there's a small handful of them,
there were people just hang out, but I also know of the other ones where people have debates,
so not everything is about drama, although there are a lot of them that focus on drama,
so I mean, there's all sorts of video chats on YouTube.
Excuse me, my ignorance.
What kind of panel do you run, Kazoo?
I don't run panels. I just join them.
I have a channel, but I upload usually commentary videos and such.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, you should follow us I
Wasn't gonna say psyche my bad cuz I'm on psyches channel
You should follow Kazoo because Kazoo does have a lot of good viewpoints
And when he finds itself wrong on viewpoints, he'll even go back and correct itself on that to put you very
platform
Yep, it's a very rare
It's very rare to people people talking a lot about all
Taking a cut of village accountability for what I did blah blah blah
All kinds of bullshit. I only met two or three people on this planet who I say yep
They accepted a mistake and they tried to change it all the others so far. You're all brain diarrhea
Oh, blah, blah, blah, that don't mean I'm going to change.
I tell everybody all the time, I'm a shit talking asshole.
That's taking accountability.
Yep, that's something to be told of behind that accountability, though.
That's something to be told of.
I try to admit when I'm wrong and make corrections, so.
OK.
Yeah, when I when I first realized that I'm wrong about something I usually
Mention it right away and and we'll meet I like I'll make a correction videos and apology videos and such so whoa
Yeah from my experience it needs more strength to accept that you are wrong
Then the other side okay a lot of people to stubborn to childish to say yep, I
Did something wrong and I tried to change it. I tried to not repeat it
But all these people talking about accountability blah, blah, blah
Nothing
They enjoy all this poison. They enjoy all this cancerous cancerous environment. They enjoyed it
That's what I call them drama
Always have to come with an apology. Sometimes accountability can come with acceptance as well, right?
No
Yeah, it's not a one-way street Apollo accountability can be work more agree
But what's the point to say yet? I was wrong and then on the next day you said you do the same shit again. What's the point?
Well accountability doesn't necessarily mean that someone was wrong. There's there's other sides to accountability too, so
Someone could be right in the end. They take accountability for being right. So
or
Actions of how they missed
Took missteps in being right, you know, they did wrong things while being right because you could be wrong and right at the same damn time
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Okay, right. Yeah
I just don't like all these fake people getting, you know, as an example, all these people
on these panels, okay, so far I went, they all say, oh, it's only words, don't get offended
by words, okay, and the same people try about what?
About words.
Don't know about crime. I go kind of like internet Allah Akbar on this shit. I don't mean I don't mean personally you
Just people in general yes, yeah
Say you see I
Had to take so much. I don't even want to start about it. Okay. I had to do to
To take so much shit out from a certain group, okay?
And the same people, as soon as they get a little bit of pushback,
they make a panelist about it and cry and cry and cry for hours.
I have a question
Exile the one so tonight on the show I'm not sure you said that you have some you've seen or heard about some kind of video
Evidence that I just learned tarot. I just picked it up, right?
Okay, so when was supposedly and tell me the details about this where I just learned tarot
Uh, that was years ago and not really learned. I misspoke not really learn tarot
But you was corrected on some things when you visited my wife's channel a few years back
This channel is this I believe that channel of hers is in the rational mystic
Okay, so there's somebody named rational mystic. I don't even know. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm gonna do you a favor
Don't be offended. I am gonna go like you YouTube chat years ago. Okay. Oh god psyche
It wasn't on this platform. This ain't the only platform that you're on or she's on
Hey, I'm gonna do you a favor
I'm going back and I'm clipping it as if you kept listening. I'm going to clip it and I will show you the video
I will show you the video evidence. I will do you better
I seen it on my wife's live when it happened
So when I drop the video is this gonna be the same
It is gonna be your same emotional response when I drop the video psyche
what platform was it on? Because you remember when I told, hey, you remember when I told
J-Dog that I would do that? I can double back with the video on another day.
So I can not scream and yell back and forth, Psyche, but if that's how you want to handle it,
that's very emotionally immature.
Alright, I'm gonna get out of here dear psyche some breathing
Okay
I don't know. I tried to stay out of it. I have my own problems with some people I just I tried to not get involved in this shit
Okay, that's what I'm talking about. Okay. All I was asking him and I
Quietly at first I said tell me when and where and who okay. He's giving me some kind of name
He's okay. I wasn't on some other platform talking to terror readers at any time
You can go and see my Etsy store, okay, my Etsy store from 2020 to 2023, you know, you can see how I was, I'm active, I have over 1800 reading times, okay?
So, I would love to hear his information, because that's slandering, it's more slandering, and he just gives it like it's the fact, and then people believe it, okay?
And this is, that is what's hurtful, it's like when it's like false allegations, and it's not, and also, yeah, if he's not responding to anything, I mean, it's like...
What is, what the fuck did he have to say there, I mean, he's just a fucking asshole, and he's like, oh.
Sorry, your microphone is low, your microphone, sorry, your microphone.
Did you hear, oh, I think so.
Hate slander.
Hi psyche. Hi. Hey, Ryan. How are you sweetie? You hear me now? How are you? I'm I'm okay
a little bit better here, but a little bit better. Yeah, okay. It's better. I'm having near my mouth
Yeah, but that was like that's more slanderous and everyone in the room is like, oh my god
He just oh and it's like something that people believe I've had my business on my tarot business heard enough
My people slandering me and it's like I don't need more allegations and it's like and then he has all I'll find this video
It's a mysterious video
Guys, this is all complete bullshit.
I learned Tarot when I was eight,
just like I told you from the beginning.
And what else is there?
I mean, now he says, okay, I was corrected on something.
Okay, well, I don't think so.
I don't think I've ever been corrected on a show by another.
It's like, I would have to have been on the show
and I don't know what he's talking about.
I would love him to produce the video, produce the video.
No, Amanda, he's not upset because of that.
He's upset because they're talking about how he does Tarot.
Yeah, and all right. Yeah, and he did not have nice things to say to me and or about me and I never did anything to him either
It's like another person that's in just in the hate clip or no reason. I wasn't talking for two and a half months
Troll baiting or whatever. I mean, what the fuck is he talking about? Was I troll baiting him or troll bidding bronze?
But no, I didn't even remember Bronzeberg. He was been gone for months. It's like then all of a sudden he reappears
I might have kicked off a panel or something like that and he's like but heard about it
And so he's decided to like go on a vendetta
Bring on the person that's sending people knocking on my door all day looking for scrap metal sending manure to my house
You know, and they're just like laughing about it like oh, that's fine to do
You know, it's like they don't like them that shit is done to them
They don't like when they're docks and blah blah blah, but they're oh, yeah
I laugh about it when it happens to me right and be happy with you know
If I'm being attacked like that, you know, it's like really frustrating and he
I don't like any of these false allegations.
I don't care if they play a clip of my show
and they don't like how I acted in a clip,
that's one thing, because that's me.
That's, you know, it's like,
you can be interpreted different ways.
I was joking most of those clips
and he's like taking it like it's some kind of serious thing
where I'm trying to, you know,
ask Mason to come on the camera naked,
which was, why would I want to do that?
Because that would be against the TOS
to have someone naked on the camera.
So it was a joke, obviously.
So what?
Yeah, but then so that's fine if they interpret a video clip that way
But he's like making allegations without any proof and just coming up pulling him out of ass
And it's gonna and it's more things that just will hurt my reputation and so
You don't need that. I agree to that one
They try to hit you where you hurt the most, you know
Hit me by attacking me and my cats saying I saying I like I
Killed killed basically eight cats what they're trying to say and something like that
They're like, oh my god, he had 11 cats when I'd have 11 cats when I started this show
I had maybe five or no six and then it's like, you know to have run away since then
I mean, it's like, okay, so I have four now
It's like that. I mean, I have had maybe they're confused when I've said I've had
three litters of cats in the past few years. I've had more than 11 cats. I had a lot more at a
certain point, but not all at the same time. And so I don't know, it's more.
It's like, are you, are you being gangstalked? Like in real life?
Yes, I'm being gangstalked in real life. Yes. This is a pattern. It's, it's, it's,
yes. And then it's, this is part of it. This is just part of it. Tell them brain.
And being as a professional gangstalker, by the way, that is so fucked up.
Yeah, it is it is and it's like that's not cool. It's stressful and
You know, it's not it's like it's just totally painting me like the worst way
But it's okay. They can say anything they want, but if you're Mike your Mike size your Mike you're getting quiet
Yeah, it's just slander. Okay, it's pure slander
And you know, it's like what they played a video where I'm like, you know talking about the two psyches
I mean, it's like if you would watch the show
He might understand the explanation about the story of psyche and cupid which I've named the show up
You don't understand the name psyche awakens, which is not like psyche is a name of a goddess. It's not like a male's name
So there's more to it. It's like it's very
I guess he's not like intelligent enough or to like you know look into it more than just thinking
I'm a hermaphrodite or something like that, which she said thank you for coming on my member Alex
Thank you for getting in the membership. Thank you so much. Appreciate you, bro
Yeah, I'm sorry and I'm sorry I yell but that guy in particular just irritated me tonight by making that allegation and then summer
Pits me off because you know she knows like you know
When she's gonna she's gonna talk shit on another show about me. It's like
She's my fucking mod, you know, it's like and I've always been good to her
I've always been she's mad about Christine or something like that
Christine who they put a picture of a crack pipe in her mouth and her actual picture on Sam Man show and she still goes to that show
And it's not a problem, but Crystal says the one stupid allegation
Nobody believes and she's like acting like I've done something horrible just by talking to Crystal on the show
So hey, Laba, how are you? Hey everybody in the chat? I'm sorry. So anyway
That's that's what I have to say, but I'm I'm right here. I'll you guys talk to but do you see how I'm dressed?
Oh shit, my my my priest callers all out of my
Out of my all coming. I'm done. Oh my gosh, but yeah, I'm wearing my
Priest outfit tonight. I'll show you
Hey guys, oh small deals
Or $25 donation, I will dance in the speedos tonight if you want me to I'm wearing them
So the American flag speed is okay, but I haven't seen any so yet. So yes
$50 if rain dancing of the on pen hey, hey, hey, hey Rapallo be respect you better kill be respectful man
Don't giggle like a girl
Be respectful. Oh my gosh, she's wheezing
Graduated from saying that you know
With fleas to saying that I have bedbugs lice and ticks now. Okay, who said that?
Who runs word and they're and they're all agreeing, you know, no one says hey, you know what? No, it's like you're exaggeration or you know
He loves his cats. I mean, they're just acting like some kind of six animal abuser and I hurt my cats and it's like, I love my cats so much.
She's like, it's like, that's what that's what that's where they're hating where it hurts.
It's like, but it's like, you know what, I don't believe them and it's not true.
It's just like people that will believe that and there's people that are like, Oh my God, you know, it's like, it makes me look like such a monster.
And it's like really a slander is portrayal of it.
So, okay, hold on. Oh my gosh, my freaking my sash is off.
Okay, okay.
Our Father, who art in Heaven.
I long in the Father, speed you, and speed you to Sanctus.
I will be done on Earth, that is in Heaven.
He's gonna perform an exorcism.
Daily bread, until those who trespass against us.
Thine is the Kingdom, and the power, and the glory forever.
You are part of our ritual.
Amen.
Yeah, you're part of a ritual guys.
This is actually-
Can you see what I did to Crystal and Goodtimes?
Oh yeah, you fucking-
I made them fall in love with each other
and they took off the phone going right now.
They deserve each other.
But Crystal, what the fuck are you talking about?
Like Crystal really, it's like,
you just talk a bunch of nonsense.
And it's like, that's what, I mean-
You're family, what did you take?
I want some, hold on.
I think that's the meth talking.
Okay, meth, okay, meth, okay.
Met the mouth. Okay. No, look. No, this is what the symbol is right there. Oh my god. What is that?
Is that kind of symbol is that
Oh
I was wondering I was gonna say I told you a high priest of Saturn if you didn't know. Oh, he's a high priest everybody
He's gonna sacrifice the guy. He's about to show to someone sat on us. He's gonna give the cat as a sacrifice
My babe
Cos you can you read the back check please no
Yeah, I'm I'm working on it. I'm working at it. Oh, okay messy
Sorry the fuck sorry my camera fell
Everything is just falling apart here. Put the green screen on I will put the Vatican in the background
Okay, so I look cool
my actually my uncle was
Gave the pope the gift on his 90 on his
1993 or something which one hope John Paul the second all the good one. Yeah, he's the good one
I'll get the Vatican
Is it going?
I will. What kind do you want Sicilian? Yeah, why not pepperoni? Okay. Got you a pepperoni. Okay, so I got the
better get hold on one second. Okay, and I'm gonna go and I'm gonna put it in my
background. When I was in Italy, we went to a Vesuvius. Oh, the volcano. And yeah, we
had we had that pizza at the base. They had a restaurant at the base of the
Oh, wow, we had some nice pizza there, and I gotta tell you Italian pizza is the shit
Really? Yeah, it was yeah. It was really good. I gotta go there and try it. It was fucking great. I'm like, oh look at me
Okay, I got a pizza. I have the picture. Okay. Here we go
You see if that works. Is it up? Hold on. Oh, you have to put it in the background. Did you see it?
I'll take the green screen off
Yeah, Pompeii
Oh, that's the wrong picture. Oh my god. Oh shit. It's recessa Annie. Oh shit. Hold on. I need the bad
Yeah, I don't know what it's recessa Annie doing there
Where's my bad? You just performed an exorcism on her. That's why I did
There's like a threes company where they have a recessa Annie doll and like he gets caught like making out with it
Yeah, I saw that one. Yeah
This is sick threes company trailer online
It's like a harsh horror movie. Oh, I want to see that one. Let me drop the link for you. It's really fucking sick. Okay
sure
Yeah
Okay, well, I don't know where I saved my Vatican picture or is it save it's on the I see it. Oh
That's what I didn't say. Okay. Oh
Okay, just give me a second guys
Oh shan camps here. Hi shan. Hello shan. Oh, and then like it then you know, but I also I will say thank you
I'm he man though for like, you know, you did say
Do you like the reading I gave you because then there's people saying? Oh, I didn't
So here we go
Okay, I got I got the bad again now
Honestly
You got any more Italy stories, Gotti?
Yeah, but I'm not gonna share them right now. Oh
Why not guys the Apollo's here
All right, I'm an Italian, you know how he is
Apollo did you did you get the links? Oh
That's nice. Look at that that works
message
Go up and do the color so we can see the color cool cool cool. Thank you. Thank you. Yeah
There are some more but those are the ones I could think of off the top of my head so
Yeah, okay, thank you. Thank you. We gotta talk we gotta talk about the Illuminati
Okay, well, I can I'm an expert on that so you tell us tell us about the Illuminati
What do you want to know about it? You could you can talk to well?
There's actually a guy that writes these really good books his name. Oh, what's his name?
He's know he's Italian guy and I can tell you what his name is but he has a he's really cool
He has a channel, but he's half an Italian and so but then it's like if he was a former secret society person
So but he's telling telling a lot of where do they get this stuff?
Well, they they went to Crusaders, right? It was before that night's Templar. Yeah
Yeah, I mean that ties into it too, but there's actually the Illuminati started by
Adam Weishaupt in Germany and stuff like that. But what was the time period?
Let me see, that was like in the 1600s, I mean, the nice Templar were in the 1500s, but let me see, Illuminati and Weishopt.
I think the nice go back even further than the 1500s.
Yeah, yeah, so the Weishopt was in the, okay, that was 1770, 60, founded the Illuminati.
The same year America was founded, that's interesting.
But yeah, that's the official Illuminati.
The official one, yeah, the one everybody knows.
They probably would go way back before the night's simpler.
They did the same thing.
They used to have an initiation where like the like the the initiate
with a kiss the butt of like the high priest or something like that.
Or like, you know, they'd actually kiss the butt.
Like they'd have to.
I don't know.
And then that's kind of like based on some satanic
thing about kissing the Satan's butt.
But then they would like kiss his butt.
And if there'd be a woman down there under under it or something, I don't know.
A lot of freaky shit.
Yeah, very freaky.
They didn't have panels like this to entertain themselves.
So they had to do it other ways.
I know.
And they did and they were all and it's like actually but somebody had all these
Documents in it about how they're spying on everybody blackmailing everybody and then they got the Knights of Templar gotten
The Illuminati got in big trouble with the Knights of Templar got in trouble too. They were bankers, right?
and so like the the jock his name is
the
More on the guy that was the head of the Knights of Templar
He was you know killed on Friday the 13th
Who was that? Charlamagne? No, there's something called the Society of Missy
They were all killed. Who killed them? Wasn't it the King of France that killed them all?
Yes
Yeah, the last the last one there are bankers and he I think he owed some I think he owed some debts and stuff like that
Okay, so job. His name is demole demole. Okay, so demole
And there's also something on the demole society. It's for young premacists. I believe okay, but let me check out the
book I want to tell you about because there's these books about that they're
really good they're really really long they have a lot of information in them
I just need to open my Kindle. There's definitely secret societies out there.
Oh there's a ton especially in Los Angeles I mean it's like so it's like
but they all tie into the gangs and everything and use all their dirty
work it's tight into organized crime but it's it but it goes you know basically
to the top to the eye and the pyramid that's like the one in control of
everything that's not who you might think either. The 300?
Yeah, yeah 300, but there's also the 300 that were part of the the the thebes the the even the
There these basically it was an army of gay couples they had in they had an ancient in three in a grease
It would be about this part and things like that in the one actually
But yeah, the think they're called the they were called the 300 the gay 300 or something like that
Later later kazoo
Bike is him. Are you leaving? Yeah, you bored him. He left. Okay. It's okay. Well, you know, my following is like, you know
Yeah, you can't you can't handle that deep stuff. Yeah
It's like guys a little bit closer. You get it. He bored him. You can't have the deep stuff. You hear that?
It's your fault Cody. Of course, of course, it's my fault
Um, well, yeah
God or the devil but it's pretty much God. I don't believe it doesn't exist
Well, because you say
We all gonna die. I remember your you say we all gonna die two days ago. I didn't hear we are gonna die
So there's gonna be a big event that we die because imagine living forever. That'd be terrible
We'd be sweet if we like out stuck somewhere like we'd be stuck there for eternity. That'd be terrible
But now if we die, we can change I changed
I decided to spare you all for a little more. Thank you God. Well, you know what maybe next week
I don't blame I don't blame God or anybody for like my troubles. You should
You can't blame yourself like yeah, we are in life, but sometimes we are victims of other people
You know, it's like that means there are some things that are like really not our fault because you know
It's especially if we're like being targeted
Especially by groups. Okay, so it's called confessions of an Illuminati and his name is Leo Leon Zegami. Z-A-G-A-M-I
Zegami. Yeah, look into him. He's super interesting
Uh, and he writes really good books and he's uh, yeah, he has also a you channel, but half of it's in italian
You have to find you see did you see angels and demons? That was a fucking great movie. Yeah the tom hanks movie. Yeah, I was yeah
Yeah, I don't know how tom hanks anymore, but that movie was great. I don't like tom hanks or a stupid son
Like I mean, oh my god. Yeah, son sons are moron too. You're gonna son. It's just a nightmare. He's like, oh my god
He's a rapper
Colors. Oh that one. Oh, yeah, that's the other one. There's like an M1. Yeah, it's like, oh my gosh
And he's a bad rapper, too. He wraps in a Jamaican accent. He goes, hey, man, what do I do?
I'd like a clip, but I don't want to play any other
So
Also, do you know about the the the Shroud of Turin as opposed to the Jacques de Molay or it's Da Vinci the first photograph
And that's why it's like yeah, yeah, I don't believe in the Shroud of Turin, but I believe it's old
I mean, it's not old, but it's I don't think it's Jesus. I think it's like
It's too old, but it's it is somebody you say it's too old. It's too young to be young. I mean yeah, it's too young
It's supposed to be I mean it was like supposedly like
Jesus died like 2,000 years ago. It's probably they dated it didn't they dated recently. Um, yeah, but there's
100 because the scientists will sometimes be religious and they want to prove something
So they will be like liars and that thing so because a lot of people don't test it
And there's I heard that you know what was big business back in the day was fake relics
Fake relics exactly. Yeah
They was on the holy grails and all that shit. Yeah piece of the cross and it would just be like yeah piece of the cross exactly
Yep
Piece of somebody's desk or something. I got replicas of the spear. I guess I got a replica of the
Holy Grail
You do is it just yeah, you know John's stuff exactly. Yep
Indiana Jones he like has to pick the Holy Grail and he like there's all these beautiful cups around but there's like one really shitty cup
Can you pick up the shitty cup? That's the one the shitty cup. Yeah
Yep, so
I mean, but that kind of does make sense. It would probably be very old and like, you know, worn out
No, I used to be heavily into the spear destiny stuff. I used to love that shit. Oh, yeah
Well, that Hitler found it, you know, oh man, I love that. I love that whole story anybody who possessed the spear controls the world
Yeah, but it didn't work out too well for him. But well now the Jews have it
Okay, but didn't they bury it in like Ireland or something like that? I heard it's like buried in Ireland
Oh, yeah, there is supposed to be sparing somewhere over there. Yeah under a church. Yeah
And that's interesting. I mean, I am mainly Irish and Scottish and, you know, English, but a little bit of German, Swedish and French, Italian.
Let's keep going.
You're European.
I think it's a million. All of this comes from the movie from Tom Hanks. What's his name?
Yeah, you look like a colonizer.
I'm just pulling your leg a little bit chill.
Oh, and you know this
Remember we're talking to like
you made it to you made it to a gay all-geo
he couldn't stop talking about it, he went to TPP, he loved it
it's like he loved it
last time we made Apollo, we made the God Apollo, but we were going to make Apollo
Apollo?
we made Apollo last night, but not you
we're going to put Apollo up
but yeah, and we had the Greek, he had a Greek accent, oh that was fun though
Did the Alexander like we had the you know the gay cop and like you know I got you know
Oh, yeah, I I reported your channel for that shit. I'm sorry
I got it doesn't get a little gay around here, but guys. I'm a gay guy. Yeah, well listen. Hey
They're like it's not bullshit. They're not like it's not grinder. I'm like
I know it's not fucking grinder. It's it's that we're doing fantasy role play at like three in the morning
Like no one's in you. Yeah, just do that when Alex is okay. That's cool. You and Alex can have fun all you want
I will Alex and I you need a better wrench
Jamie I'm gonna make Jamie a managing mob, but I don't have a managing mods except for Jamie now
I need a better wrench too. Is that all it takes?
No, it's Jamie has the new already Jamie's like the number like the first mod I ever had Jamie's the best Jamie's the best
The Jamie song real quick. This is a Jamie
Jamie handles things properly and fairly
Yeah, she does. Here's the
I think detail electorate's also a very loyal
Oh, yeah, by the way, electric bought me this bracelet
Let's see it
No
My god
Where is it? Oh there it is
Oh, is that- whoa, those are bees, Benoit Bees.
They look cool.
It looks cool, yeah.
Those are Benoit Balls.
Yeah.
Well, I can use it like that, then.
Are you saying they're anal beads or something?
They're not anal beads.
I got it.
I don't like English, but it's kinda like a cookie.
Hello.
You know what this song wants you to do?
Go to Texas Roadhouse.
That's where I wanna go.
Just go my treat.
Yay!
All the bread you can eat.
The vlogger's on.
Oh my gosh.
You just answered my prayers.
Hey, Arbiter.
Whoa!
Look out!
I'd like to serenade my Mexican queen.
Can I?
Yeah, go ahead.
What?
Do it. I like to serenade my my Mexican goddess
Well, come on we're waiting let's just some finish first
You think I offended Amanda when I called her ugly earlier
I don't know why you hate her.
She's such a rotten person, isn't she?
Oh my God.
I don't know what to be between you and Amanda yes she's entitled she's a little bit of Karen
but she don't hurt anyone she's harmless a little bit of a Karen okay but she she
don't try to hurt no one that's the point unlike others who Amanda
Oh, come on, Apollo, don't get me started on that shit, man.
Come on.
Here you go.
Jesus, man.
Don't ruin my night.
Oh, hold on.
She said lay in front of me.
Don't ruin my whole fucking night, all right?
I almost always feel bad, but no, no, no.
Unless she's talking to somebody else,
but no, I think she was talking to.
Hold on, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who, who,
Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapimu, Arapim
I got a pretty good race.
You're having mad at summers, I guess.
How much kilos do you bring back? How much kilo cocaine? I don't bring cocaine. You're weird. Oh
Only bring Mexican snacks
Hmm Mexican snacks. Yummy. Yep. Okay. I'm done with this. Well, that's what the president of USA said
All Mexicans are rapists drug dealers and all these
No, that's a bunch of bullshit. I don't believe that is not it's not even like a conception
Mexicans are like the hottest
I'm attracted to it.
Avocados are the biggest Mexico imports.
I love Mexico.
Mexico is beautiful.
Then you need to go, Apollo.
Yes.
You need to go visit.
He's been ordained money.
He's a priest now.
Can we meet over there?
The color is awful.
Can we meet over there, Ray?
Click your color, man.
Sure.
Meet me in Juarez.
Fuck what would they say back I need to meet me in horrors. I don't know what it is
It's it's a city in Mexico
Yeah, yeah, you've got a gang rape me and then sell body parts of me. I know
You're weird, dude. We don't even do that
We can meet in Acapulco. I meet a sweet, a king's creed, a sweet there, and we meet in Acapulco.
Acapulco.
What is this? The love boat? Acapulco.
That's actually more dangerous.
Oh.
I'm good friends you know who I'm good friends with Apollo
You don't have any friends
My good friend
You'll know this guy
George the Lattice
You know George the Lattice
George the Lattice. Yes. Yes. Good friend of mine
Man
I'm getting a little bit of respect of you man. You have
Knowledge outside of usa
I knew you'd know who that was
Huh, you think I fake it, huh?
Well, I think sometimes you're a good player seriously
I am one too, but I would use different
Methods than me and you know what you're doing. You're good. I created the game. I don't play it
Yeah, maybe maybe but you're good what you're doing. I respect that
Playing all sides
It's not easy. No, it's not
Who said what when they said it how they said it to who they said it
Gotta keep track of all this shit
It's all repetitive
Holy shit, and then we have killed here and say and he said hey
I am part of this drama community for for ten years. Wow. What a badge. What's that?
That's something to we really
Who said that this cell this cell guy till it one or whatever cell two or whatever
So too, who's that?
It's I won it's I won
What's he saying the one with the guy the excite one the guy who was here a few half hour ago
It's I won. Oh
Exile yes exiled. Okay. Hey summer. Sorry, man. It's my accent. It is what it is
Maybe I can't believe I can't believe to say
I am proud of this drama community for about what 10 years what?
What that's something to be proud of I would hide it
Gotti, do you want me to bring you back anything from Mexico? Yeah, pinata
That's it. Yeah, I'll be good with that
No snacks. No, no, no, no, no, I don't need any snacks. Maybe some of that Mexican Coke
Though the real Mexican Coke. Oh
Yeah, I know what you're talking about. Yeah, the sugar cane whatever it is the sugar cane. Yeah, and a hat
I want one of those big giant hats
I'll see what I can find. I like those hats
Maybe maybe
Try to find something Santa Muerte too. Oh
I know you want that even though I got one recently, but yeah, see what you can find
Get one for yourself too
No, I don't need that shit. I'm good. I don't protect you
No, it doesn't it really does
No, it doesn't trust me
I'll rocker soil this pants on camera
I
Patrick New York made himself
God you have a question. Are you really in the wheelchair? Maybe I am. Yeah, why does that make you think less of me?
No, no, God forbid. No, no, no, I spread that story a long time ago
Shankamp says for me to get you some of those Mexican pointy boots. I have to pair
Already. Yeah, I got a pair from India. I got a pair from Greece
You need ones from Mexico. Yeah, get me. Yeah, get me the Mexican ones, too
You visited Greece. Yeah, I've been to Greece
Where?
Mykonos.
Oh, I hate Mykonos.
Yeah, well, hey. It's all I could afford.
It's ex- what? Mykonos is one of the most expensive places in Greece.
Oh, what can I say? It's all I could afford.
Good one.
Yeah.
When I was there, the waiters who were supposed to lead me to a table
So what I
Just picked it for me a tip. I gave her a hundred a euro
Yeah, yeah
Yes, man, it pisses me off here, and it was not enough. It's insane. This is me. I can't believe this story. It's so insane
But that's like 150 bucks us
I think so, yeah, how many people was just you?
No me and my family
You had 20 people she wanted like no only three only three
Three people the eight like ten thousand dollars with the food
So expensive yeah, it's not like it used to be
God is international a good Suflaki would be like what two bucks back in the day now today. It's like fucking 20 bucks
Yes, exactly. I better go to the main end and you have the better dishes a better restaurant anything
But I haven't had a good Suflaki in years shit, what is that?
Suflaki it's like I'm like Peter bread with like a lamb
onions a little bit potatoes and pita oh my god Greek potatoes oh if you haven't
had Greek potatoes in your life what are you doing oh my god fuck I haven't had
those in a while leave the shit fucking Apollo what are you doing man why do
you fucking bring that up come on you have for sure there were a bunch of Greek
restaurants over there you know not not where I am oh
I'm not in Germany. There's hundreds of them around my city around my house. You're honest of them
Lucky man, it's good food
Yeah, Greek food is great Indian food is good really good
Mexican food is the best
Mexicans, okay
It's the best. I can't eat that hot shit
I'm gonna ask my
Maybe I'm gonna meet
I can't take the heat now it ruins the enjoyment of the flavor mild I like it mild
so just a little bit of heat just a mild heat yeah the gringo style
pinchy gringo pinchy gringo
Let me tell you a quick story about what happened to me today. You you you tell me if I was wrong
So I went to the supermarket real quick to grab some stuff I
Parked I parked in an area. That's not close to the
The um, you know where you return the carriage after you're done with it
So I wasn't too close to where where that carriage drop-off was so
After I was done put my stuff in the car. I
Decide to take the carriage to the front of the store
When you say carriage, do you mean like the cart the cart? Yeah, the carriage whatever
So I take the cart to the front of the store and
There was like a like a barrier in the front of the store
So I leave it there
I leave it at the barrier because I didn't want to go back in the fucking store
I'm not gonna fucking take the thing all the way back in the store and drop it off, you know
So I leave it right there in front of the thing
So I start walking back to the car
This fucking asshole he turns around he says this is right before he walks through the door
So he thinks I'm not gonna see him. He turns around. He says
That's close enough. He yells it out, right?
I turn her eyes to his girlfriend like Turner faced and they both walk into the store
I'm like what a piece of shit. What are you talking? What are you fucking opening your mouth for?
Cuz I didn't return the fucking carriage all the way in the store like some fucking nerd. I
Should have left it there in the middle of the fucking street
Right
Right, okay. All right now go ahead. Tell me what I did wrong
No, nothing nothing
Cool, sorry, bro. Why this faggot after bring that up that I had to fucking bring it all the way into the store
I mean, it's their job. Like don't they have like fucking card attendants shit
Yeah, exactly. They do have car attendants, but I wasn't gonna leave it in the middle of the fucking things
So, you know, some other car can hit it. I could have easily done that
But I decided to take it all the way to the front of the store at least
Let's some car attendant come and grab it. But why do this loser? Okay? Okay?
You're boring anyone to death
Boring anyone to death
Listen, Apollo, I'm making a point. I'm making a point that you don't fucking see
This guy, yeah, he felt the need to fucking say something
Like it was a problem for him that I didn't take the cart all the way into the store
It's a small example of how people are on here and the rest of the world
They can't keep their fucking mouth shut about shit. They got a chime in on every fucking thing. You know what I mean?
That's how a man to Erickson is
See see there was a point to the story that's okay
So the moral of story is don't take the card back just leave the shit there
Yeah, they have card attendance for that shit. That's what they pay them for
You're such a badass body I told you
Yeah, I got he got he has aura everywhere he goes
Yeah, we're
Every
You know one thing I made I
See whenever go the other appender and their woman
I see that the paint is dropping, I hear it, it's like a flood.
Yes, all the women dropping the paint, the painties, you know.
I don't know what it is.
It's a gift.
So put your painties on, right?
It's a gift and a curse, Apollo.
What?
Yeah, I know what you're doing, trust me.
I couldn't understand your accent.
Too bad. He said put your face his own way
But I know what you're talking about it's a curse to have that amount of mojo. Yeah, it's not easy
And plus, you know, you know one thing you're on some panels sometimes
And you got all these women creaming for you, and they're not really
You don't really want these women creaming for you. You know what I mean? They're not the type of woman
They're really fucking like pigs
Like you wouldn't you wouldn't even want to look at this type of person in real life. You know what I mean?
This is a look wise you mean look wise look wise. Yes. Some of them are fucking really dogs
Yeah
I've seen horrors Apollo. I've seen horrors that will make you turn like fucking stone cold into dust
It's so bad. I feel your pain
Johnny called you have to train them. We have to train them. We have to train them buddy. We have to train them
You should talk to me. How dare you?
No
the
She refuses. She can't cook. No, she can't. Oh my gosh. She doesn't do it. I
Do what a useless woman. What are you? I do cook Apollo. You know nothing
But God said you can't I
Said she can I said she doesn't as you can okay. Well speak English motherfucker
Sorry, I'm humble sometimes
Yeah, brain is a lot to learn that's only two rooms under in the house. Oh Paul you see that Johnny said you got a sexy voice
I
Johnny in the chat. She said you have a sexy voice. I
Think she fuck
Don't get shy now, bro
No, he's a man leave me alone
Fuck money said shut the fuck up Apollo
Two dollars to get a link everyone
That fake cancer bitch Hannah. I'll give you a fake cancer bitch. I'll give you a link go so long
Money you're learning the game man. You learn to the the wrench game now you learn the
The shut the fuck up game
Yep, you're gonna have a successful payment money keep going. Hey, Gotti. You're learning class. Yo
You know who looks like a skinwalker
Hannah
Yeah
Oh my gosh
A skin walker with BDIs?
Oh, this hand up on the chat. Oh, okay.
Ugh.
Oh, shit. Not these cans of shit again.
We're aura farming right now
Can you hear me side yeah, oh shit, I've been talking this whole time you didn't hear where I said
No, oh fuck I said we're all gonna go as Hannah for Halloween
Oh shit, we're all gonna be ugly pasty-faced cancer bitches for Halloween
With the with the chopped boob did with the chopped boob and everything
Likey did you fall asleep?
Oh shit.
Let's take a shower.
Perfect timing!
Me and Fatboy, you heard?
Ew!
Yo, that was destiny.
That was destiny, Tony.
I like your little train choo-chooing ways, choo-choo.
This guy's so funny.
He goes on all the pounds and pretends to be allies.
It's like, oh, Alex is crazy.
Oh, shut the fuck up, allies.
I'm on a point changer.
I'm all over that ass, Benji.
Tony, chill out.
Yeah, chill out, Tony.
Not my bad, sorry.
Yeah, there you go.
Now you're learning, you understand?
That's how I like it brother. That's how I like it. Thank you. There you go
Now maybe we can get along a little
And Apollo killed the panel as soon as I left it went from 50 to fucking 20
In the panel these boring assholes
What a fucking boring
Okay
We're not
Go ahead bring them up. You think psyche tears about you. You want those numbers in front of her
Oh, you know, we're some boring ass all up here
Psychic is about a sweet talking about
Also, thank you
So we got a fake gangster guy we got a fake Greek
black man god knows where the fuck Apollo we got Tony Baloney in the
building and then who is that over is that rain and we got a fake gas and
way PD want to be bitch you got me I never heard that one before
so you got bitch you better fucking reset I bet you're a fuck you're home
Oh, you got baby
To the joinboard hooker go back to the joinboard. Oh, I'm a hooker
What does that make you you fucking slut American slut?
Well wouldn't be bad at the right
Yeah, American slut
Don't get me started. Okay with American hate
So we got a retorted hooker. I was actually giving some credit for coming back up tonight
Because I he didn't want you around here because you and JT and God you're all like on the chopping block
We're still you know figuring out all you traders or friends
God seems to be a friend a little JT and you and
Are you trying to come back now? Okay? Sounds like a toilet say the word
Oh, I sound like your mother when she gave birth to you son. You
Sound like your mother and probably you how many abortions do you have bitch? How many abortions do you have bitch?
I hundred percent you had abortions
Now i'm gonna hit deep bitch because you don't know who you're fucking with how many abortions did you have you don't know who you're
two three two three how many kids did you kill in the womb okay because you weren't woman enough to be a mom
so you had abortions the fuck up kaboom how many abortions did you have think about all the little kids you killed in your womb
because you weren't ready had an abortion you weirdo yeah right i don't believe it for a second
You probably had five never had any
because you don't talk about
you're weird. I'm just going to look at.
You have some weird
fetishes, dude. Killing kids.
Why crystal did it earlier?
you you ball bitch how many abortions did you have let it out let it out bitch
the truth shall set you free abortion bitch you bought how many abortions did
you have allied master control how many kids did you kill in your fucking stomach
How many times have you been calming your fucking pussy in your back of a car in an alleyway after a ball, and how much calm...
and then you woke up and you were pregnant you were pregnant and you were like oh my god
you were pregnant oh my god and you were like i'm not ready to be a mom but that was a good
fuck wasn't it it was a good fuck but you still were born in a fit so you got some calm putting
you by some loser so loser came and you and you aborted your own child bitch you were aborted your
a fucking human life
that's scary
I bet you wish you had boarded your daughter bitch
this fucking disgusting pig
you're fucking deppy
you're deppy
Alex
yo this bitch fucking
aborted a human life bro
that's scary
Allah Akbar
this motherfucker I just broke a paddle
Oh, I got bored. I just broke all of you. This bitch had 30 abortions.
Your face from fuck, you spoke down and started praying, oh, I look out for her.
Who wants a next? Who wants a next?
What the fuck are you?
Yeah, tell her I first took my dick and bought another kid. You hook up.
Fuck, Mr. Bitch.
Bitch?
This is a girl.
This is a girl, imagine a man wanting to be with this woman, this is not a woman, that's not a female, no female talks like this.
You understand, imagine marrying a girl like I do, like I do all the time.
You're a butch, you're a butch that gets combed in, you're a comb bag.
How much comb do you have in your putty and mouth, bitch?
Oh my God, you have combed.
You you walk and come drifts out of you from 1980, doesn't it you that's so much come you having you you're still dripping that shit out
That's how much come you take you fucking hooker
Weirdo weirdo weirdo you got me. Yo, stop dripping calm from 93 on your sheets
Next time you go to a bone get drunk and get fucked in the ass by a man's like a little bitch, right when you take that cock
You kill the life
That's why
I bet you're a pedo
peat girls girls kill lives because they get drunk check this out girls like it's nothing
like it's nothing right you have a one night stand with some guy at a bar the next day you're
pregnant and you kill your life because your horny ass your horny ass had a horny you you
previously had to get fucked one night now you're gonna kill a human inside of you that's the craziest
okay you decided to get that dick in you now you're gonna throw away a human life because you
were a horny bitch at a bar one that old drunk now you're gonna kill the fucking human life
especially that it's yours it's your kid that i don't what the fuck is up with that my baby
you're gonna kill your own kid because you were horny one night
Don't ask a question
Look, there's a heart beat inside your belly. That's a little kid. That's your that's your child
Right back you heard
What the fuck
Rain wins he crashed the fucking rain wins you're loser Alexander rain wins whoa
Well, you know what I'm gonna give her that one. I'm gonna give her that one
Check this out Alex. Who the fuck is that weirdo talking about abortions and shit? He's in abortions.
Alexander KO in the second round. Winner is Reign.
That fucking extended first round. They didn't even go round.
Alex, I don't feel dude. You got knocked the fuck out.
By a woman.
By a girl.
My god
Being and she had
Eight, what was the number five eight? So I don't even know abortions
Crashing out that I couldn't keep up with it. I'm not gonna lie
Don't steal other people saying I don't money. That's somehow
Our
Hamlet
So what's that? No, it's holler not hobbler
Fucking Apollo dude, you're so tizzy man
Tizzy it's you. It's your fault. You mate. I'm excited about doing this. Why?
Yeah, why'd you do it we need content why you do this buddy?
We was that good I would I feel like that's kind of bad content. We can't talk about normal shit forever goes goes
I don't have to debate, I'm not a debater, I'm not a massive debater, I don't like to debate at all, but I will say though, I think that, that was kind of bad content, everyone was speaking over each other, everyone was yelling, even if, like, trying to put it back from my point of view.
It never happens on a, on a pender.
You gotta spice things up.
It never happened on a pender.
Oh, Billy's backstage.
You guys are all talking, I can't hear you guys, like, we gotta go, like, at least, like.
Billy who?
Billy Hayden Billy Hayden all looking brought his fingers. There he is. Hi Billy Billy's you went to sleep
Go fuck. Hi Billy. Let's go drunk. He's high rain
Hi, look. I'm sorry
Gotti
I go by God up here Billy
You go by God is that short is that short is that short for Gotti? Yeah, you call me God though
He's a genius got he I got he I'm forbidden got he how are you?
Don't make fun of Zanny come on
Zanny does the best voice impression of me out of everybody
So who is this who's this guy? It was just attacking rain this fucking New York guy. That's why come on
What's you very weird midget weirdo? I don't know in weirdo. I guess so holy fuck
He's a meter maid
Think he said I really got you
He didn't say anything
Oh, you just don't like the guy, you know, maybe like I don't know the guy. How how the hell can I like somebody if I don't know
Who the fuck is this guy?
Billy tell him how long you've been leader of the gang
Now I'm gonna open my chat up pretty soon
Bill is the boss around here now. I'm gonna go live. And yes, I do support. I support anybody that's doing this
So I can doesn't matter who you are. You don't care if he's gay
Okay, that's good. That don't bother me
No, cuz I'm not gonna be all
We're all getting along right now
But when you just join like that and I know Alex I have many arguments against him
But what was your argument? What do you feel like he said that you didn't like?
But one I know the same one name one go ahead. Are you talking to me? Yes, sir
Why is he commenting that he doesn't know rain I don't believe rain is ever had an abortion I doubt that very seriously
How do you know because I know rain well enough
She wouldn't she wouldn't do that she got pregnant she wouldn't abort her baby she'd have it
Your opinion's a little bit, but you know, that's a hard
I would make a good mother
Yes, she'll be a good mother. Oh sure. He is. Thank you. Thank you Billy. Welcome rain
I already am three three cats. Yeah, you know God. Yeah, God. I think you'd be a good man, sir
What?
I think you guys would all be good men
I'm I can't be a man. I'm a god
I want to say thank you to Shan Camp. Yep. She helped out that that idiot Lord Vader cause
Lord little prick Vader Vader what the fuck is your problem?
Holy fuck
Why what's he doing now?
Call me pedo and shit. He's here on Wiccans bad
Vader works for Jarrow Wigan. He sucks Jarrow Wigan's ass, and he sucks Jaycee's ass. Oh
shit
Well, there was an opening
Yeah, so many fights going on. I want to say hello. I see my friend Kazumi was up here tonight
No fuck right. I trolled the guy a little bit
I first time I met him JC let him up on on her panel when I was up there
I never met the guy before that's where I met Kazumi was that JC's panel and
Why is it okay for you to troll people and when I do it it's like mean-spirited? I
Can honestly answer that because you have like a more like a deeper voice and like they think that like
Even if they think the other people are serious like they think you're it just comes off as more
When someone do it back to them
Haydn ties he's got he's all about Haydn
I'm his biggest stepping stone out here Gotti
Yeah, so can I can I say something to you and I don't want to like and I'm not trying to like be mean or nothing
You look like mr. Clean if he had hair
No, there's a guy named Remy way back in Fox 46. They started calling clean
Well turn your camera on to you. Why let's see what you look like
He looks like you it's your go ahead
Yeah
I'm gonna make a cup of coffee and I'm gonna smoke this joint that I rolled just a little while
You should see Billy on Christmas. He looks like Santa
Wiggins said I was trying to look like him growing that beard out
Well, I don't sit there and do this all day long
Stroke in that fucking beard like he does
What was there the argument be like if you want to like grow your dick you probably wouldn't circuit all day long
If I put my dick in your mouth when it's tiny will it grow oh my god, Jesus
Well, people love this shit. This is like the number one topic over here
Well, that was a good point
Someone says he's trying to turn all men gay. Is it true? I'm the gayest fucker out here. You heard
I need to leave I need to be scared and psyche. I
Like to say it to stay straight
Actually psychies in his profile pic look at all spit on them before you go
No, that's a bit of a thing.
That's not that's not like in that picture. No, that's not. That's Charlie and Patrick Row in that picture.
I came up here and this this got derailed. I came up here and you guys fucking let me join a right when Alex joined.
But I came up here just I could I had a question so it got derailed as fuck. It's like an hour later
Yeah, sir, sorry I haven't I have a question for you
If you went camping and you woke up the next morning you found an empty bottle of vodka and your asshole hurt really bad
Would you tell anybody?
I got so drunk I fell I fell down
would you tell anybody yes sir I guess I ain't going camping with you I don't
fucking kiss and tell the Navy joke every question and control that's a
Navy joke in 1987
Rain said she was going to Mexico and she was staying for two weeks. Hey T. Y. T. Y. Yeah, if I
If I fart and you smell it, does that make you a fart smeller or a smart feller?
Debatable debatable a T. Y. T. Y. Are you caught or unca?
Please please psyche and this
You know the words are you Jewish or no
No, the juju to go along with you could be
That's like he's Jewish right
Hit him with your rosary beads
Looks like the 1980s fucking Dracula
He looks like the guy from the Thornburg nothing
He's a priest Billy he's a pedophile
I am a reverend. I'm like a small deal
The book is different than a cast start and I'll forgive him father for you know
You were fucking sleeping don't fucking say you want
We all confess our sins then we all stop confessing our sins when you start
Oh my god
I'm sinless
God we got the opposite of the fucking ginger on the panel, but it's the opposite of ginger
I don't even know how to say that to be like oh
Hannah I'm the one who cloned you the other day and was posting at yummy
That layer cat she's not she's about you're fucking out in orbit somewhere is that dumb bitch Billy?
Why do you want to talk to that thing?
Billy she's actually live let's go over there who yummy's live. Yeah, you want to go
She wouldn't go back to come up and was trolling me and then so finally I asked her I said let's go back stage and she fucking ran away
Let's make it whisper sweet nothing into her ear. I wanted to see her cleavage
First thing is I'm a Yankee, okay
I'm an old Navy guy. All right. He's a he's an American sailor
He's a Yankee doodle donkey in the real seamen, huh, sir. Yeah, I'd have you bet over impact quicker than you can fucking say your mother's name
When you troll bro, it's not even funny though
I'm the most talked about
One person left out of six are you really that funny? I am the most clone person out here
That is
Hey God, who's the most clone person out here me
Who's the most dumb dumb oh on the panel you
Wiggins fan club
you. And don't say I have a
question. I have a question for
you, Apollo. Hey, Apollo. Oh,
shit. You you go in the
bathroom. You're an American.
You come out of the bathroom.
You're still an American. What
are you while you're in the
bathroom? You're a PN.
That was good. That was
fucking good.
I'm gonna go make myself some breakfast and then I'm gonna go live. Bless you. All right, Billy. Bye. See you my friends
I'll see you Billy. I'll see everybody later
Hey, this one's for Wigan
Oh
Dude for like two hours now and I fucking it's like what what's your what's your question ghost?
Please
I was in the middle of a very important question
What show was it? I'm biting my knees. I'm biting my legs. I can't wait. Someone said dumb dumb
I was just gonna ask for it. It's like I'll do not I'll just oh god
What did you want to ask us just ask it? All right?
D. Y. D. Y. Before I go. I got
What D. Y. Which the difference between northern women and southern women?
Don't know northern women say you can southern women say y'all can
You better don't don't stop me.
You are such a horrible comedian.
Hey, Palo, this is America.
You don't matter here.
You know that, right?
Are you guys an art American?
You don't matter in America.
I know, right?
Oh, OK.
Dude, I came over here two years. Oh my god. You realize I'm gonna sleep
$20 bills are gold if you're in Europe
Yes, yes
The most prized possession in Europe if you're European
Yeah, you know hard cold cat
Standard is the American dollar you guys keep that in mind and oh, yeah, okay
I
What a sweaty priest
Judas Priest under the collar
Have any of you guys seen God or Apollo
Rain even have you guys seen blade to the movie?
Oh God here we go
I saw the first blade. I saw a sling blade. Yes. Hi. Hi. How are you?
Yes, me. Hi, Erin. Hey
Hey
You are the opposite of the Irish goodbye you said I know he's one of those
Hi, Gotti. Hi, Rainey. I mean, Aaron, Aaron.
I ran.
He just called you on rain.
I was thinking of rain. Sorry.
Oh, okay.
Psyche?
I can get you out of my head.
God just had a brain fart.
He did.
Psyche, kick him.
Please kick him.
Hi Jamie
Now I don't want to leave Aaron's up kick him. I gotta go eat breakfast. I'm hungry
Don't worry if vader befriend you no big fucking deal
If she comes to my chat he wasn't gonna be
All right
Later billy
I got one last joke before I go
Hey, so like you ever wonder how god made Italians
How did how did God make Italians?
How does he have to do it God took a polish it one hand a polish it the other hand went what?
I have teeth Wigan does it
When were you ordained? Was it tonight? No, actually, I was I've been our day minister back from 1997
Wow, I had no idea
All right, bye guys
Hey, God, may all your women have tits like watermelons.
God damn, you're the longest, the bleeding.
Bye, bye.
Holy crap.
Bye, monkey.
He's just very patriotic, psyche.
Jesus Christ.
Can I say the word?
Can I say the R word on this stream?
No.
Say it.
I think he's a very dumb, dumb.
I think it's just dumb, dumb.
Oh, yeah.
I think you know what I'm kind of sensitive now. Do you want to say like please stay?
Like don't go please don't go
Hey ghost, what was your question?
Oh, it was stupid. It was uh, you were going to Mexico for two weeks
So I was like, can you stay there and it was supposed to be funny, but then oh, I would love to stay there
I'm getting I would love to stay there. I'm getting my my Mexican citizenship as well
Can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come in, can I come
Who who you it's you dude. It's your picture me
Oh, I was cool. Wait me. I was looking at something
Yeah, like a blow-up doll
Oh, okay. Yeah, he's okay. All he heard was gonna be in good faith tonight and I was really excited
But he was crashing the fuck out
What oh the McQueen. Oh
Yeah, it's what he does
God never crashes out. I've got well at least I've never heard it. I try not to you know
Yeah
Are you okay Alexander?
You know what? So I can say something kind of uh, you're kind of rude
Hey ghost you want to get kicked up the show?
Okay, you don't have to yes
Bring me back some nescan candy
Yeah, I will Mexican
Is that a churro, oh, there's like salt churros but no the Mexican candies are so much better
Yeah, I don't like the spicy with chili ones. I'm like the chili candies. It's like literally I I love the chili ones
Be like oh my god, there's a brat in the room in mice in the room again again the cat are catching mice
Did you have like
But um don't worry ghosts you won't have to worry about me anymore because I'm I'm going to Mexico to live there soon
I'm gonna miss you
What do you mean, I'm still gonna be around
No, fuck never mind
I'll just be in Mexico like I'll be up on panel, but I'll just be in Mexico
My question was is like you couldn't join YouTube anymore, and you have to stay there
They have YouTube in Mexico like it's not some third-world country
Mexico oh my gosh
What's wrong
Hello, why are you crying?
Who's crying you what what's wrong?
Yeah, you have like a melon head what the fuck happened. Yeah, you buddy listen. He's there's really smart
That is a lot of brains in there. I'm derpy
Paul you need to learn our speaking English
I try
We go at least he's trying
Go get some coffee
Wait, you didn't ask me what anything what you did God you made cycling might because of this picture
I know
What did you did was that sent here do you screenshot that shit this one?
That's your boy. That's your boy mr. Papas
Papas
Let's put wait what?
You some gay dude from New York
No, dude, that's not me
I like your voice Apollo. Just in downtime. Stop kidding me. No, you don't. I'm not kidding you. Yes. I know my voice is strange for you Americans, but that's okay. I'm not gonna have to do it. You'll see Rudolph the red nose reindeer just like this.
I like it. Now she's gonna say it's cute. There's an Aaron in chat
Nobody can understand what the fuck you're saying especially when people talk over each other
Nobody can understand. That's true. I apologize. I'm sorry. Go ahead. No, not you I'm talking about
Where are you from
Shelf I'm not a shelf born in Greece
And I'm living in Germany at the moment he's in Düsseldorf, but not for long
But you from Greece, that's awesome. Yep. Where are you Dunkirk?
Who's Dunkirk?
Living Dunkirk. Oh, yeah, please not really
You know, you know, you're not you know, you know Düsseldorf in Germany got it. Yeah, Düsseldorf. Yes
Yeah, near Düsseldorf and Cologne. Oh Cologne's very nice
Yep, well red light district here
Hey Apollo, what does do Haas to mean?
Do Haas
Yeah, oh, yeah, the Ramstein song you mean. Yeah. Yeah, they say it all the time like what does it mean?
You have you have
Yeah
There's a deeper meaning, you know, if you listen to the whole real
lyrics
The Ramstein song is really really good deep. It's about a a young girl who got raped
You know, I know I know I know that was the our word was her name crystal you did say it but we're
How many languages do you speak sir hey who gotty
You don't speak eight fucking languages. You got he's international. He can speak a lot of language
I
I thought that is too funny. He says sir and then proceeds to insult him
You know good sirs used to have like, you know duels
We still call each other sir. If you guys would do I would like to see it. Please. Please do it live. Okay?
What are you talking about now? I can't call him sir and still respect him
Stop talking about the little stupid shit. I had a question for him
You know what I'm not gonna come sir now. Hey dum-dum
I want to keep you in your white night for her and she fucking ruined it
I'm so sorry. I will not be white-knighted. How dare you people white night for who?
I'm assuming me
No, I only want that for goodie. That's all
As you shut down
Right
It's it's it's it's it's it's
it's it's it's it's it's it's
Yeah, all right. Get me one of those glaze ones too fuck it. All right
I'll feed that Aaron one
Oh ghost is this chop liver over you
What's your name the the the woman but just showing what's your name get him a crawler
Okay
Where are you from?
I'm from the United States
Can I guess what state?
Yeah
Can I can you give me north? Can you give me where north south?
No, you said you were gonna guess
No, no hands you didn't ask for any hands you said you were gonna guess
Alabama
There you go
Really
Yes
But can you give me some can you get me so I can actually go we told my Obama?
It's door stuff East West
You just said fuck it. Goddamn, how many directions are there?
Four. Pick one.
Come on, you can tell by my voice.
I don't know if you're not going to sing, I'm going to leave.
I know where she's from.
Are you close to New York at all? That direction?
The streets? The streets?
the streets of New York.
Whoa.
That's great.
She knows.
Gotti knows.
Aaron, do you know any songs?
Do you guys actually know where she's from?
Yeah, we were friends for a long time.
Okay, Gotti, is it?
Can you give me a direction so I can actually guess?
It's pretty cold there.
She's from Alaska.
Yes, that's us. She's from Alaska
No, she's from Texas
She's from Alaska
Yes
Me. How me? How are you from Ukraine?
Nika, but my caribati number you got it son. These oh
I just said Alaska
Can you hear me?
Come on, you want a camera.
You should be worried about a wolf or a...
Shishi.
What does that mean?
Thank you.
No, he needs to speak Greek.
Good.
Hello.
What?
I don't understand.
Yeah, it's my Japanese
You could say anything though, and I'd be going, uh-huh
Oh that narrowed it down
Now you know where I'm from Ty
Well, I tell you what I'm trying to
Call where you were and maybe it might be call me anytime
If you're lucky she'll read you green eggs and ham and I'll tell you what if you can read two books
I'd be surprised and I might fall in love if you're lucky
Someone say everyone is a good singer. Is it true? Everyone is a good singer. Oh, yeah
Brother it's USA. Yeah, she can you give us can you give us can you give us an example erin?
Yeah, fucking Aaron give some example. I agree
An example of where I'm from?
No! No!
Oh singing!
Yes?
There you go.
Hello!
That sounds good, right?
Is it me or is it no?
Hello, darling.
He said hello, darling.
You're all I ever wanted. Oh my god. Who's killing? Who's killing a cat? Who's killing a cat?
Who's skinning a cat?
Who asked your question Alexander? Mio?
God, he stopped farting.
Alright, I'm going to leave.
Why? I got green eggs in him.
I can't stop farting, that's why.
Did you have Mexican food?
Do you want me to stay?
It's a fucking accident!
you don't mind
in some countries farting is a matter of expression of respect
show some respect rain
you're always eating that broccoli
you're always eating that broccoli bro
we all should stop farting and show respect of each other
I love broccoli
I do
put a little apple cider vinegar on it, it goes down nice.
Oh, no.
You just got to brush the line on that one.
What's the wrong with that?
That is disgusting.
How about a little bit of cheese?
That's weird as fuck.
Cheese is okay, but I like the apple cider vinegar.
Yeah, I'm a weird guy.
You should see what I said to my corn.
You sound like a weird guy.
I don't even want to know what you do to the to the corn. I want to tell you shout out name this panel keep these bitches in Mexico
Goddy
Aaron
Yeah, we're all gonna take a
That but I take a bus
If I'm gonna go to Mexico. Yes, but the fuck we're gonna vacation in Mexico
Thank God, and you're not invited and it's coming to me
Yeah, you're not invited. Oh my god, fuck it. No, who's gaslighting me? I
Don't know
Must be you
It must be me. Yeah, it's because you're gassy, bro. Where'd you get that picture from? I
Like vinegar. I changed my mind. Yes, you made it. Yeah with AI
Yeah, oh nice. I like it. Thank you
Is it based on you or did you just pull it out of something else?
Did you make it or did the AI make it?
AI made it, yes.
But they use you as a template?
But they use me as what I told them.
Oh, okay.
You didn't put your picture in, okay.
No.
But you know what God is saying a lot of a lot of the women on these planets are very ugly very
It's okay
He has all the nasty ones yeah
All the pictures of the nasty people
He's like the archives
Let me answer the phone
Okay, that sounded extremely cool cheesy balls and broccoli says giddies gay
I've never heard a good
Beware good, isn't it horrible when you try to insult somebody spell it wrong
Did right now
You can't come back from that era.
God, do you know what I think is in the Bible, correct?
About who?
Abe.
Abraham?
Yeah, I know Abraham.
I think that's him.
Abraham Lincoln?
He was a brother to Moses.
I don't think he's in the Bible, but you know, I don't know.
Oh, I thought you were talking about the fucking founding
fathers and shit.
What do you want to know about it?
You think that was a founding father?
Yeah, I thought you were talking about that.
Watch this it's not gonna go over to or watch this
What by the way on your picture I just have to ask oh
Wow, my picture jammy took care of a good job, Jamie
I'm talking to God. I got it. Whatever fucking name is. I don't know. You know, what are you saying?
She looks like a dog. She's a black dog
That's it she that's just showing her picture to you
That's a beautiful fucking dog
Yeah, she's a black dog
Looks like a protector too
He is he'd whip anybody's ass
You know
No, he's a pit and
Melanua
And you know what I love about that picture
Nothing
You have to love my puppy
Okay, I want to know that picture on here. I want to know why you don't smile. I
Don't like people
That's a good reason
Well, just because you don't like people doesn't mean you don't necessarily need to like smile
Because you just like I'm happy with life
Yes
Yeah, but I really really don't like people
You're you you
That one's better than the last one I like very few people I should say
That's all right. I'll give you that one
Do you like me?
And do you like you you call me ma'am
Alex is mad because he's not cool enough to be up here with us
He's mad because he ran out of cocaine. It's I mean it happens. I mean, I'm sorry
You should have fucking don't get high on your own supply all those
Fuck is that a rat
I think so, I can hear you
That wasn't me
No Alexander's in the side chat losing his shit over abortion who reads that stuff
Like he wished he was aborted
This is the name of the people that read stuff that Alex writes dumb dumb
Well, I don't want to bring that up actually never mind. I'll let that go
Later, don't be mean
Are we on a double day now
Yes, yeah
I want the daughter of the dj if you don't mind
The daughter of the dj
It went it went. Oh my god. He did not. Oh
He did and you laughed
You belong to him now, okay, I'll know I'm dating rain. Nope
Got you out of y'all take both of them on a date. All right, see ya
You're such an asshole guy. Why now he's back. Why did he why did he leave?
Ty said that he was gonna take both of us on a date. Oh, hell no
Get your ass back up here silly
What who's to was that you Billy I thought you're eating breakfast
I have a question for you. Are you reading your own chat? Are you reading this YouTube chat?
The YouTube chat. Oh
That cheesy was you Billy
The cheesy broccoli, right?
Yeah, that's what Billy said his cheesy
Broccoli
Homeboy brought up the fucking vinegar or yeah vinegar on him
Yeah, I'm broccoli. I'm sorry that is
I mean, I can understand the fish because like one like, you know, like fish places, but you put on broccoli brother.
You know, it might be amazing.
It might be really good.
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm saying.
I have no idea.
I like broccoli, so.
I don't think there's a whole lot, but
I like steamed broccoli. I like cooked broccoli. I like fried broccoli
Red wine vinegar and did he actually fucking leave the real he put the link in the yeah, so I don't know if
The psyche's still around
You probably fell asleep. I'm not sure
Oh god
Does somebody say take me with you
Ma'am sir
Ma'am
Cutie you were talking about a duel
Well listen, I think I think well, what was did you actually want to talk about that?
the dual
Yeah, I think there was such a thing if you do you I don't know if you guys know about it. There was such a thing
And doles yes, there were yes. Yeah, they're telling someone you got there and fucking
That's when we we didn't have like the
We only had like a muzzle on it
So like we could only fire one bullet unless you're set there and reload for fucking
I don't know how long it took you but like yeah, that that was such a bad
It was yes
Yeah, I was there and they didn't know what I said was
One right
That was like I told you yes, I know this because I was there
Now nowadays we can like verbally do it. Uh, okay. Oh, that's fun. Oh, you call him pookie
No, I was reading what Vader said
No, I was reading what Vader said in the side chat
Okay, we can all talk but you know I'm not really but we got free shoots now and now we can all talk
Have debates and stuff. I'm really into duals. So
And where did you two go up from because I've been on sites for a while. I've never met you guys
Maybe I mean, I don't think we've ever met. I don't think we have no
I've only been here a couple times when psyche was actually
Oh, okay. Yeah, that makes sense. Yeah. Yeah, I mean, you care of reading cards. I mean, that's sore
Thing what about you?
I don't want to be disrespectful ma'am
You can call me rain
I see a tree frog. You can you can call me rain
Oh, rain. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Um, how'd you find that channel as I like was it like tarot card readings or just like drawing an open panel like he, um, I just typed in like live and he was one of the first he was the first one to pop up.
Okay.
Go eat your breakfast. I'll tell you who's spamming and this in this shot right now is Alex
He's fucking crashing out. He's still crashing out. It's been like three hours, dude
Like get some rest brother. Oh
You guys haven't met Billy
I
Mean that name kind of as somebody's named Billy. We know they're going home
You know, he's the the guy that was just up here. Um, you know, the old guy
Why is he here he had his own thing to do
Yeah, that's really supposed to be eating breakfast Billy. Oh
No, you got to go over to
What's your name? What is your name?
Rain, what's your name?
Who's name
Slayer, what's her actual name you me?
Yes, you meet there we go
That's what I said
Never happened
Are you going to go Patrick? Are you know this for sure? Oh
That's why God he left okay
Yeah
I apologize girls if I'm wrong like I am I do yeah, he likes her more than he likes us Aaron
I know I didn't do tonight. I didn't do tonight, but I do like to debate a lot
And I didn't do it tonight really at all like maybe like once but
So I apologize if I came off like rubbing you guys wrong
No, that's fine. I just got here
Debates I love all that stuff like that's what I get into
That's good mean you're smart. Well, okay, that's not necessarily true some really really dumb people can debate
Well, I mean, maybe about a certain topic.
I mean, I'd have to agree, maybe.
You have to be, you, well...
Well, no, if it's something that you're passionate about,
that you know a lot about, then yeah, you can debate.
But if it's just to, like...
Well, Alex...
I'm sorry, go ahead.
Yeah, no, I interrupted you.
You go ahead, my bad.
I'm trying to figure out...
Alexander I don't understand why he's so angry
It's all the coke he does I
Said check the score and I always say that to him because I've won so much
I don't know what the score is. I just say it to trigger him to get him
But I did trigger him today, but he fucking I've never seen him like crash out this like for so long
I've seen him crash out, but not for this long like goddamn five hours later, brother. Oh
Uh, it's because he's tweaking. He's just mad at the world. He's tweaking hard right now. Oh, okay
Well, stop being mad at the world. Oh
Alex is mad cuz his mother didn't swallow him up here. I don't know if we can because but do you guys know someone?
Yeah, I know somewhere. Okay. Yeah, I should be really cool up here. Yes, you would. Yeah, I agree.
I don't think she wants to join though
You don't think so away I don't think she wants to join I
Think she should I think she should I don't know if she wants to go
Who has a managing mod
Um psyche said he was gonna give Jamie a managing mod Jamie are you managing my
Yes, no
Yeah
Green said that that's what psyche was gonna do
Jamie is there you go
And you should have summer come up cuz right if you have a managing mod you can let people up on the panel
Don't know if it works like that. I was told it does but I'm not sure. I don't know nobody trusts me enough to make me a managing mom
Man you really are losing your shit Alexander
Well, so now I would trust you enough. I don't think that I don't want to be rude here. I really don't be rude
Like you're not smart enough because obviously you are but you're definitely nice enough and you're not like
Like you wouldn't be like a mean unless you have to be inside my view. No, that's very true. I'm like that too
I'm not mean in this. I absolutely have to be
I don't like YouTube. I don't like uh, I love free speech and I love rumble and all that
I don't I have to be really careful what I say, but um
You know YouTube is like crazy nowadays, right? You know with the to us
Yeah
I can be real nice, but I can also be a savage.
If need be
Like I would got you but he really didn't get you like he was roast you saw me you just you saw me drag him by the fucking hair
Well, you were in a dumpster
But he's just louder
Overtalks you like you're not winning when you're when you're louder and we're talk
I don't give a shit if he's loud or not like I'll still fuck him up
The thing about is we can't hear you when you talk though
Okay, but what he was fighting with you. Yeah, earlier. He was picking a fight with me gaudy everybody on the panel basically
I let him have it
Yeah, but we didn't hear you because I was just something they're yelling
I mean, that's my I don't know about everyone else a comment in chat, but in my headphones
I could only hear him. He was just yelling yelling. I could hear you. I couldn't make out what you're saying though
That's just yelling and just being like noxious
That's not cool Alexander
Be abortion crew you came out just fine
He did say and I
He did say that she
Had
Seven was it seven? I don't know what the number. Thanks summer. You're amazing, too
I don't want to bring it back up to be honest with you. I'm not like that. Oh, wow. Now we have all day, but I'm not going to bring that back up.
Oh, that's okay. If you want to talk about, you said she was ripping something and she had seven abortions and I think even like, I'm giving him a favor here by saying that because I think he went more with it.
Later, Gotti.
Oh, bye, Gotti.
Don't be mean to Summer either. What is wrong with you? Oh, yes, I finally been called a hooker.
Missed zero little froggy
You always call me a hooker
You what I miss you
Like two years ago if like you two girls over on here. Oh psyche. Whoa. No, sorry. Oh
Later
Like you imagine we started this but you started this panel with these two girls
I mean dude it wouldn't have been like
Yeah
Can I ask you a question did you just sleep or did you eat I'm doing something I'm actually
Hey summer I was surprised for you to open it might take a little bit, but I'm almost I was surprised for you if you really got
if you
Does someone want to join tonight or no?
Okay
You said you have a question for me psyche. Yeah, are you time?
Here you see my wife. Are you THY me or no, you're not time. No, she's not time. I'm not time. Okay
I have a question for Aaron. If if you guys don't mind, like, did it hurt at all?
When I fell from heaven? Oh my gosh, that line.
It's the corniest line ever. Okay, I will give you that one.
Debatable. That is the corniest line ever.
Can I get five seconds to think about it? Absolutely not you had your five
I'm sure Aaron's heard them all
Good, how are you? I'm doing good wondering why ghost is talking about my 20 abortions
That was not that was not me.
That was not me.
I took a picture at the Borscht
Clinic of one of them.
We're going to try it out.
Summer.
Come on.
It's a chicken nugget.
It's literally a chicken nugget.
You know what a nugget means?
A nugget means like somebody that
has their arms and legs cut off.
Really?
I never knew that. That's funny.
Well, yeah, if she's had 20 abortions, of course, she's an abortion queen.
That's right.
Well, you know, there's a closing here and stuff, you know.
Let me talk to Summer for a second.
Summer, I was under a lot of stress today because not only was that show on but, um,
You know I had a people looking for scrap metal all day at my house and banging on my metal door because they were told
Just to bang really loud until I answered that I wasn't answer
Scrap metal is like just extra like the metal from like you know cars and like that
Like that. It's like all cut up and stuff and people can come pick it up and like oh
Yeah, so someone though if there's an ad apparently we're eating at scrap metal from
But, you know, I know who did it too because he said last night, he's like, oh, he's going to get doorknob tomorrow.
And I know it's like, you know, maybe Alex, like, you know, antagonized him a little bit.
But I didn't, I really didn't.
Yeah, Alex is not making her situation better this way.
I know he's not.
Neither is.
He's not set on purpose.
Yeah, but, well, that'd be, if he's doing that, then it's like, you know, he's in trouble.
But I just, I don't think, I just think he's a loudmouth, but.
But that's you know, that's it. Yeah, well, we've known site we've known Alex a lot longer than you have psyche
I know but you still are good with Alex. Aren't you? Are you like friends of them? No, me and Alex are big good in a while
Okay, well
Well, it's like
Cordial to each other from time to time but not especially when he's all fucking cooked up like now
And I see what he's doing and nothing I've said that I wouldn't said and haven't said to you
I know what Alex is doing and I keep telling you that and you did you know
So I can't keep telling you you got it. I mean he's came up here and told you that he sent pizzas a shit to your house
Well, I don't I don't know. Well, yeah, I mean he might have I think it's like they send pizzas under his name all the time
And it's like that's what happened last time too. They said they said pizza. He said he did it
Okay. Well, you might have been just taking taking a you know, it's like, you know, just taking credit for I don't know
But I just don't have proof of that, but that wasn't
Whoever's petting you in that moment you put your eggs in and you can't do that because the people manipulate you
I might be an asshole, but I'm not manipulating you
I'd say it'd be worth
Well, I don't know. I'm just like it's like getting called by some of those people
It's so it's like oh look at these just full of lice and fleas and ticks and you cover shit
It's just like there's all this like really disgusting graphic language about it like that's very untrue
And it's like it's like this is it's just like it's like so nasty
But that's being said and all like that's just well as far as far as the panel goes like psyche
I will say this
For at least two months, dude. You poked and you brought it and everything. Okay, and you can say you
Every person that's on that panel
I haven't talked to those people most of them. It's like all those people. I've kicked off the panel you play
Whatever LES said he was only honest one. Oh, man, cuz he put me back
No, she's talking about Vita, bro. That's the only person she has
Summer I'm sorry, but you know, you don't know what you just done discussion later because I don't want to do it right now
Okay, it's not gonna be it's gonna be it's gonna
If you if you could shut ghost up then we could talk okay, I'll think oh yeah
Okay, go ahead so so there's been plenty of times that
For instance, Christine came to you and said, psyche, please stop showing that clip. It bothers me. It upsets me. She's not upset with the point that you miss with that situation. She's not upset about what crystal said. She's upset about somebody that she supported in her front. Her friend finds it gets a smirk on a space every time he plays it. And it bothers her.
You and B to have your own history. I'm not gonna get in that
So you've played a part in this too. It's not like everybody's just attacking you to attack you psych
Summer okay, so we're bronze. These are all people that supported you for a long time
Bronzeberg disappeared for months. Okay, literally months and then he reappeared and it's like I don't know if like
It was like this almost the same thing with elbow too. It's like they just reappeared and then it's like
Then they started being like really bad on the panel and I kicked them off the panel
And then they started to go badmouthing me on beatas and everyone goes to be this and badmouth me or whatever
When you work people's villains, they're gonna badmout one side
They're in my feelings, you know, it's like and they're talking a lot more
That's why you make videos of them and songs of them and and you play clips of it
One of bronze bird I mean yesterday after that first panel and stuff like that and so I mean that's like a whole thing but
That was after he like screamed over me. I'm beat is calling me the worst names
I'm beat is twice in a row and it's like she had like four or five people at a time screaming over me
My point of being all of this is every single person has a part to play and you as well. Yeah, I understand but it's like
Broke I would say and then he's like, oh, oh you said broke
And now he keeps repeating that.
That's the worst thing he can say that I said about him, right?
And it's not, I didn't mean to say that.
All the things that are happening to you online,
that's the one thing that bothers you.
You've got Alex up here doxen the person that is putting you through hell and hot waters and and threatening them
You think that's not gonna become back on you. You think these trolls hang on each other's ass a lot
Shit Alex is doing and you're worried about what?
Go shut the fuck up. I'm not fucking talking to you
Why are you yelling?
Cuz we're having a fucking conversation and we asked you to shut the fuck up
Okay, yeah, sorry to interrupt. No, no, no, no, no, I got to go and take the puppy out
But I have a good night, but if all you can summer
So I can eat you like this. You have a good night rain
later Aaron
Ghost it was really nice meeting you
Let us talk
That's a fucking problem people want to get in everything and not let two people fucking talk shut the fuck up
Stop gaslighting him
You can't say shit. Hey, psyche if you want to talk to me then we could talk but I'm not doing this with him up here
Cuz it's fucking ridiculous
My point I'm making is everybody has put a play put a play and stuff
When they got their feelings hurt you got their fill into everybody and when I get aggravated
But there's nothing I haven't said that I haven't said to write on this fucking panel to you
over and over again
Right, but okay, okay, and then you want you expect that your mods are supposed to go and fight all your battles
Why they're not even in your chat. I don't expect that
But cuz that's not cuz I'm friends with I've been I've been friends with all of those people and I'm friends with you
So I don't need to get in it. I know but it's like if you're friends with me then why are you sitting on?
But I've been friends with them longer
Okay, but I mean, okay, so I don't say nothing so I leave I stay out of it
I didn't I said something tonight because you irritated me because you kept trying to praise Alex like he's some fucking God
We like oh well summer's fine, but she just sat there of course
I just sat there because I got friends that are all argue with each other
Yeah, I don't have to get in that in the middle of that. It's not a stranger attacking you. It's friends and supporters
They're not they're not my friends. Those people on the panel are not they were they were for a long time
Thank you. You mean like that. Like if that's like that's well, you treated them like that though, too
Allied up there. That's they're not ridiculous. I mean, that's my mortal enemy, right? And it's like, okay
He's the character expert on me, right? Okay. So anyway, summer. I don't want to argue
But you think the things Alex is doing is not gonna get you in shit
That's but it always goes back to something like something it's like we can go tip or tat and like about like okay
But it is her tip or tat either all of you all stop and leave and it just leave it alone
People actually just not making a I music. I don't know how many times they begged you beat up for sure
Asked you a billion times well summer summer
Just that that's all I'm saying just try you want him to leave you alone. Don't sit don't fuck with him
Don't do it a song. Don't do it
Don't don't mean if you think I'm poking at you. I mean, it's like, how would you see that unless I was like yours?
They're like at my show like listening. I mean, but she has friends here
This isn't just about you psyche you created a community and so people are gonna come whether they talk to you or not
They're gonna still watch people are gossiping. They were trying to cause conflicts or they're exaggerating things. They're said and those
Don't want to take any accountability and that's fine. I think everybody on the part in the pot. You don't think so. It's cool
Tag people the whole thing with the biscuit was was a was a reply to it and you can see you talk shit psyche
Well because I'm in response to things but not like that like that not like that not like that that's in the last night
Maybe I am in response to Bronzeberg, but it's like the even the AI songs were just very very tame and like nothing
It's like so ridiculous
Wait, but see this is the thing when you play for to tip for tech
You don't get to choose how the other team tax when you take oh by the way
So I didn't make some new song about Christine and you I played
I have old songs where she's in there, and it's like, oh, it's like Christine and Fawzi. It's not like, whoa, whoa, whoa
I'm so sorry Christine. Plus, Sam-Man has Christine with the crack pipe in her mouth and her full picture on his show
She still goes over there. She doesn't even care. Okay, but she cares so much because Sam-Man didn't put it up there
Say it was somebody trolled it did that they paid for that. That's part of it
No, that's not that's not part of the show that everybody knows that
Okay, well anyway, it's like she's all I'm saying is again all of this but of course you're still like no
I've done nothing. So I mean really
It's just gonna keep going in a loop and I've told all you I don't want to see that
Okay, I think that very clear. You would have said that if you would have said that
I don't need to say anything when I say a hundred times. So all you are I don't want to see you all fighting
Well, they didn't help me.
So no, just like you sit on this panel,
the night before Alex said he was going to shove
his dick in my mouth, and you sat there and said nothing.
I don't even remember that summer, buddy.
Of course you don't, because, see, I don't drink,
so I'm going to start drinking so I can tell everybody
I don't remember, because I was drunk.
I'm not drinking summer.
I mean, I haven't even had a drink tonight.
Well, then why?
Well, then I don't remember, because I'm stoned,
because you were sitting right here on this panel.
I'm about to start drinking right now.
It's convenient for you to always not remember.
Okay, whether you were drunk, stoned, not paying attention, it happens multiple times.
Okay, well, I don't remember that because Alex always talks like that and you had a
relationship with Alex where you can't talk like that.
And I haven't had a relationship in a long time.
Let's move on from that. Okay, I just want to show you something and I want to see if you
like it, but okay. And it's like, if you don't, I will fix it. So you're not on it. But I think
you will like it. But if you don't, it's okay because this is what, but this is like
Really what I had I was like trying to do like a nice surprise and so it doesn't work. It's fine, but if you don't like it
It's fine, but I want to show you
Okay, it's not what's not playing something. It's uh, I have to be pulling it up. Okay. Hold on a second. Okay. Here we go
See if I can find it. Okay
Okay. Oh, okay. Well, I'll take me a second to find. Okay. Is it?
Can I say something like it takes you a second to find, or are you going to quit?
Go ahead, ghost.
Yeah, I just had a question for Summer, which she knows how over. I have no problem with her.
Summer.
Is your problem with us like is because
It's because like the AI videos. Is that the problem? No, I don't have it. See this is the part you're missing
The reason why he's upset with me is because I'm not go
I'm not getting in between it. I still hang out with psyche still love psyche to death
Yeah, I'll tell psyche when I when I have an issue with psyche me and psyche go edit on this
Y'all see me and psyche go around around 500 fucking times
I'm people are upset with me because I'm not people he's upset with me because they already know because all of them know
Me and no, I'm not going to get in between people's battles because usually people work them out
So I don't get in between that unless I see it's like too too far
These is amongst friends these people all used to be friends and supporters of each other
Not just one way if you know to me
Summer if you don't mind is that okay? Well you asked me a question. So I was answering the motherfucker
yeah okay i think it's absolutely fine like especially when there's like like imagine like
there's two brothers going at it like they'll fight like fucking crazy but you know
dr it's fucking crazy to come outside like what's the rope problem though because like he made
like an ai song i mean no that's not it no that's not it no ai song is not the fucking issue
Well, you keep fucking asking it. I'm letting you know, bitch boy. Okay. You're gonna you're gonna finish your point after I make my question because
Whatever the fuck I want because you don't run shit. You're just gonna talk over people. I mean, I can if I want
So you you you just demand that shit, and you can you give me the same respect, right?
Cuz I'm telling you that it's not an AI song you keep repeating yourself
I don't like look in the middle of my point and you talked over
It's not it
So pay the fuck attention. I don't need to catch you up on the lure of what's going on
I don't give a fuck what's going on here.
Well, you do because you get to ask me about an AI song, and that's not what this is about.
You just talk over people, that's all you do, and then you cry about it.
Get to your fucking plate!
You cry when I talk over you
This has nothing to do with you, so I really don't even have a conversation with you about it
Cry 24-7 so what the fuck you should you probably should
You just talk loud give a fuck cuz it doesn't do with you
Your guests like no, it does have nothing to do with you. So there's that
You're just another motherfucker listenin that's it with a fucking opinion
Because you think this is over
That's you think this is over
The fuck up goes a lot of people there like that are
You know what? You guys want me to suck the shit out of your channel.
Burn her ass in the fuck up.
Okay, well, I just want to show something.
Okay, now I have to, now I have to, I have it ready.
Okay, so here's what I have and you don't like it.
It's okay.
AI song, dumb animal.
It's not about an AI song, you dumb fuck.
Listen, you don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
Straight up.
You're teasing me.
I don't know.
I don't need to have a conversation with you.
You're gaslight and psyche what you're not gonna do
Conversation
You know what I agree with you she should
I wouldn't call anyone. That's for your fucking panel. Fuck that
Hey guys, I'm gonna go get breakfast, but um, okay, I'll see you guys later
I gotta go. Bye. Bye, sweet. Okay. Sure. You made everybody run away. Okay. Okay, guys.
Fuck up. They asked me to come up holler. I have a minute goes. Okay. Yeah, we actually
thought we were gonna be cool. Shut the fuck up. Once again, not talking to you.
We would be arguing if you would let me talk to the person I cannot talk to.
You're asking questions about shit that has that to do with you.
Do you know what open panel means, ma'am?
Suck a dick. That's what it means.
It doesn't mean suck a dick.
But do you know what open panel means? Go ahead.
Black Psyche's dick.
I'll give you a third chance. Do you know what open panel means?
Black Psyche's dick. From the back.
Okay, cool. So you don't understand ma'am like anyone. I don't care. I don't give a shit. I don't
Me and him are talking not you
You go wait one minute
So I've been working on this. I don't know if you can see it yet. Can you see it? Okay. Do you see it on the screen?
Yeah, okay. You see it says psyche verse, right?
Yeah, I like the colors. Okay. Thank you. And then so it's kind of like, you know, inspired kind of a little bit by IP 2, but it's not IP 2.
So there I have a, so I have, you know, some channels listed. And so I wanted to put hotness summer and talk your ish on it for you.
And so, I mean, I appreciate that.
You're welcome. And I also have like pages on there.
other people because i'm being accused of like not wanting to promote people like you know and stuff
like that and it's not and like i'm just being misrepresented but this was at like seriously
out of the kindness of my heart i really want wanted to help promote your channels and stuff like
that and other other my friends and so i think it's gonna be a friendlier thing and it's like so
that's all i want to show you so i'm still working on it but it's gonna be psycheverse.org when it's
way to say apply for people and stuff like that whole directory looks like a
directory of live streamers basically it will tell when you're on and stuff like
that so that's pretty cool like thank you very much I'm working really hard on it
and I do hope
I do hope you you like it. So there we go
Stuff like that sweetie you got a lot of cool things that you could do
You know to be people people talk shit about me every fucking day
It's like I promise you like I get I have a track I get more shit said about me than fucking
You know what I mean? It is what it is if people aren't talking about you. They're ain't doing something right now
I you know, maybe once all the smoke cools down some of people that you know, maybe you can at least have conversations right now
The smoke's up for everybody
and particularly the all of you all that I love and like and and support and will
continue to support you know I mean right now it's just tense for you know I
Like I said, I'm gonna take down and I'm not gonna play the beat as long as anymore. It's like, you know, I'm not good
I'm not gonna like really make any more. Well, yeah, I can't promise. I won't make any more diss songs in the future
But but it's gonna be more good nature. I don't know, but I think it was kind of you know kind of
Good, I think it's just different hat from both and it is what it is
You know, I mean only thing I'll say is if y'all wanted to stop and it
But you know right now again the motions are high everybody people's on both sides. I'm not just talking about them
Well, everybody's upset feelings this hurt. Whatever, you know, I mean
Shit happens, but it can't begin to move on or heal
From both sides not just you not just you know, I mean like everybody I'm talking about everyone
So
His mother did not I can't miss a child. I promise you I don't know like Bronzeberg very well
I mean he was on the show before but it's like I don't even have enough
I don't even know anything about his person. I've never even seen seen them on camera or anything. So I have no idea
For cuz I'm not the only person at the group right
But I know a couple people that are upset in this crusade. He's leading this crusade and he's like not leading the crusade because listen
Hold on. I just want to say this
Especially the women that are important all that each one of them are very strong women ain't nobody leading shit
They're just everybody this upset and frustrated right now
The katie woman is not some strong woman. She is just a like a follower
See, baby, just let it go.
Jamie, she's hurt Jamie a lot.
And it's like, and then she doesn't care about beat it.
She just wants to sit on the panel to annoy Jamie this whole time.
She's been trying to do that.
You know who I was talking about.
I was talking about Christina Bita.
God damn it.
I'll put names on it here.
Christina Bita are both very strong women and ain't nobody leading shit.
They're feeling better.
I don't hate Christine.
I love Christine still, but, uh, you know, she's very mad at me and it's like.
I I I've only apologize so much beta has just really said some things that you shouldn't like you shouldn't say to a friend
And it's like and I never attacked her like she's attacked me. Maybe I have been
She's really there to be fair there's been petty shit on both sides, okay?
So that's all I'm just gonna say in that middle lane, you know what I mean?
But like I'm not I can't be like, you know, it's like yeah, I love you to death dude, but like come on
We're not everybody has put everybody has played a part in this in one way or another
Okay, I just like
No, cuz we're talking that would be nice let us talk are you
Talking about so how do you know if I'm gaslighting you dumb fuck
Get his dick out of your mouth, dude. I promise you as soon as we get done
I will speak it right back in your mouth for him, but I'm trying to add just we want to talk right now. Is that okay? I
Don't think I mean you have to I'm not the owner of the YouTube
Don't ask because we were talking you're the one that keeps interrupting
Yeah, but you're talking about shit and you're trying to gas like him
You know what are we talking about? You don't even know what the fuck we're talking about how the fuck you don't
Gaslight you have gum nuts
Also, that's dumb dumb. Not dumb. Can you imagine if his mother would have swallowed?
That's a good one. What's your argument?
I'm not talking to you psyche. Anyway, back to our conversation.
I understand it's like, you know, you didn't say anything
Bad about like that bad about maybe today was a little worse, but but but that everything I said
I I've said to you me and you have talked about Alex me and you've talked about you know
I mean me and you have checked every single thing that I've talked about
Like I wouldn't say we haven't talked about
Fuck what you're talking about no one cares about your opinion shut the fuck up
That's a
You know, I get frustrated too. I get frustrated when I feel like for no reason like you know
Like I said earlier like with Alex and yours relationship
I was excited about you and Alex getting to know each other and it's like it's weird like you just want to like grow this weird
Like she's a better friend, and it's like dude
We're all friends
You know even if we don't get along we can start to get along because of you
Alex and I got Allison I really really clicked Alexandra and also Alexandra's come out and
Happy that you and Alex I'm glad that you have somebody that's by you that you could be friends with
I want nothing but the best for you nothing in that that's why when it's flown in like a competition type of thing
That's where I get aggravated. It's like dude. That's weird. I want to see you happy. I want to see you do the best
You do
But you've done that you've even done it with alex you did it with alex
He's you were like oh alex came up and and defended me alex
Baby, he's buddy trolling you more than you will ever understand
And I hate to break that to you, but I promise you he is buddy trolling like a motherfucker. He don't even like gay people
Okay, well, it's like like real shit
It's cool. Listen, baby, you'll you'll figure it out unfortunately the hard way and that's fine. I'm that's cool
I'm just I know Alex very well
Um, yeah, and it's like, you know, it's like Alex and I'm talking about the male Alex for Alex female that might be listening
Yeah, and Alex is like, you know, he's like last night. He was just so loud and I know it's like I keep them off a bunch of times
Oh, he's gonna get you in some shit. That's what he was trying to get you into
Well, and it's bad enough you already got all this dumb shit on your back and I'm not talking about beat it in all the
Bronzeberg none of that. That's not what I'm talking about
I'm talking about the people that are sitting people to your house and because bronzeberg and I'm not doing that
Sorry
No, I'm talking about Bita and and Christine and Bronzeberg what when I say that they're not doing that, right?
But I'm talking about the people that are doing that him doing the shit that he was saying
Dude, they're not gonna go after him. They're gonna shit on you even more and if he's such a good friend
Why does he continue to put your ass out?
Maybe maybe he maybe he's talking too much about like, you know a little bit aggressive
He's not a cop and he ain't getting nobody fucking arrested
But we know that we know his personality. We know he's like that. That's kind of like yeah
But unfortunately you're gonna be the one that that pays the piper for that one. No because that's what you understand
What I'm saying when I say that he's antagonizing allied and maybe like yeah, maybe yeah, that's what I'm talking about
Allied has been he has had his channel is 100% I'm not saying listen
I'm not saying he doesn't deserve some antagonizing shit
But what bothers me is at the end of the day the person that's gonna get the crazy should happen to him is you not Alex
Right and Alex knows that too right Alex or not. It's still happening. Anyway, the guy was the guy is still yeah
But though they could turn the fucking heat up even more. This is my point
More and then he's already admitted to doing illegal things
I mean, it's like yeah, and so I'm already in contact with authorities about it
We're very interested in this and they're extremely interested and so, you know, I'll handle things the way you need to that way
Not through fucking Alex. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, I know that's my point
Okay, I got you and you know, I apologize for you know, it's like for losing my temper with you and stuff and I apologize for like you know
You you you go where you want you say what you want you do what you want
It's like of course and you will I know but um, you know, I'm not gonna take it so personally. I thank you for like, you know
we both can take a deep breath and like come back
and talk to each other always rationally.
And I like, I appreciate you for that.
Of course, I respect you and I, you know, in your work
and I know you've been going through a hard time.
And so I just want to apologize to you
and thank you for staying my friend
because I know you could have, you know,
easily just left tonight and never come back
and stuff like that.
And I would, and so, you know,
You know, thank you for like leaving the
Friendships aren't always gonna be you know, I mean, I don't get me wrong. I love when we're all having fun and everything's great
I love that but sometimes people are gonna get into things and we've got into it before but like that's why I always say like I
Do believe not everything buddy, but I do believe in you know, things can be worked out. Yeah
Okay, well, the Nora wants to say hi
Hello, Nora. How are you doing beautiful?
Yeah
Norse here, and you know, I you know, I love my cats and it's like you know
It's like it's like if I had kids it's like be like people saying oh your kids are ugly and they have like bat
Is there clothes are dirty and stuff? It's like of course
I'm gonna take it really really personally and like or say that you know that's rolling those like you this is what I don't
This is the part and this is I don't understand right you hang out in a troll community
You always have from what I could see
And you know that if people see something like when they see they got something on me
And they know there's gonna be certain things. It's gonna trigger me and it's gonna have me go
Spatastic right
And it's like, okay, well here if I want to get it, you know, get get psyche irritated. Well, boom
I'll just talk about a cat litter box or I'll talk about some fingernails like
But it's like spreading it to like all like this huge like group of like these
Community and then people come and find you same thing with me people talk shit psyche
They come look for you and then they see you and then they see either you're like that or you're not like that, right?
Yeah, but it's like or they don't even like check because it's like I see a lot of people saying oh my god
Like and there's like that are they don't even know me and then it's like it's just like it's spreading spreading like that and people
Insulting of tarot and it's like oh this and this and it's like I've explained all these things like a million times
And it's like and then I continue to explain it and it's like it's going back to the and even if I was you know
I was like neglecting hygiene or neglecting cleaning at one point. It's like I've gotten so much better and it's like
And it's like no one is like recognizing my improvement. I mean you have a little no people do recognize your improvement
You just focus on the trolls
Well, DJ Electra page all kinds of people speak life into you all the time psyche and you just don't hear that
They're their criticism is louder than anything positive. We could tell you all some Jamie Nancy
I mean everybody he man everybody tries to pour positivity in you
No problem, but today I today I wrote a few people all I said all I did was send them the link to bronze first thing
I was like, oh, he's gonna he's gonna do another one of these and then it's like beat is like
Oh, well, you know, like three or four people contact me.
I wrote three or four people.
And so what these actual people I thought were my friends
all run to beta.
I mean, it's like-
It's not their job to fight your battle though.
Psycho you're a man.
And you, you wrote page dude.
She's a woman that's on crutches and going through shit.
And you're trying to pull her into some stuff
You said you wrote page earlier you know page is going through it
You know that she's on crutches and you want her to go fight your battle
Anybody to find my battle I just sent them the link and I told them that I was getting people knocking my door asking for scrap metal and
Yeah, but all I did was like say that Paige would be there anyway
She's at the first one too, you know, and she was there tonight, too
And so yeah, she always saying that she we all support each other, right?
But it's like oh, we're not here to pick stuff like we do support you
We do support you I get big hate session though, and it's like you have to say some of the things
Two videos dude two videos two videos you've made AI songs
You have sit here and then your own trolling you've talked shit too psyche. It's like you forget what you've done
What's the worst thing i've said i've said things like oh like throw bronze chicken into a pan
Well, okay, no christine
No
How many times did christine ask you not to play the crystal moray video?
How many times did she ask you you play this shit like twice a day?
Perfect make the Crystal Marie video. That's a trip kick video, and I like it doesn't matter and you're playing it
You you put responsibility on everyone else, but you're so
And the path that video is about Chris K and I've been playing it because of Chris K
She talked about you. You see you're deflecting. This is this is what I'm talking about
Well, I would love to see you just be like, you know what I did that and I did it because I was pissed off at her
And I was being petty you can't even stand on what you do
Really not pissed off at her but Chris K but Christine
We're being petty
I were not talking about Chris K. You were being petty because you know she just like she told you she ain't even upset what crystal said
It's the fact that her friend
Well, I'm playing it because of the other
You never want to hold you never hold responsibility for anything that you do dude. I love you to death, but you just don't you don't
Because you know what she asked you and then you know what you do you play the video two three times a day
I don't play two times a day. I play one. You were there for a second psyche. No, I wasn't. Yes, you are. Oh, whatever, dude
We've all watched it. Everybody watched it. Okay. Well numerous times. Yeah, but it's like still
It's like I didn't I didn't say the allegation and then Christine was like so like mean about it
And she was upset because she asked you not to play it and you kept playing it
Yeah, and you know all you keep doing is passing the ball
Yeah, because but you want everybody else to take responsibility, but you don't take responsibility for your actions
It's crazy because she keeps clapping me and so and then so and also with the beta thing
I was like, you know, I keep going to keep going to be talking about Christine right now
Hey, well Christine keeps clapping. I'm not gonna get into years of beta stuff. Okay. I told you that
There's no there's nothing there anymore. It's done. You know, it's over. It's over. So um, she's she said you know
I have a lot more history
It's done. It's done. It's done. But my point being is you just have to take responsibility
Sometimes you're petty just like we are here, but not in the same way that it's being like, you know, that's not true
Dude, it's not true. I'm sorry. What were the diss songs about beta? There's about her harassing me over this talking about beta
And you've made just songs about betas, dude
but i'm not i told you i'm not you want to keep going to her and i'm not getting into that
he just like oh i'm just playing a viral video no it's not it's not something that's viral now
it was viral 14 years ago you're playing it to annoy me until like it's you and i would just like
you do the same thing you put videos up to annoying her but in response but uh and i was
talking about christine you did the video numerous times and she asked you not to so then she started
Okay, well, Christine, her last name's not in the video, nor is her picture, so there's nothing identifying that she doesn't...
It doesn't matter. She asked you as a friend, then told you that it bothered her.
Everything was rude.
Yes, she did. She told you numerous times, dude.
She said, go to hell, so I kicked her off the show then.
Yeah, after you're doing what you're doing now, you don't want to take responsibility for anything.
that I I let crystals like talk but it's like we know crystal everyone knows she's a she's loony to
no you were playing the video after whatever dude okay well okay but look we shouldn't go into the
christine stuff or the beta stuff like you know it's let's just I'm not gonna go into the beta
stuff because you're all's relationship is completely different right but like it has
But that's that's and I'm just she's not to I'm not getting into it
How'd you get in the middle of the Christine and I it's like you know Christine and me?
I've known Christine for a very long time. I brought Christine to the channel. That's why okay, and I'm just giving you my opinion
I'm not in it. Am I okay? That's fine, but it's like it's still it's like, you know, you're willing to
Well, and to tell you that you're not owning your shit. Well, it's like I'm respawn I respond to things and just like they and then it goes back and forth and stuff
And I will withdraw when it's like and I think that it was a tip for Ted did not that it just put it on you
Did I right? No, right?
And you're here, so that's good. I mean you're the only I mean then that what's his name exiled one he came tonight, too
but also he's making allegations that are totally unfounded without any evidence and then totally
true untrue but uh fuck um so i don't know i think he said something about he was going to show a
video clip or something so i don't want to i'd love to see it but then he said it wasn't even on
this platform then he said it was several years ago so this is like very impossible plus i can
prove when i can i can prove how long i've been doing tarot i can prove it i i mean i can i don't
I can show at least from 2000, 2020, I did it professionally and I did almost 2000 readings,
positive reviews, over 2000 readings, 1800 positive reviews. So, I mean, it's like, and
I still have my Etsy store and everything. So, I mean, it's like, that's not a question,
but it's like, I'm so sick of being, you know, slandered over, over tarot, and then it's like,
oh, why is he doing tarot? Well, it's because I'm not, I'm hardly ever in a peaceful mood to do it.
Plus I wait for people to ask me, and then Bita's like,
oh, well, he just charges for everything.
That's not true.
I've done so many free readings.
It's like, incredible.
It's like, most of the readings I do are free.
And it's like, and then it's like,
but people are just like, not really.
Like, you know, it's just like, I've been slanted about it so much that people are like,
you know, believing it.
And it's like, that's really annoying.
Because that really does hurt my business.
What people are believing at Psych8?
What people are believing at people that don't know and ain't going to come here to you and
support you?
What about the people that are here supporting you?
Who gives a shit what Charles think I don't care what the people that are here are but that they're all in their little hate group
You know like you know just people are talking shit. It's part of YouTube. We're in the drama community, sweetie
I mean
People are gonna talk shit. I know but if I mean, I mean, I just don't see anybody else having I guess people
I get shit talking about me every day every day
Shows with all of your like yeah, I got whole channels on me sure do you're not the only one hate to break it to you babe
Well, I know okay, but it's pretty I got whole communities that talk shit about me every day
I've had bitches call the police and say I've stolen their car in another fucking state
Baby, I promise you, you ain't the only one.
Okay, yeah.
Okay, so, you know, that's what happens
when we belong to drama communities.
People take something and they run with it
until something else pops up.
Okay, yeah, and I respect,
and I do like have respect for you
and I do know you've gone through like a lot of the stuff
and I know you've gone through the difficult things too.
And it's like-
Yeah, I gotta, I mean,
I gotta sit in jail because of internet shit, so.
And so still I know I'm gonna say I understand I understand but
Yeah, I don't want us to be like no art has to be affected too badly by all this like a because a lot of people do get it
like all of a sudden it's like
Another I've taken time off because I can't another person. I just can't deal with fucking Jay dog
I've said I just took time off because I just can't there's certain things
It's just not worth my fucking energy and he that's another one
You know what I mean?
And I just feel like you do have certain people in your fucking ear right now that really don't give shit about you
But they're opportunists and they're they see an opportunity and they're gonna ride it
I have my eyes open to some of those things
The same time I do appreciate when you know
Thanks support. It's not real support. Remember that cuz remember just a couple weeks ago the same other fuckers was talking shit about you. So
and
Yeah, and I think a dog is an opportunity for not
You know going too hard on me
And you know, and I you know, I love you and I'm sorry
It's like getting stressful, but I hope we know I don't want
Other other relationships to like ruin ours and stuff like that because it's that's how it seems to happen like with everybody
It's like somebody there's like some other some other person they're upset about and then it's like it turns into like the only person
I can ruin our relationship is us. Yeah, but it's like nothing
I'm ever gonna say to you that what I said tonight on panel isn't nothing
I haven't sat right here on this panel with you many a times and said the same shit to you
I feel like people are in your ear from it manipulate and shit that
I don't know what this whole like, you know, you're in the hub of all communities because there's a bunch of different communities that all came together.
And what makes all of us communities.
Because I heard that kind of little shot that you threw yesterday and I was like, really?
What would I say? Which one?
About just about like basically we all wouldn't I wouldn't have anybody people wouldn't have anybody if it wasn't us being here
So something along the lines you said that I didn't say that I forget how you said it
I forget how you said it
That was more about other people because it was like I think that he is getting like he's like really excited to
He's like he's saying that is oh, I've always had
My brother's panel because he gets people all the time sweetie
Okay, well, that's he's had a channel. He just says it like how people to sub and shit like that
But like he has panels all the time
Actually saw the I saw him promoting that show particularly and and this show like too
But he went almost two months without saying anything
Right, because we weren't talking, I had nothing to do with it, like he wasn't here or anything, and it's like then all of a sudden he reappears hating me when we were like fine before.
You don't remember getting into it with him on other panels? That just slips your mind?
It slips your mind that you didn't you got into it with them on other panels
I just remember that beat is like when he was like, you know talking over me on beat is she kept like letting him on
But you only remember one time you don't remember him being in the chat
You don't remember him jumping up here on this panel. You don't remember
I remember like we might have I might have like keep them off the show or something like that
But or there's been many times you and wrongs were have gotten into it. I can promise you that
I don't remember and I say I don't think I was drunk, but it's like
Maybe maybe we did but I don't maybe stress is keeping your memory. I don't know but I'm let you know
This kind of anger just like sit with elbows like and then he's like and then it's like oh, I'm so sick of like people saying I
Was a support. I I don't need it to you like especially like him because it's like, okay. Well, he
Donated he made a big deal out of that because you said he didn't ever donate to you
Donated $10 to get flurry diamond kicked off the panel and so that's kind of like not even a donation
I could consider it. I was like, you know, he's got some he was like one of those, you know clapping things
Yeah, that's the only time he did and he's acting like he's like, you know, saved my life and stuff like that
So I mean it's like and then he yeah, I don't know. He's just like he's just uh, yeah
I'm just I don't
Care about oh, you should watch Chris one with her ranch because she was black in the fuck out of some of your people earlier
So what just that one?
Chris was charisma
Okay, I'll look into it, but I I don't know. She's been in pretty good mod, but
and
You know, I just never had a problem with her like, you know, she's always been kind to me
And so it's like and I am a sucker for kindness sometimes because I was like LES was like being nice to me yesterday
When I went to money for 20s, he's been nice to me and then all of a sudden he just like flipped like it is 180 degrees
Oh you motherfucker. I'm bronze bridge friend. Ah, and it's like, okay. Well, and I was like such a sucker to like
Hey, he's being cool, and he's like,
oh yeah, I'm sorry, I'll talk to you that time,
or I'll keep you in touch.
So you didn't go over there and you don't feel like
you got like a little snooty with anybody,
and that's why people got snooty back with you.
Because brunt they brought bronsford on it's like that that finally was talking to bronsford and it's like you know
And he was like oh and then he's like oh, yeah, bronsford totally destroyed you he won that battle
It's like okay. Well, it wasn't a battle, but and I don't feel like he did win any battle already
So there were people up there saying go psyche go psyche you'd be okay with it because there was nobody up there
I didn't notice that there were a lot of people that were that were questioning things that were going on in that chat tonight
And I did appreciate those people there's even people I didn't know and so that that was cool
And but it was like that's also because I have so many people blocks
I didn't even see most of the chat because I have so many people blocked because I just like I'm sick of everything
They say is like some kind of horrible show
So then why focus on that and why not focus on like your podcast that you've been doing with Alex or
named after me and it's called Psychius Sleep Tarot
and then he's like, oh my God, Psyche,
he's taking some hermaphrodite
because, you know, he's talking about two psyches
and he doesn't understand anything about it.
And nor does he, you know, I don't even know.
It's like-
And people say mine has been worse by pimp.
So I mean, like, you know what I mean?
Like, I don't, again, Psyche, like people talk shit.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Talk shit back to them or just if it gets to you too much,
take a break.
It's not getting to me too much. Well, it's like other than like, you know, I'm being like, you know, actually physically in the real world
You know, yeah, like you're not being game stop not from not
Not from Brownsburg. I know not from Brownsburg
That's who I'm talking about. I'm not talking about the what these idiots that are doing shit to you offline out or online
You know what I mean? I'm not talking about them
They're there. Well, if you go back and actually listen to that when I come up
I say, Hey AMC. I thought that was AMC from our auditing community. That's who I thought that was.
Until you said something and I heard you listen and when I heard you talking, I was like, Damn,
I was like, I didn't even know that. But if you go back, I say, Hey AMC, because that's who I thought
it was. And he said, I haven't seen you in a long time. So I thought that was one of our guys from
I was like, oh shit, I was like,
so it kind of seems like worse than it probably was.
Okay, so I understand, it's no problem.
Yeah, I understand that that was one of the
thick little sticking point.
Yeah, that yeah that guy's
He's the one that struck me and like you know be his friendly with him and he and she even said tonight
Oh, he's the one that porn bombs me and then I was getting accused of writing the n-word in the chat
And it was like and then it was like oh that was like my friend
I was somebody else's exiled one's friends or something like that. He's like, oh, can you let him back blah blah?
But I was like I was like for a few minutes like it was like it sounded like I had typed
Can you want to go back and forth with like bronze burden whatever?
No, and I'm ending it like I'm ending it
No, I don't want to go back and forth with them now because I'm scared or like, you know
I mean it's just because it's like such bullshit
But it's like I mean the the toothpaste is out of the tube already with everything because all these people are there's just so many
Bitter people that seriously though the worst thing I did to most of these people was kick them off the panel for maybe 10 seconds
And it's like people are just so
Well, in the group that I was on the panel with, minus one person, I can say that no,
that's not why those people are upset with you.
Okay, well well most of them I think seriously, but especially but or did it's like or they're just like people that are like these beta
Buttlickers and who are like just like so yeah, they just like you know are just like
Well, even the people I thought were friends go run to her and tell and and I report to her and stuff
And then she's like you know as we were all friends, right? You keep saying like we were just your friend
We all met and that's what happens when you build a community people are into
I was the exiled one from their community.
It's like, I didn't leave these people,
and my door is still open to most of these people, but...
Yeah, well, guess what, Saiki, guess what?
People don't talk to me either.
I bring a lot of people together.
A lot of people know each other
because they've jumped off panels or whatever,
you know what I mean?
So like, but do you see me crying in a bow and chariot
for the last two nights up there
with an empty fucking panel almost?
But it is what it is like people could get mad and not talk to me and not support me or they can come and support me
I don't even take it as they're not support me. I take it as hey, there's other shit going on and they're doing their thing
Right, we have ups and downs and like viewers and then the viewership is like that not that important like
Right!
She was like, oh I couldn't care less about her numbers or anything like that and it's like and she's acting like I
Oh, she was a stepping stone and then at least is a stepping stone and then Emma says she's gonna be no
I mean I'd say that probably all of us all you know I'm saying like
You got a lot of people out of all of those communities, didn't you sure and a lot of people have met a lot of people here
And that's like and I'm 100% because that's what we do right we build each other up and then we the building supports each other
Yeah, I'm sorry, I'm sorry to interrupt, but I've always said to everybody, and I'm on most people,
I'm like, please promote yourself. And it's like, it was made tonight. Oh, he's like, he's mad. I was
promoting Paige and Teresa. Who I introduced her to, like both of those people were here first,
and it's like, and I introduced, and it's like, and then it's like, Paige, you know,
I wrote Paige tonight. And then, you know, I didn't hear back from Paige, but but
Because you know people have real-life stuff going on that we don't really at some points don't give us good about you too drama
She wasn't busy enough to be there for an hour, so it's like I mean that's fine
But she can do that she can do that because sometimes people are going through a real
See, this is what this is what hurts me about you, psyche, is that you get so engulfed and I get it, right?
I understand it because I've done it myself, but it's just like you get so infused with this shit
That's going on on this YouTube stuff that you forget that you have real life friends that are going through real life shit
Like seriously, and he leaves the panel
Alright, well, I guess I'm gonna go cuz I'm not gonna do this. I don't I'm not gonna talk to myself. I'm sorry
I'm sorry, but I don't whistle. I'm sorry my mouth. That's alright
You it's like you forget that they're going through real estate and if so what if she comes in a chat? I know
Well, it's like because it's going through a lot of shit
Likey
But it's like from people I consider friends not like one word of support for me like not one
Or like, you know, or he's not like some filthy disgusting shit
She have to do that when she's going through real life shit
Other shit is like what she's going through so much that she wouldn't be there, but she's there
She's sitting there and she's like
Going out of your way to check on her everybody cuz I can tell you for me unless I've came up on panel. I'm
Hmm
How many times have you went outside of your stuff that you got going on checking on the people that you're asking them to step up for you
How many times well nobody ever does hardly hardly except for like a few people and then to everyone else tells me oh drop these people
I'm not talking about you mom saying how many times do you do it? How many times do I do I what?
How many times have you checked on page?
Have I picked on page?
checked on page on page
Yeah, she hasn't been on in a long time, but I would go to her show and it's like but I don't want to like become a center
Like try I don't want to become like a distraction from but you want you want her you want people to stand up and do all this
I go to people's chats. Sometimes I don't talk I watch as much as I can but I also have
2000 subs I mean, but if they don't know if you're not talking and they don't know you're there
I'm there supporting
in spirit like I definitely am it's like so but what if we all said that to you that's so fine it's
like a bit I mean but it's like but instead of hate watching no because so many people hate watching
I just say it's like so I hate watching I'm a hate watcher I've got 30 people in the room and nobody
talking and it's like and then in the last night I had like 16 likes 16 dislikes I mean I was like
so it's like wow it's like you know it's like there's a lot of people that are just hate like
um like saying bad things in the chat but they're yeah but they're definitely like
disliking the stream and and here to like you know just dislike it you know it doesn't matter
if they give you a thumbs up or a thumbs down it's the same thing you know that right for the
algorithm and it does help if you get more yes yeah but um well but no actually actually that's
false because it doesn't matter either one as long as they're hitting it it helps her either of them
Those are facts that they dislike is a thing, you know, it's like it doesn't matter
It still helps with the algorithm. That's why I'm I sure I always say it what does it matter if you hit the thumbs up or you
Thumbs down it's still good
Okay, it bumps your other of them as long as they hit it. It doesn't really matter. I mean, it's like I know that's true for like
Yeah, okay, well, I think I think I think hopefully
I I understand your points and things like that. Um, I think we're maybe we won't a hundred percent agree or see that I
No, we don't have to agree on everything
But it's just it's just like and I don't expect you to like go up there and say hey
I'm sticking I'm gonna stick up for psyche and like I'm not I'm not going to I don't I'm not
I don't expect that and I didn't think that but I mean it's like
I mean at least like
I mean, I don't know it's just like I would you know what I don't need to do anything because the people there know that I still
Hold on. No. No, this is the part. You're missing psyche. You think I need to jump through hoops to prove to you
But yet the people I'm sitting over there with have said and said we know summer still hangs out with psyche. Yeah, I should do
Yeah, but it's like people can hang out and not like me and it's like so it's like it's like I'd like really dude
Get it really really so you think I hang out with you because I don't like you really you think I have time like that
You bet like exile came up in tonight. Well, I don't care. I'm talking about me
Godie and stuff like that, you know, and so it's like I'm but I'm I'm talking about me. We were just talking about me
Yeah, well, yeah, so maybe I compared it, but yeah, but it's like still it's like they don't know they they're like
Oh, yeah, you're like oh, I'm still going over there, but it's like that doesn't equate to like I fuck with them
It equates to like I'm on I don't need to because everybody knows how fuck with you
So I don't need to jump their hoops because it makes you feel good. Well, that's what but they but it's secret
But he loves now when I thought those people have known me for a long time
But it's just like it gives him credibility. I'm saying and I don't need credibility my name
My my name is good. I have credibility with her. Come on, dude. Seriously. I don't even tell her
No, because it's like when people like Peter there, it's like, oh, well, this is a
No, no, it's not my job to do that to make you feel good. I'm your friend. I'm not your puppet
I didn't say you're public, but if you were to say I'm his friend you don't Alex
You have people do it all the time on this panel
I'm on his I don't need to and and if that's what so that's what I have to do to be your friend
That's what I have to do to be your friend
He's my friend, you know, I don't need to do that. Everybody already knows I'm your friend
Well, I don't know if they do
Well, I need to do that to prove that to you if that what you're telling me I have to do to prove to keep our friendship
No, I was I would know you don't do anything to keep the friendship, you know, okay
Well, then I don't need to do anything because the people around me know who I fuck with so I don't need to that's just that's a feeling for you
Mikey
No, I don't have to do that.
No, no, she doesn't psyche.
She doesn't have to do it.
This bitch is full of shit.
She's losing control and she's bleeding.
Fuck off.
You're bleeding through your little nasty twat.
Look at you losing control.
Fuck you.
No more kids about you, bitch.
OK, yeah.
Oh, come on.
Alex, come on.
You're labest fuck.
Your name is fuck. You're washed up has been
Everything you touch you've ruined everything you touch. Oh good. That's why you have ten kids and then where are they?
Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex Alex
kicking him off somewhere. Oh my god. Okay summer. And I and I will say Alex I'm talking about
we'll talk to her like that. She's my friend. Okay. And I'm not going to like let you on the
panel and talk to her like that. Okay. That's terrible. And that's what I'll say that. And
whatever you're saying about summer is not true. And you know, she is a mother and you respect
women and mothers. Okay. And I don't like it. Stop it, Alex. That's bad. Okay. Bad, Alex. Bad.
That's what I'll say. Thank you. I figured I'd bring up some decorum since you guys were having a positive conversation and you let that dickhead up.
Well, I can't control his mouth, but, you know, it's his mouth, you know, it's like so.
We'll just talk a bit. Yeah.
And Smash, the only thing with you is you keep saying like,
oh, well, you're telling me stuff about mentally disabled
people and stuff like that.
You don't know the whole story about Mason.
And so it's like, there's more to Mason than meets the eye.
And so that's all I'll say about that.
I work with the disabled, bro.
I know I could spot him.
He's not as disabled as you think.
OK.
Yes, the fact that you you want to lean in that direction of being disabled says something
Oh, he knows how to troll. Okay, so obviously he's not that
Mentally to fit
And they are not yes, exactly. Okay, so you don't think he's disabled Apollo. I
Have heard no, I don't think so
There's some stuff that's come to life to me, especially like...
Parlo!
We're gonna have to like hide people and fuck with them and stuff like that.
Be careful.
I told you.
What's up with Parlo, man?
Your bitch has been hiding in my chat, man.
Why won't you hit my panel no more?
Your bitch has been hiding.
Oh my gosh.
What you scared of?
What you scared of, boys, man?
Let me scare the truth.
What you scared of, man?
Why you be hiding in my chair? Are you scared the niggas over there man?
It's like you want you why don't you unbend me, bro? I don't have that big of an issue with you
I'll tell them to leave you alone when you come over there pot low man. You can come back over on the counter, bro
I'll call the wolves off. I'm like man leave the nigga alone man. Yeah
Just let you just letting you know I'm gonna throw a shot to Alex pretty much all day though. Oh, yeah
Alex are a whole fucking pussy with the fucking he's infection and everything
Alex is fucking crazy man. Oh, you know what? I know what I learned to do with him
Holding back. So when he get up on the only on money for tools, but I just trolling back bro
So all you got to do trolling back
I know how to do it. I've been doing something for months. I'll throw that now call my thousand rats like nigga
You are I'll troll him back. Well, yeah, this shit. I'll get hold on man. It's like a question real quick, man
I want to see you in Bronzeberg keep going back and forth cuz it's just entertaining
Now listen, bro
Yeah, I don't I don't brosbury. I fuck with my angles. I fuck I fuck with everybody, bro
I'll come round as motherfucker. I thought you can't get it. Oh, get it all get your boy
That's a big chance of your man talking mother fuck it. Get the fuck out my business, man
Waiting for you to speak in the end German, please
Wer ist ein guter Hund?
I
Okay
I never said please, bruh.
Yeah, some fucking balls, man. Why are you talking about?
Balls over here in this sector, man. Yeah, man. Oh, yeah, no
Stop
Yeah, I'm soft over here, man. Let's right now. So let me see what happened tonight. Okay, so let me see
I'm not so like you need to grow some balls too, man. I said I said I want to
I said I'm blocking me because I want to talk shit to Alex is Alex ain't going nowhere else where I'm at
One of them, yeah
Okay, and I have Exile blocked on like so many accounts
It is funny, but I feel like Bronzeberg
Bronzeberg's a homie man
Jesus, this guy is so boring that it's the same turning shit over and over. Yeah, not even original
Okay, so smash your unblocked
Thank you
I didn't unblock the exile, but yeah, it's like smash it, you know
I'm known for saying some wild shit from time to time so grab me some grace
Yeah, he's not to worry about him. Yeah. He's a harmless. Yeah. I'm I'm a gentle giant.
I'm fine with that. To everybody but Alex, I'll make him my son every day of the week.
I just you know, it's like and then it's like people are making all this big deal about oh
He's like hitting on straight guys. It's like oh, please straight guys can take care of themselves
Aren't you know straight with straight guys are 90% of the you know the males or then 95% of males and it's like you know
They're fucking they're fine straight straight guys are not some you know protected class right now
I mean Jesus Christ and they're supposed to be like straight guys and not know whatever. It's like I
Like, I don't even know their pictures.
Like, I was like, what am I hitting on an avatar?
It's like, and it's not like the ground
you're glowing to.
And he's like, and some of the straight guys
are like notorious for like, you know,
hitting on the women and stuff like that.
And that's how it kind of started.
I was like, you know,
the kind of giving it back to some guys and whatever.
And so I know with the Mason, it's been,
it seems, maybe it seems like it's like, oh no, he's like,
There's a disabled guy and he's like, misleading him or, or, but he's not as dumb as you think.
Aww.
Hey, sit!
Yes, I have two German shepherds you speak some German because they can train them with some German right well bird is a retired
Dole pain on she worked for an agency
And so she knows German commands as well as English commands, and she knows handsome
That's awesome, and it's here is retire her retirement or yes retired. He's retired. Yeah
Yeah, I always wanted to ask you a question. How is she trained in Germany?
What's your other said German comments? They speak they trained. She was trained in German. She's an import
They train them in
Them do train them in German. It's like they use like
She is they will buy a dog either like
from Holland, okay, or from
Germany. In her case, she was
brought to Germany. She was
brought over here and then
trained with a handler as well.
So, I see. Yeah, I was, I
was, I'm, I've never been a
cop, so fly it over exaggeration.
I'm only six eight. Yeah, so she
was trained here as well.
Okay, Sam and you want to come
up if you're here, if you're in
the chat, you can come up.
Um, that damn fishy fingers. Okay. So, uh, they're trolling me. It's okay. It's okay if they're trolling me because
And, uh, Psych, I have another German Shepherd. Her name is Taylor. And she, yeah, she's pretty quiet. She doesn't bark a lot or anything.
And Bird gets jealous of her when she comes around.
This is Rudy. Hi Rudy. Rudy's been sitting next to me on the couch for like weeks. He's like, he's just like this next to me
And then he goes outside. But yeah, Alex. I don't have a dog at all. She's just barking away. Yeah, she's fake
Dumbass
That cats really hardly any fleas because I do like I'm combing them a lot
It's like there and I'm also my house is cleaner than it's been in months and months a month
And so I'm not some kind of like I have
Headtimes where I've been pretty bad with like cleanliness and like you know
My house was a mess of like some of my houses
But this one I take pretty good care of and so it's kind of we don't do bugs in my house
The flea is any of that mess the yard is sprayed the house is sprayed they have
treatment on you know, I don't I don't do that. I have I have fleece sprays too and I vacuum and you know
I pick these blankets and I have a washer dryer and so everything's quite clean
But uh, you know and the cats are well taking care of and happy cats and it's like not like not like
People were talking like I was doing stuff to the cats or I was like, you know, or oh my god
65% of his cats are are missing and stuff like that's just like
I
Love your cat. You're always loving on home and you're always talking to them and I mean they go in and out
They're cats, you know, I do have a litter box by the way because I won't tell me
But it was a I was given a gift. Hey, are you psyching man? What? I mean, say listen, bro
Listen, man, if you I'm gonna stick
Okay, and I don't want to hear it. Okay. Anyway
I don't want to hear right now seriously
Bronzeberg okay, and it's like you know go go hang out with him if you want to as I don't want to hear
He's winning and stuff like that if you were my if you're on my show
I don't care if it sounds like I want people to kiss my ass
I want I want you to say you're winning if you're talking about people winning
You don't have to say he's winning and you know, I'm gonna be very annoyed by that. So
Yeah, anyway
Uh, let that be a lesson. Let's put you in the put you in the back
Okay, you're gonna be you know, you was you're still sitting there. He wanna you want to go? You want to go? Go ahead?
You said do I want to do what you want to go?
You know, so you want me to go in on you, bro? I ain't gonna do that to you man. I'm gonna do that to you, bro
Okay, I could if I wanted to I ain't gonna do you like that man. I don't I'm not mad
I'm kind of just kidding too
but
Now I'm gonna go in on partner on Apollo though Apollo shirts. You stay shut your bitch
Stop talking to me nigga. I know why you mad
Niggas just destroy you on my panel
Yes, I'm still crying. Yeah, I know them niggas them niggas killed you on my panel, bro. You mad as I ain't say
Okay, you come to black land when you come over to black town, bro
I'm gonna take you to my good funky time. I'm gonna take you
Not my fault I'm white
Man, you motherfucking orange you fucking green. You don't got white skin or black skin green
metallic
You burgundy you got burgundy skin motherfucker. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I can go there and be white and be be just fine
I ain't talking to you man
You like you don't like cats with a friendly ghost me
Just your ass up you like the dad for motherfucking Adam's family the brother
I
Don't fuck about you. I don't give a fuck about you your muscles are your ugly bald head. Mr. Clean looking motherfuckers
All right, I got you bruh, man your head like a motherfucking tortilla shell
I go to this day
Your fucking ball here like a night stand like an egg cell. Yeah, man
You're here like a BBL motherfucker. You're here like a collapsed ass
Light bulb head having ass nigga
Funny face looking motherfucking you like a cartoon character. You like Charlie Brown
What mom?
Whoo, that's your sandwich head ass up here like a motherfucking pink your head your head like a pink piece of bologna
Your head like a motherfucking your head like a tape you rang your head like a bald-headed elbow
Fishnet head motherfucker
Like, bro, you ain't got no eyebrows or nothing.
You look like a fucking, you look like a creative player
from 2K.
Why are your eyes, damn, you're on the side of your head.
You look like a motherfucking creative player from 2K.
You look like a nigga just drew you and you came to life.
You weren't even born.
You didn't even come out of a pussy.
You, nigga, just drew you and you came to life.
You were drawing.
You look like a stick figure.
Where are you, man?
It's fine.
Well, you got a hole.
Steal it here, you motherfucking.
I don't need to make some mistakes with your eyes.
I don't think I'm going to make them, man.
Hold space between your eyebrows.
That nigga here looks like a frying pot.
chicken dinner on your ball head.
Teacher, I can ask you a question.
Is this what you people call cooking?
Yeah, I'm cooking. I'm cooking. I'm cooking his ass
Because I'm still raw like
About
He unblocked you how come you ain't in the chat trolling Alex? Why are you still up here?
I don't know
Cuz I find you cool cuz I find you cool mr. Queen
You're gonna come up before us mr. Clean mr. Clean
Are you gonna make me rice uncle Ben uncle Ben you're here like a ball sack ball sack head-ass nigga
You're here like a you look like a naked mole rat raccoon face
More here than me. What are you talking about? You're here like motherfucking number nine apply to you, dude
your head like a thumbnail thumbnail
Man, put a ball cap on your motherfucking head
But you need to wear a bag or your face
Put a hat on nigga
You need to wear a motherfucking Donald Trump wig when you go out and put it
Can you guys slow it down?
I take some notes
Take some notes
Okay, buddy. Yeah, I want you learn cooking
Go on cooking. Oh, yes
OK
Let me tell you how to cook man
Maybe like an unseasoned piece of chicken like an unseasoned motherfucking turkey leg no flavor
Your picture look like your picture look unseasoned motherfucker
It does actually I'll give you that
Man put it out. I got so I got a word with I got some word of advice for you, man
No, it's not begging other men to be unblocked. Oh, can you please daddy unblock me? I want to go in the chat and show
I just want to please unblock me. Cry me a river
Cry me a Rick just move on with it and cry me a river
You're here like a motherfucking light lantern
No hair having asked
Musket rat. I'd rather go death. You're like a shaved pink monkey
The chunky monkey
Blast monkey monkey the chunky monkey. I called you a monkey. That'd be racist, too
I got to be what?
Yeah, if I called you you look like a ball-headed baby. You look like a girl, bro, baby
That that my my
Racism
Such a bitch
But somebody in the chest why put a laughing emoji in a chair, at least I got somebody to laugh
I did my job. Okay, it's cool. That's what I gotta do man. Throw some goddamn jokes
I'll be throwing these unseeds and ass jokes. Then y'all be up here crying and shit. Come on. We're that shit
That's your bitch ass up
That's what I'm saying y'all be getting up here crying. Oh, man. He was my friend for five years, man
He brought me shut your bitch ass up
Shut your pictures. Oh
Man, I lost my friend. Oh
Get this nigga Kleenex
How many beers are you down tonight, dude?
I can tell you y'all like what five no you a soft giant you six you six eight, right?
Why are you up and crying? I hope you're begging a gay man. You damn this seven foot tall
Maybe you should you could be in the NFL nigga. I want to talk shit
Maybe you can be a motherfucking line back in the NFL right now
You'll be crying you're prepared a gay man to unblock you nigga. You need to go beg a
Tell him to shut your bitches off tell him
Now you tell them that it tell me now you tell them that Scorpio
You tell them that solid view tell them that right now
I'm waiting for a swollen tongue over there tell me
Yeah, we got a rat man Alex in the chat Alex. That's your man. You know what Alex?
I'm I'm gonna catch you a money for two old's panel because I ain't cuz I might get put in the back over here
I'll catch you over there on money for two old's panel. Oh, you got your bitch ass over there
I'll cook you again like I did the last time bitch ass
Oh, you got some real heat with Alex
Crusty move with her money for tools panel stomped on the curb stomp. That's that's nothing for him. Yeah
I can't use the troll of trolls and all that shit. I've smacked
Can't out troll me. I put a nigga on the Summon Jam screen
You won't you won't talk shit about true zone. Yeah, I think you think bronze bird is bad
No, I'm way worse than bronze bird
On the Summon Jam screen for the whole winter spring and fall
But you'll get your hands on the screen everybody
The whole motherfucking shat and pan will cook you
I don't know I see my name come my name up
Nothing now, yeah, I got it man
I do love doing the show, and I even like a lot of the trolls,
but I like, you know, there's trolling that is like funny, and there's trolling that is like,
like, just like, goes too far, and it's going a little too far with some things, and, you know,
and I have dealt with a lot of stuff later on in the past couple of years,
It's like it's like maybe a little bit of a
You know friendly your troll friend friendly your troll. I want to like I want to make I want to like clean up the trolls a little bit
But I do have a lot of a lot of good people here. I have a lot of good people around me like summer and
Apollo even she was so in a smash
No, no, no, no, don't put me on the on the same side like summer. Don't know
Summer even summer sitting in a tree
No, I ain't with no clicks, bro. Don't don't put me with nobody
Yeah, I go on a panel cook a whole I go on a panel better whole panel niggas by myself man, I put in work
Okay, I ain't got a clicker. Well, I ain't got a clicker with a bunch of hyenas, man
I'm a motherfucking lion. I smacked one unit with his lines Paul
Yeah, we don't have conversations before man, you know, I ain't I'm not listen brah
I gotta try to tell you I ain't picking and choosing between you and a new man. It's a shit. I'm just a spectator
That's all it is bro. I ain't picking the choosing with nobody
I don't have nothing invested with nobody on YouTube. He said he's your brother and stuff like that. No, yeah
No, I can't say he's my brother. I just what he cool
Cool
I ain't about me saying somebody's my brother sister. I don't have nothing invested with nobody on YouTube bro
It's a it's only a couple of people this you know that you know, I got close to me outside
I got close to outside of you to whether now I ain't no friends in this shit, bro
Just like being in the street, man
Nigga hug you and shank you at the same time
I'm gonna fuck a hug you tell you they love you mean why that take them there take a long ass machete
Cut your leg off. Why are you hugging you?
Ain't no love in this shit, man
Yeah, that's the really shit. I can tell you man into anybody listening, bro
There's no friends. There's no honor among Steve's man. Ain't no friends in this shit, bro
My fucking tell you they love you. They dare for you
But it's not IPC where we're gonna go start macing homeless people, okay?
And so it's like but even people that makes homeless people seem to get like a more of a break than I do so
You know, they should remind me this should remind me of being at work
All the fake love I seen going on that work niggas all my co-workers in that show like many niggas phone it
Old girl. They being that all
Buddy buddy as soon as the motherfucker leave. Fuck that bitch man. I like man. I said, what you just sitting with him eat lunch
Now it's fucking my song man. It's some funny
Summer did you see the cue thing and like I just want to get your opinion on that
What did you think about that if you saw it?
If you didn't see it then
Do you know what i'm talking about the cue?
Summer I guess she's gone. Do you anybody watch the cue thing anybody?
Paulo smash, you know, I don't know what this
Okay
And but yeah, well he he's a streamer. He's like
You know, he was recently sleeping in a homeless camp
He left his he left his bag with the guy
He was sleeping in a tent with for a week and left for three weeks. He came back the bag was gone
And then he maced him in his tent in the face.
And the whole can of mace.
That's what happened.
I just wanted to get your opinion on that,
but it's kind of crazy.
You didn't hear about that?
Woo, I found out that IP2 people,
that's a thing with them.
And that's kind of disgusting.
And so definitely I'm happy to be starting my own network
Wow, so I didn't know all that was happening like
Really harassing the homeless. No, no, no, no, no
Before you start here, I'd like to add something on the discussion you had to with some okay
My opinion. Yeah. Yeah, go ahead
I have to agree with her on one thing, you know, obviously, this is a drama community and people
Gonna make all kind of lies all kind of bullshit about each other
Right, but what I disagree what I disagree with you with her is this goes for both sides
Okay
So if one side you have to accept the bullshit to talk to one person then the other person have to accept it, too
Yeah, you know you can't say oh, I can't talk bullshit about you, but you can't talk bullshit about me
Yeah, exactly. I
Because it's like I felt like it was a double standard a lot of time where it's like anything
Yes, it'd be a big deal and then it's like if they could say everything they want
It's like I said both sides to be clear
I never said one time. I didn't say I know you somewhere but there's a lot of I know
I'm just letting Apollo because he said that that way he was making like I said one side and I clearly said both sides
But did you see that? Okay? I missed it then. I missed it, but
My points, sorry
Uh, my point is again, that's what I have since I joined this this panel. Okay
People think some people think they are more special than the other, you know
No, I can talk anything about you, but God beware you talk something about me. Yeah
so if you if you expect other people to accept that's what when I said tit for tat that's what that
means in college is so you know tit for tat tit for tat yes I'll go back and I'll talk shit maybe
sometimes on my stream after and it's like then they'll respond with it you know tit for tat that
means both parties but it's been a lot of a lot of it's okay oh wow he said this or he didn't do
this it's like well it's like I don't know it's just let me ask you a question so yeah
Whatever could it could it be a time to where you and bronze bird bronze bird could like talk it out with nobody around
Because that's because I was at me and this one guy from my from my sector. We had problems
We were trolling each other going back and forth, but we had a discussion behind the scenes
We talked we talked like man, but he didn't have his subscribers. He didn't have his subscribers church, you know
I didn't have my subscribers church, you know, we was like, man, you know what?
Yeah, I apologize for what I did. I mean, you know what, we can still troll and joke on each other
All the other shit we were doing, but let's leave it alone
That's a great point because I really could I do think that like like if I was to talk to Bita that night when I wanted to
One-on-one and it was just like we could like because we've talked on the phone one-on-one
And we like the last time we did we got along we talked on the phone one-on-one
We got along we talked for like two hours and we were it was like great and but that night
I went on and then it's like we got kind of fun on the show, but then it's like all of a sudden like
turn when other people started getting that's why I can guarantee I can
guarantee I can guarantee if you had a conversation if you had who's that
talking about if you had a conversation man behind the scenes without nobody
around yeah yeah we'll be good that's with anybody bro because that's what I'm
saying me and the me and dog but Bobby Knight to be exact we was going back and
forth for months but we talked we had that discussion behind the scenes like
man like you know what bro
We met at the end of the day. It's just entertainment. You know, we chopped it up and that was that yeah, but nobody around though
So sometimes that's what it takes. I
Would like to do that. You know, it's like if you if he's open to that
I'd be happy to talk to him one-on-one in private
And then it's like, you know, because if you go on if you go on through third person
You send in this person and they trying to come talk on your behalf that person talking on your back
That's not gonna work bro because then she can get
Yeah, I got to talk like me. Yeah, exactly. There's a lot of people that are like
That just like they cheered on they get involved people get in it turns into like a group thing
It's like that same thing in real life. There's like a group of people or what I want with people
I got along perfect the people one-on-one and then it's like their friend comes around and they show off to try to show off
And it's up like that and it's like it's maddening and it's like but people do change around other people
It's like a chemistry and it's like
And so but I would like to be able to talk to people one-on-one and I would even well
That's why I said hopefully you guys could let the smoke calm down for a little bit and then maybe people could talk
You all talk. Yeah, I would like that
I would like that but then once you all talk because I've also seen you and be to do this once you all talk
You got it when you come back not worry about what the fucking they say or say
Yeah, but but the thing with beta and I is like that's what she she's like
I just went to her show, she stopped coming here, so I just went to her show.
I'm not going to point fingers, I said I'm both sad, so I don't want to get into the show.
I don't think that's my favorite, but I'm saying what happened was like...
That then like there's multiple people on the panel including him and I got screamed over on the microphone
I couldn't I was I watched back even Kate the turtle who's like I mean I've seen I've seen it for both sides dude
And I'm gonna continue to say that and it's like that's the thing you want to sit here and put everything on everybody else
Quick so I know we don't see that you know, I don't fuck with you don't fuck with me
But i might ask you a question. You said you knew true. Would you set something up between these two?
Bronzeberg laid on down the road between bronzeberg and
I already said it's a sport when we and him were talking
That's why I said that they got two choices. They can keep going back and forth and that's fine and dandy
Or they can let the smoke settle and then maybe talk
And even if there is like trolling going on it's like at least if there is an understanding about
Of course there's going to be trolling going on because there was trolling coming on both parties. You were trolling too
Right, but I'm saying it's like if we could come to an understanding about it like because I would like that
But it's like that it's like we're gonna get the point
But that's what happens when you when you engage in an avert and verbal war broke things get said
They both say don't make a right. That's what happens when you trolling bro
I didn't start a war. I didn't start a war with them and I didn't start with them like seriously a lot of people start with me
Like maybe I don't think there's not that many times
I basically will mirror people, I will mirror back.
And so it's like, just like when you,
or someone was really nice to me,
I don't know if it's LES yesterday,
he was like all friendly,
and then it's like all of a sudden,
and he like turned on me.
It was like, suckered into like any kind of niceness,
any kind of like,
and it's like, I'm so willing to forgive.
I'm so willing.
It's like, I'm so willing to talk it out,
and I'm like willing to hear, like,
I mean, I don't try to hate anybody like but I'm gonna say I'm gonna say one thing. I'm gonna get up out of here man
one at the end of the day, bro
Y'all still when it comes to viewership y'all still support one another because if he's talking about you his views gonna go up
You're talking about him. You're gonna get your views
I'm telling you but I did this before with another nigga on my on my in my second bro at the end because we talked about this like
But you know what even when we beefing
We our views my your viewers are gonna come over here. My views are go to your channel
So at the end of the day, we still have any chill out as we sending people to each other's channels
That's an understanding that that's a lot different than just like coming at me out of nowhere
And like there's nothing and I'm not gonna go on his show
Especially like shows like that were even if you watch it from the bushes. You're still supporting
Well, I was watching
So if you're looking this over one should continue for the future, right?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, I don't I don't give a fuck what they do. I mean, you know what? It's entertainment, bro
Fourth wall is like when people people reference and being a show or something like that
I mean, it's like so much. What I'm kind of doing now. It's if there's an understanding
It's it's a different thing than just like someone coming at you. They got to know where
And then, you know, and then it's like,
but it's not out of nowhere.
There's illegal stuff.
It's not coming out of nowhere.
Well, for me, it came out of nowhere
because I don't know why he's mad at me.
And it's like, what did I,
I don't think I was that drunk.
But I did, I used to do, I used to drink a lot.
I used to also do very, very, very long days
where I'd be on for 12 hours
and a lot of stuff would happen.
And I'm going through a lot of videos
and I'm seeing like a lot of stuff.
like that happened that I don't remember at all.
And I'm like, wow.
For example, like some people who I thought were friends
were bullying me at a certain point.
And I would like basically just get off the panel.
And I would like, I would just like leave my own show
and stuff.
And I, well, maybe I do that sometimes still,
but I still, I was listening at least this time.
I met those times I was only listening to it.
So.
But this now now unless I fell asleep, which is kind of rare
I will be listening to the show. I'll be backstage doing stuff and stuff, but I'm gonna try to like
People are friends that are Michelle
but
You know, it's like it does like there somehow. It's like there are there are like reputations and I and
Especially since I monetize and stuff like that
It has
Trying to get a different audience because the thing you're asking for and you're in a drama community is just
You know you say like I asked for IP to and stuff like that
I mean, those are the community you said you came up with.
I was born out of IP2.
I was born.
My father and IP2 is Benny and stuff like that.
And so, but there's so much that I've learned since that, that I did not like the last six
months, maybe, but the first, the first, the first thing that the IP2 people that
basting the homeless is a thing.
So somewhere I was going to ask you, what do you think about Q?
Yeah, that's why I don't fuck with IP2 people.
That's why we would tell you.
to be a part of Abbey too.
If somebody does too like that in front of me,
I'm gonna mark the fuck out of them.
That's what's gonna happen.
I was just about to say that.
It seems like he's pretty easy.
If you hurt a homeless person in front of me,
then you're gonna have to hurt me too
because we're going at it.
I don't compare to your man.
Exactly.
I saw a video here on PsySpenderman.
I don't know if Chris, but they were, holy shit.
Chris K.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've never liked him.
Man.
Guys, guys, guys, and me having somebody on the show,
does that mean I endorse them?
Sometimes I have people on the show so they can.
No, no, that's not what I'm saying.
What I'm specifically talking about.
I'm not saying that.
When I am specifically,
and you know what I'm talking about,
in the very beginning,
You were like, you know, you wanted certain things like you wanted, you know, the Howard Square and you wanted the soft Abbey to like
All right, wait a minute. Let me finish
And we would ask it there and say psych dude, you're so good with your fucking terror
You're so good with all you know what I mean? Like you have so many gifts and you're like, no, no, no, no
And then you got what you were asked for and well it comes with a lot. You don't get the pick and choose
because it comes when it's bad and it's good right right and what i'm asking you is do you think
have you ever thought about changing your whole this algorithm and everything up because the
things you're asking for being in a drama community i am it's not i mean it ain't gonna
happen it's not realistic man your community will not allow that okay hello hello
People that are in here tonight. I haven't had one problem with anything anybody said in the chat
I mean hardly say I love this. I just say this is good. Like I say there are
Certain different types of trolls. All right, I know and so I'm fine with these types of trolls
The types of trolls aren't like you want to punch you I mean, you know
People that are yeah, but this is not what I'm seeing and Bronzeberg aren't trolling you
Well, no, well, I don't know Christine is kind of a troll. Oh, that's not trolling. There's far more than trolling. Yeah
And really I think Christine is a little bit, I mean come on, I mean it's like Christine
Well, but we can say the same thing about you. I mean don't take Christine for a second Christine
No, it was crystal. Okay, Christine is like I was trying to have a funny show and it was like
I found it funny and I'm sorry that you didn't find it so funny
Your last name wasn't said you weren't Docs your picture wasn't shown. It could have been any Christine, you know
You took it so personally and you made it
Fuck you psyche fuck you go to hell
Because she wasn't upset with what crystal said
She was upset because her friend went and listened to what she was saying.
It's a drama for me on a T. It's mad at Chris.
But again, but we've talked about the same subject for six hours and here's another myth.
So do you think maybe you're being a drama queen right now?
You know why I played the clip over and over because I was showing that I was saying no,
Christine has it and I was like, I know she asked you not to.
and you thought it was funny and you kept playing it you want people not to treat you with drama but
yet you beat people with drama summer we're not on good terms anymore so i'm going to play because
she's pissed me off but she can talk shit about you what are you crying what are you what are you
upset about fair game makes me have a you can play a video and she can respond whatever she
chooses i'm sorry so why are we upset i'm not okay maybe it's a defense mechanism maybe it's a
Yeah, it definitely is because I had no problem is Apollo you're sitting here saying okay
I'm gonna do this because we're no longer a good time. It's cool, but then she could talk shit
And that's our defense both
But I'm gonna play the video, you know
Then you're upset because he's talking shit. I'm not upset. She's talking shit, but I'm gonna talk back
I'm gonna talk shit back and I'm gonna play that video again, you know, it's like because that's why I eat
That's why she's talking shit. So that I mean you've got what you wanted
Goes in a circle, right? It's like so it's both. It's not just one you started it. We can and you say you did
Choose to come in on my panel. I would talk to her we can work it out
But she's not going to she's like i'm never going there again, and i'm gonna kick him off of every panel. I
Settle
Smoke settle you keep putting fire on it. Then you want some people to come talk to you while the smoke's going
She is too, she is too, by clapping me and not letting me explain.
What are you going to?
She's going to respond and you're going to keep playing and doing what you're doing.
What are we upset about?
Basically even.
Right.
So why are you upset?
That's my point.
I'm not really upset.
I mean it's like.
Okay then.
We shouldn't be aggravating about the flaw anymore.
But I'll do tip for Kat.
I'll go back until she stops and then I won't stop.
So it's going to go forever and that's until we can reach an agreement.
So let's not do a $6 stream talking about you don't want this stuff.
She comes back here and we can talk. I'm not going to come to an agreement.
It's like she has to come here and she is going to force her.
You're going to keep trolling her to make her talk to you and you think that's going to work.
And then you're going to get upset when people do panels to talk to you about you.
Psyche. I will. I will.
You can. You can do that. You can, but don't be upset when people are on panels.
She talked to me and discuss it and then I don't care y'all can do whatever y'all want is what I'm saying
But I'm just saying don't care about it. He doesn't have a show. So how can I talk to her? But she doesn't have a show
She runs both of my chair. She's a co-host of both of my channels look and now I'm promoting her
And so it's like now maybe she has a reason to talk to me
But wow
Now Christine Christine has no reason to talk to you but trying to be your friend when she was that was it
Well, she has no agenda
Your channels are coming off
No, it was a joke come on summer I can take a dick
Yeah, well, I didn't you choose to take a dick. Okay. Oh my god. Well, I bet okay
And you ain't took dick in how long so you really can't claim that
You're done. You just told me and I can't throw you back. I'm just kidding Summer. It's all trolling. It's summer. I'm I don't have a mean bone in my body. All I do is like act, right? It's like I'm trolling too.
I know. Well, we're just gonna be trolling each other. Okay. Miss. Miss troll. You know, I got down all day long. I can back. I'm.
But we know but somewhere and I have an understanding not because we talked back in private or anything like that
We don't understand it just because you know, she's just cool and she gets I don't she gets it on on a level
some people don't like where
She'll come back and talk it out. That's the thing. It's like
Where people cut me out and cut up all communication and then goes and then just talk about me behind my back
And then I see it and it's like then I'll get really mad which happens, right?
But some are technically we're on panel. So I don't know how much behind anybody's back. I mean, the whole world could see all of it.
Yeah, but it's like even on panels is like people don't know I'm watching it or it's like, yes, we do. Yes, we do.
So I'm always watching. Okay. I'm always watching. Okay. I watch always there's silence. We all do.
We all do. I am like God. I'm omnipotent. I just have eyes everywhere
Even if I'm not watching I have people to talk to me about. You knew you were watching that because you knew it was good
They were gonna be talking about you hate waters hate water messages for everywhere. I get I am
But but the thing is the thing is
We all say it's okay
So I should give all the brands, okay
I saw it just joined it so many pennies. Okay. And he didn't have the chance to say Evan. Hello. Hello
And people who normally never joined this panel all of a sudden they pop up and then
Say you gay fuck
He wants to have a conversation he has it on his channel just like we did tonight where he could control it
It's simple okay, but if you really want to have that olymp ranch and he knows that because again
We're in a drama community. So you're asking a whole community to just not be what it is what it's been before us and what it
Will be after us. That's not gonna happen
But you he's got his own so he could control the conversation
No, I don't want to control the conversation because I will go one-on-one at the most of the time
You know, it's like I'm not gonna let me so he don't mind the drama. I mean, it's what it is
I'm a gay guy. Do you think do you think I care? I do like drama and I like I like people in the chat
And you know, like it's like that's a normal reaction. That's why I'm not up here trying to make excuses for it. Okay
I might as well make it interesting if I'm going to do it, it's called a show.
First of all, people take this so seriously, like it's like life and death, but it's like
actually it is seeping into my own private life, which is like that's not appropriate.
And so that's,
No, that's fine.
I don't agree with that.
And you know it.
I've talked about that plenty of times.
That's great.
Yeah, sometimes it's getting to that off the panel level and it's like I want to keep it on the pan
I've been it's like and I'm not saying like, you know, it's all you know
One thing I will do is if I know that somebody is is known or a type of person that might even take it into real life
I'm not going to go back or forth with that person somebody. I know it's gonna keep off panel
Then I'm cool with that we can talk to each other we go is I mean I'm gonna go to hell everybody knows that
I'm not I'm not gonna follow your all's guidelines or rules when we get into it with me
I'm gonna talk shit. It's what I do about any and everything
I want to because people do it to me every fucking day my past and things I've been through get thrown on my face every fucking day
So
I'll probably see you there we both have thrones there. Okay, so
I got sent by Christine to help too, so we're going to meet there.
No, I really do have affection for like almost everybody, you know, it's like and then it's like it go until it gets to that like nasty area
That's when I like start having problems
But I really do have affection for everybody and it's like I don't people take it very personally if they get kicked off
So I do have a show to run and sometimes people
So there's some people that are not super interesting. There's some people that are like have bad sound quality
I understand I had bad sound quality for I understand when people kick me up sometimes will block me and stuff like that
But, you know, it's like, you know, I'm improving and I'm getting a little better at it, but
I think my show is going fine.
But uh, it isn't not it's not the easiest you get your mic shit under control. That's
I got sent to like actually one night. Yeah, I got sent a new microphone as a gift
It was like actually instead of finding manure on my long one day
you know my outside my door I found a brand new microphone and
I don't know the person wants to be mentioned
but I always want to thank the person first this microphone
It's a great microphone and it helps to show a lot and and I do have
Around me, so I'm just saying I'm think I'm most of the time. I'm like 99% thankful 1% of the time
I'm like, you know little little bit of a bitch, you know, and it's like what was that tonight about someone's like
Oh, well, he's like the sassiest, you know, bitchiest gay guy in the like I know I'm not trust me
There's a lot more bitchy sassier than me. I'm pretty masculine when it comes to like most gay guys
And plus I can hang in this community, which is like not a lot of gay people will like that like that
I can I can put up with you know
being called F-A-G-G-O-T like it's nothing, okay?
But not a lot of people.
So it's like, I really can't hang.
And it's like, so I'm cooler than people think.
I don't know.
Some people think that I'm just like some like little...
Two-Face Pansy or whatever, but uh
Whoever said that knows who I'm talking about, but uh, yeah
So don't but don't mind if I call you a two-faced bit. He's not not you some of those
I call somebody that in response to them calling me that on their show. So
I'm not telling you do you babe. I'm not telling you you want to go back and forth. Do you want to whatever do you?
I'm not saying that at all, but one you there's two things you can't do you can't sit here and expect people to sit here and just
You know what I mean fight battles
I don't scream to the top of my lungs. Hey, I'm friends with psyche. Everyone knows I'm friends with psyche
Yeah, everybody does though
So I don't need to I don't need to prove my friendship to anybody and if I have to prove it to you
Then then you're not seeing our friendship. Okay. Well, I know you don't have to prove it to me
I know I know it's there and it's like I know we can talk we can talk
like that. I'm I'm I'm a grown ass woman and I just I'm I'm not I'm not as man so you can
talk to me on the other side you expect size to prove your he's friendship to you. No I don't
no I don't but I point out examples to him of why I won't do it because many a times he'll sit there
and and let shit go.
And won't do anything many of time. That's why we're in the situation
Summer you know what you know what I will it's when if you were to like say hey, you know get that person off
Like if they go to a point, I always but you want me to do it when when whenever
Because I would why would I do that whenever not whenever not whenever but it's like this is your panel
I shouldn't have to tell you when some guys threaten any girl
I'll say I hate summer Dickerson or summer like sleepy summer or something like that and then go on the panel and cut
Call with everybody
Show me a clip where I said I hate
But I said the panel was called okay, I'm not gonna go on a panel. This is I
Something negative about you and then talks everybody
Without talking about people that I've been friends with for years, dude. I'm gonna go on my friend's panels
I don't give a shit what their title is
But I would say I participated in the part of conversation
I wanted to and that was what I was saying Jimmy is fucking weird. That was it
Yeah, I know and it's like you you really weren't bad baby. I'm sorry. You've known me by now
Ain't nobody great make me do anything. I don't want to do I've been forced to do things my whole life
I'm not gonna do shit because somebody wants me to jump through roots and ain't gonna happen wanting you
It's just about what it's about. I just just know I don't have to know
I don't have to do that because I put my friendship to you on a daily basis when I'm up here supporting you when I'm standing with you during fucking other shit
I don't get it everybody's fucking beefs
I don't expect you to take my beef son because if that's the case buckle up buttercup because I got a lot of motherfuckers on this
Internet don't like me
If I see someone but if I was okay, but I'm not talking about me in that chat
I'm gonna or you in that chat what I'm saying is like I will have your back and especially if you call out to me
I will have your back, okay, and then it's like just like no question
It's like I'm not even just have your back. It's like, you know, at least I like
It don't matter what you would do is what you have done.
It's not about me, it's not about what you're expecting out of you.
I'm just saying I will do that for you and I'm not asking you to do anything for me.
I'm just saying I will have your back and I care about you more than you probably think.
And so I don't want to upset you or you know hurt your, I don't want other people to either.
I just think that you, I know that you're so strong.
You're acting like that I'm just this way with you psyche and I'm not, I'm not.
Uh-huh. There's all kinds of people around me that got beef going on and I'm not in they should
Yeah, I'm just not
This isn't my fucking life. This is where I come for entertainment and fucking release of what I'm dealing with in the real fucker world
Uh, okay, and usually if I rip somebody apart is because they came after me
I'm not just going around her fucker with people because you got to issue Christine's got to issue Apollo's got to issue smash
I don't do that. That's not me
I beg to differ on this point.
I don't really give a shit,
because you don't even think you are part of the drama community.
And you suck at every day.
What should anyone else do?
You're in the drama community every day,
so I don't really care what your opinion is,
is what I'm saying.
You're just as insane as I am.
We all don't care about anyone's opinion then.
All right, awesome.
I don't give a fuck about anybody's opinion,
what they think.
You're either gonna like me or you're not I'm not gonna waste my time on figuring out if I'm gonna be your if you're my friend or not
You know we cool or we're not Apollo. You're just like me. You just deny it yourself. You start
Stop the insults, please. I'm not
What no no no don't compare me with you
Well, too bad set honey because you do it all the time you go from drama community to drama community
And you get right in the middle of it every fucking time because that's what you love. Yes
No
You're in denial. That's not my problem. I walk in who the fuck I am, baby
I'm a red flag walking and I don't give a fuck who like
Because you act like you don't you got banned from TPP you followed us over here
You're in every fucking chat in every goddamn conversation
And you've only been around here for a little bit so pack down young and because you just like me actually you're worse
Because you don't walk in your fucking truth
You are too
Tell the fucking truth you came from me and wanted my place, okay
Jamie's words not mine remember the fire. No, I don't remember you this you came at my deceased niece
Who does that seriously seek help Jamie didn't wait too much like shit like a miscarriage to never let me
grieve the loss of my knees or to her cronies to ordering stuff for her on her mom's credit card
and lying to her mom about it. She was asking the baby dad, I couldn't fucking breathe. She smothers.
I didn't have a life from her drama. I did not want to date her and she wouldn't accept no
for an answer. She was jealous over baby daddy. Oh, and you want to see
I don't know this sounds like an insane person
Yeah, I don't know. I don't know
It sounds like a lot of personal. I don't know you're talking about but like that's a lot to me
Just bring it out on it. Well, yeah, why was somebody texting me that and it's all bullshit
It's talking about mentally ill people being fuck. I mean Jesus Christ, and then it's like an Alex you fucking
Somebody off too. I'm sorry. I wasn't reading the chat tonight
So I'm sorry if I miss I did hear like a tiny little bit where he's talking about abortion and stuff
I don't know it was like he's very inappropriate Alex. You're in trouble. You're in big trouble
Like that's just not something topic to talk about or joke about but it you're just ridiculous dude
Like what are you doing? You're gonna that's that that that bothers me that you said that to this person
I do like Alex and so you're in trouble Alexander McQueen, okay?
Are you there? I'm telling you I'm telling you about the dude. So wait
He said something to somebody in the chat and they
Will just tell him talking about abortions and stuff like that. What the fuck Alex? I mean, come on
Don't fucking stupid
Yeah, that's this cost way too far. I assume that everyone knows that but not everyone take him seriously. Don't think Alex seriously. He is a
lunatic
I mean it's just it's just to laugh at okay don't think Alex here. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
That's bullshit now. Okay, seriously
That's that's not jokes. That's not fun. It's not funny
But it's like but just laugh at him because it's like it's just like
It's so ridiculous that it's like it can't no one can think it's seriously if you think it's seriously or think I adore
So I mean that's ridiculous. Alex. You're in trouble. I know you're here
Alex you pissed somebody off that I cared about that's not good
Yeah, wait, you realize that we've all had that same approach with Alex. Well, I know but
But I can I can I know you have to stop me in the back side. I don't know
No, no more power than any of us. I don't
Get them and take your wrench Alex, okay, that's that's not power
You're gonna lose that wrench, okay, you're not and you're not a managing mod by
Okay, Alex, but I will I will un-wrench you and then I will let anybody that wants to kick you out
Do not talk about
You know, personal things like that again. Okay. We're like, you know, and don't talk to someone like that again. And I hated that. Stop it. And not only summer, everyone, everyone, but he's been personal with her, he's been personal with her and that is something special.
I'm
Fortunately, yes, you are a follow. You're very special
Yeah, my helmet and everything sweetie, I'm gonna I'm gonna
I got a paddle
You're more like me than you are a client, but you are a follow. I mean, I'm gonna discipline him if you
I have more or I have more online
Got more different
Not all this motherfucker you don't you start the shit. Yeah, you love it you love it
So like I said
Did I ever attacked your your children? I
Haven't attacked your children. What the fuck are you talking about? Oh?
Yes, I mean what somebody else is no, I have not attacked your children
You but prove it
i don't even know your fucking children so you better try again homie
now what i have made fun about is your fucking fat cricket ass i right here
that's what i make fun about you on a daily basis show it show it show it thank you
well that looks like a fucking gross fucking vagina there we go yeah he's got a pussy face
Well, imagine having a whole family of slave groups, 12 people of summer school saying they want to fuck my children, my daughters, my kids, my mother.
First of all, somebody says that to you and that's what they do with me.
That's what they do with me, that's what they do with me.
You and Chris have nothing to do with me, pussy.
Yes, it does and you and Chris is responsible for what he says to you and he owns what he has said to you.
So what Chris says to you and you fuck with him all the time, you fuck with him, you fuck with him all the time.
Your kids are grown first of all.
about. Second of all, I'm not
with him. It's not. I don't
talk about you or what you're
talking about because it's not
about me. I don't talk about
you. I don't talk about you.
I don't talk about you. I don't
talk about you. I don't talk
about you. I don't talk about
you. I don't talk about you. I
don't talk about you. I don't
talk about you. I don't talk
But she's not mad at crystal. She's not mad at crystal dumbass. She's upset with Psyche
Listen, you fucking idiot. Why? Why he didn't say
I'm sorry. You're slow ass
Welcome to the drama community
These go for both sides. You can't pick a choose
But guess what? Welcome to the drama community
Why don't you say all this to Chris?
Why don't you say something to them?
Pussy face.
You attacked me for something someone else said.
He didn't say anything to Christine.
Pussy face.
But see they didn't say anything you don't know why they're upset so say the fuck out of it ain't your goddamn business
I wasn't attacking psyche me and psyche. We're having a conversation. So shut the fuck up pussy face
Hey
You like it with Jenny
I don't get what you're talking about, because you're no better than anybody else.
You take your own ass with your oxygen tank and sit there and do whatever you want.
You're a pussy face.
Pussy face.
Because your beef is with me. Your beef is with Chris.
I don't have to repeat nothing, oh man.
Keep the fuck up.
You do.
From the back.
It's 8 30 in the morning. I'm good. So anyway smash. How are you doing smash anyway?
Why people attacking people someone you didn't say doing a okay me too
People oh, I love your face. I'm here to support you
We love you, and then you're responsible for what Chris said, but he's not responsible for what Harry said.
And talking all this shit about the people, all this shit about...
Why don't you tell everybody why you got kicked off TPP?
Why'd you get kicked off TPP?
Why'd you get kicked off TPP for trash?
Why do you get kicked off TPP?
The same reason you care.
I'm very okay in there, as far as I know.
Why did you see that actually I've got locked either I just don't go this at all
Okay, I don't see what you do why you
You care
You try to manipulate
Manipulating
Manipulating witches
Back for me, Hyena
Okay, if I could say right idiot
I mean idiot. Yep. I I accept it
Your blood pressure up you better calm down now. We don't want to get that blood pressure up, sir
Yeah, don't worry about mine. Oh
So scared
I haven't heard the
We care about you so much Apollo we don't want that blood pressure get up
I love you Apollo
Okay, do we don't biggie boo I love you Apollo. I love you stop it stop it
Give me some kisses. Come here old man.
What's wrong with you?
Apollo, come here.
I want some kisses for you.
Apollo, I think you're so hot.
You know these bulls all over the place, right?
When you sit on Apollo's face, it's a whole different ball game
that pussy-face is.
Sexy man.
How you doing, Apollo?
Two pussies grinding, though.
That might as well be a scissor.
Poller.
Scissor on Apollo's face.
Out one.
Dumbass.
You little puppet.
I thought you are.
Hey, I can, I can give you a, a polo, a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you a polo, let me give you
So, Smesh, you're always for conversations, okay, let's have a conversation.
Yeah, let's have a conversation.
That's what smash all the same. Oh, I only jump it's to have a conversation. It's all he's doing
Paulo he's so cute
Up here whose eyes that I'm at the screenshot that
It's not put the other pin off to put the other one on the screen that I and next time you got a line
Apollo when you come up and I won't put this shit on the summer jam screen. I'm a screenshot that
You got a roast I your I caught like a 12-gay shotgun
You know fucking you like be both of Friday. You got the both of Friday's eyes man
Force Whitaker I
Me got a muppet I
Motherfucker, your eye look like the bottom, your eye look like the bottom of my foot, motherfucker.
That long ass eyebrow you got.
Mm-hmm.
That's like one of those golf eyes. I was holding one eye. It's a ball game. We're around there.
It's just gonna go in.
That shit don't even look real on this. That shit don't even look real. It should look like it.
You got an AI. You got a motherfucker. You got a computer generated eye.
Funny face, motherfucker.
I think you know that thing stinks
Shit, then they got asked my like short shit
Then they got like the like the like the back of a fat girl's neck under under her belly on a hot summer day
That niggas I smell like motherfucking battery acid and hot dog water
Then they guys like under boo sweat on a fact that nigga I smell like the back
I think I smell like hola toes is bad breath and all and they can get a bad breath
I think I had his whole face think leather face ass nigga from motherfucking texture chainsaw masculine
That's that all seen on the back of the dollar bill
I think God misplaced the belly button on like in a jiffy belly button. I asked him
He got a walk like an Egyptian. He got an Egyptian on Horus. I asked me
They disconnected the umbilical cord from his head
My money to cover Draco a man cover Draco, man. That's my nigga Rick man. Come up here, man
Papa Draco, that's my dog. I brought him over there to the to the sector over. That's my dog
He from me from my side over there. This was what we do. We roast niggas now
Well, I ain't with the girl. All right, you know, I'm on my roach. I'm a cookie. I'm a roach
You don't get trolled and roasted
for
that
And he got he got all you got fucking a whole rainbow
You got black around that I like damn, dude
Well if you turn that shit to the side it really does look like a pussy. Oh, yeah, the word cover. I might go a lot later on, bro
If I'm awake, I'll catch it. Are you you supposed you something my channel smash? Yeah
Only see you in the chat. I gave you a wrench on us. I think I see you in the chat a couple times. Yeah, I
Mean I'm trying to comment about your arcade room. Oh, yeah. Yeah, I'm trying to think who's who be on my panel that can come over here
I think
Bronzeberg and been up there
Who else done been on my pen this from over here?
Okay, the auto rotate off on your phone and you turn your phone to the side you spray you're looking like a vagina
That nigga I look crazy nigga out like a asshole
God damn
Bro, how you got puckered eye?
He got the eye only a mom could love only a great auntie could love
20 face any guy like a funny people's or nothing. God damn, bro. What the hell?
Where the hell is your eyeball, bro?
We're probably a problem done Bromelia. I know you probably like you probably want to kill true
It's on bro. So I'm a Leo. I just want to come up here and get that off
And I think he hooks up breathing apparatus. So he's on up to his eyeball
Breeding which he hooked up to is he really hooked up to a machine? Yeah, he's hooked up to a machine, bro
Then they go round around with a nuclear weapon on the ground around a motherfucking bar first wife first was talking to him
He constantly heard that thing on
In the back
I'm saying Apollo bro. I ain't you know, it's all
I had to get that screen shot
of the
You said you're arguing with someone
Don't don't call ice my buddy. I get five on it buddy buddy. Please. No, don't take it buddy
Take me back to take me back to the chicken shake buddy
Come on up Alex. It's safe up here. I think
Now let's just show a rat ass up when you when they want when it went when we motherfucking need help they put not the back
Sitting up they put the rat sitting on this guy rat man. Do num do num do num do num do num do num
I'm a rat cape on motherfucker made a rat fur. Haha. You bitch ass nigga
Sort of Alex has the skinniest fucking arms I've ever seen on the internet man
You a Patrick in why just like my name is like these arms look huge
Like he's got some skinny ass fucking crack at arms. I saw him on fucking camera one time
But I was going to a Patrick in why I just take my name and just put truths on productions in the search engine
And I pull up and just subtract my channel man. Appreciate that
He's awesome channel boy. You're gonna hear a lot of jokes man. You come over there, man
You're gonna hear a lot of jokes man. You ain't gonna hear nothing like these crybaby ass niggas over here
These niggas over here be crying all the goddamn time. We don't want a nigga tired of hearing that shit
They ain't always Joseph they talked about some real shit over there. Yeah, they do it
Crying is you through some at the moment. I'm not here crying is you
Why did that?
Detect me the first buddy. I didn't say wrong buddy. Why did you call ice buddy?
Why did the fed bitch fall off the dog off of the ceiling and buzzer was her eggshell buddy
I don't know how to
Butter
Well here apollo talk all here is butter really just sounds like he's got butter fucking voice
Can't even close your mouth of that fucking thick-ass tongue you
Was you was low-key begging I just wanted to roast Alex. That's all
And you call a big call whatever you want, okay
What's I can go mad them out of me I don't mean something be quiet everybody I pretty quiet a summer man
What's up, man? Do you see Alex though?
Alex is big Alex is begging for for that wrench in chat. It's like, oh, I'm sorry. He's alright. I'm sorry
It's like you'll never begin the fuck got a wrench. Don't Alice got one
I was got a wrench and he was like he was about to take it out. I was like, I'm sorry. He's like
Now I ain't cash that he was begging in the chest for a rich crying
He was crying about losing his wrench and shit. You gave or you gave the most rogue nigga a wrench and you oh that nigga
Alex roll. Oh, they got one thing I do like about Alex man
That nigga one thing I do like about him. He can't do he kind of remind me of me
He's gonna hit go on the panel go against the whole panel of niggas man. That's all they got like about him. I like that shit
I like people like that. They don't, they don't get no size, nigga. They just go, they go against the old panel. I like that.
Mine is direct, mine is the snitching, but he kind of reminds me of me.
Yeah, sometimes I get in those, those modes where I want to create waves.
But he was, he was about to lose his wrench in the chat and then...
He was practically begging for a psyche to let him keep it. I'm sorry. I'll never do it again. That's literally what he said
I'm gonna go begging for wrenches man. God damn motherfucker. Yeah, I've never known wrenches as a motherfucker, bro
I'm thinking about just doing a whole reset taking everybody's wrenches on my channel, but I ain't gonna know about that's too much work
Bro, once I if I give it I give it to you. That's too much work
The only way you get your shit taken on my channel if I see you do some flaw shit
Yeah
I originally got my wrench here last week and psyche took it within like two minutes
Yeah, I had a wrench over here for like one day. I had a wrench over this muffle
But he just gave it back to me tonight, so I'm like, all right, I guess I didn't ask for it
But all right, cool. So you can post my link. I'll give me a minute. So I'll say she's got
I'm telling y'all over on my side even though listen, I live in a predominantly white area, but my channel was mainly niggas
So all niggas over there. I'm just letting y'all I'm warning y'all before we all come over there
It's all niggas over there. I might get a few white people here and there, but it's mainly niggas
There's not for the week harder. They tell a lot of jokes over there. I'm just letting y'all know it ain't like over here
Yeah, I'll stroll into that shoe fucking flint with a fucking gas all over my clothes, bro. I don't care
Let's just don't bother me. I love roasting
I'll gas all over my clothes. I'll tell a motherfucker to throw a match
I'm here
Now Pablo you good now Apollo what's up man?
Talk to me
Now I'm done roasting right now, bro. I said
Yeah, I was away crying, you know you said what he was away crying. I was away crying
Man, he was away trying to catch your breath
Yes, you can breathe
You said eyes those tears weren't rolling down a sheet. They're just like and he got a turn as I right here in this motherfucking picture
He got motherfucking. I'm not tearing going nowhere though
He has until his head all the way forward for the tear to leave. I would hate I would hate for you to go to jail
They take your motherfucking mugs. Yeah, they had take your moisture from the back. They start turning around
We want to see your face turn around this
Take a picture. You got the face only a motherfucking great great great great grandmother could love motherfucking
You ever seen those eyescanners?
especially
this can't discount that I that should have to fucking zoom out that nigga he'd like he's like mr. Potato here
Then nigga that niggas that nigga lips nose and eyes is glued on his face and they get shitting this shit if he caught
Can I do it that eyeballs definitely secure?
But did can you have one sentence without saying but did I sounded like a motherfucking teller?
Are alien you sound meaning from this goddamn plan
So I'm planning that to do like a alien in this motherfucking picture. He sounds like holy moly from mr. Friday from this Friday
Holy moly done that shot. Yeah, buddy. I have flies on the dough next buddy. Do you sit two for one buddy?
You buy two done
I bet your house
You like you own one of them goddamn corner stores some quickie markets
You know indians will be on them quickie markets smell like underarms white castles and cheeseburgers. Yo, I bet your house stank
It don't stink your house stank. Yo house smell like motherfucking your house money speaker cords
Yo, I smell like a fucking prostitute. Yo, I smell like a prostitute
Yo, that's my like after sex with two between two thousand pound niggas. Yo, how smell like shark shit?
Yo, how smell like straight dookie? Yo, how smell like motherfucking feet?
Yo, how smell like a JV locker room nigga? Yo, how smell like a unclean motherfucking rug?
Yo, how smell like dog shit nigga? Yo, how smell like a stank ass nasty ass little box?
Yo, how smell like a fat bitches king of roof house? Yo, how smell like under my couch nigga?
Even though my couch is clean nigga. Yo, how smell like a motherfucking
Babies diaper that ain't been changed in which nigga
Like your house smell deplorable if I walked in your house
I would have to come in with a hazmat suit on fuck nigga
I'll have to put on 10 COVID masks smell your house your house smell like ass cheeks bologna and cabbage
Damn
Come on a power that nigga has my like cheese curves without the motherfucking without the mirror never sells
Then they got a smell like donkey bro, then they got a smell like
Don't you
Then they got how smell like a monkey's paws then they got how smell like man that nigga smell like a nigga get halitosis on his skin
Then they get
That's what it's about right there look
But through some say to me
I'm gonna talk you know, but she just but the truth will say it's your fault
Who want to be next man, I'm trying to roll somebody
Logic the same Christine logic
You say who?
You say who are you in all?
Mike Jones
who
Nigga who your eye nigga
What's that? That's not nice man. It's just man. It's I need a has more man. Yeah, I need a whole motherfucking has
Man, I gotta be I gotta be like bubble boy. I gotta fucking put it on a motherfucking a stank
Fuck a bulletproof vest. I gotta put on a stank vest
Talk about Christine and fuck that old-ass Christine. She don't like me
Whoa
They're gonna attack people what you say I don't give a fuck she was up here
I cook her as I ain't gonna do it why she ain't up here. I roast her as if she was up here to me
No, no, no, no
No one is allowed to attack Christine. No, I roast you. I don't give a fuck. I do what I want to do
And all of them think they are half way intelligence
I already know Christine J. J. Christine is Jacob Rinson. She that's she had behind that account cuz she never fucking
Comment in my chest. I said, what the fuck is this Jacob Rinson dude comment on my channel
So that's Christine doing that high behind that account right there
Damn Christine you you can come in if that's really you you can come in under your real account on my channel
It's all good. I might roast you for a little bit, but you know, it's all good
They're probably gonna be quiet now man. God damn. I don't want to be a panel killer
We're listening to you. You're the master of cooking keep cooking
Guys, I'm not trying to finish this this website
Do you sign up? There's a free version of it. You get there's free
I don't know I think but it will help me out with that with credit
So I can finish the site because it works by credit
I'll get some but I think it's a few sign up for free
It'll give me some if you could sign up for that
That'd be awesome because I ran under credits and I spent a lot of money trying to finish this website. So
That would really help me just free sign up
Appreciate it. How's everyone doing? I'll start to say as long as I can we have a nice panel going me. I'll get on camera. Hold on
There's not gonna be there's not gonna be a speedo show, you know, it's like I don't know if you guys wanted or not
No, I'm good. You say you about to do what now
Nothing nothing nothing you know me. Hey, okay, so let me see
Christine look at 300 years old Christine the light tail from the motherfucking crib
That's you know, that's the oldest woman ever live nigga. She 400 years old nigga. She a prehistoric dinosaur motherfuckers
They don't put her bones in the motherfucking museum nigga
They gonna attack you please for what?
I want all the smoke that bitch are like a doom a la abla got the
Brain
The double standards are amazing
That bitch is like a cracker die with no teeth. She's like a baby dinosaur with motherfucking
Creep monster they found her ass. Oh, yeah, this is she wasn't even born
They just found her a guy that's like, oh, yeah, she's already grown. She was born
She's already 200 years old and she looked 200 years old at one years old
That's a prehistoric that's a prehistoric witch that wrote on a motherfucking broom
She was his name from Harry Potter. She that teacher from Harry from Hogwarts riding around on with brooms and shit
Okay
Hey, Paula your eye you got a baby goat eye motherfucker. You got a motherfucking you do I you got a fucking you got a
Got a ninja turtle eye. You put you got to put on a mask nigga. You like a mask of Zahru
Apollo
If I didn't know that was human I would already think that's a mask
Remember
I'm gonna talk to you
I'm not hating I'm just throwing jokes. I don't hate any of these people man
I don't mean her was good at one time. She got mad at me. I don't give a fuck
But we put say on this banner we don't know what you get man. I don't care why she mad right now
I don't give a fuck. I don't hate nobody. I don't have no hate towards that lady
You're here like come on panel like let's suck it out. Okay, there's just jokes man. It's all it is man. Yeah, damn
If you're here, get on the panel and I'll talk to you.
I mean, I don't know if it's the right person.
Is it?
I don't know.
I'm already experiencing like a lot of shit today.
It must be a time of, I don't know.
He's here to take the jokes.
Well, okay, when she pulled up, I'll do it then.
If I catch on money for a two-hole panel,
I'll do it over there then.
I ain't got what y'all want.
Y'all gonna start crying.
He isn't here, don't you?
Don't talk about our dinosaur that we got in the museum.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
It is not a dinosaur.
Come on, leave her alone.
Hold on. Let's see. I'm just kidding. Okay. I'm gonna be getting the bad again again. Oh, here I am
Wow
Let's see. Yes. It's I don't know. She's not here. Okay. She's not there. Is that is she Nora?
Is that her?
Christine is that are you Nora? I think she's Nora because I remember Nora was trolling last night in a Christine kind of style
But I don't know for sure
So a brainstorm, okay, is anybody
I don't know guys. I'm about to if someone wants to someone wants me to go longer
I'll stay tonight for another
Eight minutes
Unless someone sponsors, and then I will stay longer, but otherwise I'll wrap it up
Yep catch up nice conversation smash. I enjoy I enjoyed the conversation
Yeah, wonderful
Or else, yeah.
We'll see.
You haven't even tried me on a subject?
I know.
I can't, uh.
Try me on a subject sometime.
And oh, OK, look, everyone's running.
OK, thank you.
Oh, oh, wow.
OK, let's see.
Well, I don't know.
It's been crazy.
OK, so everyone's running off the panel.
Smash is you and me
Yeah, I will say I will say thanks for thanks for on bad me
And me alone for three days moment imagine what's gonna happen in the next three days as animal queen has three days off straight
Okay, what do you need say come watch talk to me
And you need it. Well, you know, I spent a lot trying to get this website done and give me a number dick
I don't need the bullshit. Just how much? Oh
Whatever you're comfortable with whatever you're comfortable with I don't want to like to ask too much
And so it's like I don't and I don't know your budget. And so whatever you're comfortable with and I would really appreciate it
Little bit. How much do these credits cost though? Like I mean, well, I don't know
Well, it's okay. So it's a site called MapManus and it like does like a lot of the the coding and stuff like that
Which is really hard to do and so I first I bought like the $20 membership then I upgraded to the $40 membership
and then I bought
Credits twice and that's another $20 per credit pack. And so I spent $80 on it so far
and then kind of that was my
food budget but
But anything anything I appreciate and I appreciate you
Um, and I appreciate everybody and uh, thank you
And I'll keep the show on longer
and I will uh, hold on. Let me take a take down my my uh
I'm just kind of coming in in the bad again. I'm coming out of the bad again. Let me see
Okay, I'll turn it off. Um, yeah, there we go
Okay, how does that look and Alex?
Sorry, that's embarrassed. I'm embarrassed
But yeah, oh my gosh, this wasn't it was a pretty crazy day fun. It's fun
Yeah, oh Alex do you want another I need to write Alex another song did I write you a song?
You're you have the page song. I don't need to write Alex's own song. I think Alex gets his own song
It's gonna be called
It's gonna be called that night. He pulled me over that night. He pulled me over you took me to the car
That's like bent you over
Also, if anybody does, you know, if you have like a if you have a channel and stuff like that
I will definitely give you a lifetime on the website. You know if you help me out right now
And so I mean I am way too busy to do channels. It's it's okay, but well, you know also or if you want
Anybody wants coaching or reading or something like that a personal reading like on the over the phone or zoom. I have zoom and I will do like
you know
as long as you as long as you want on the on the zoom call, you know, and I
Know, you know, I mean, I'm here every day, you know, I'm not I'm not gonna
Not gonna just like
Leave you anybody anybody unhappy or anything like that. I'm gonna make sure everybody feels
Like
Fair exchange
But I'm gonna I'll keep it going longer though. Okay, let me see. Yeah, I do have my so this is this is my actual
This is like a rich, huh? This sash I have this is a
I think I'm a few years ago. How are you gonna see it?
There you go. It's pretty cool. It goes like this see
It goes over. Oh
Goes over my my priest outfit. Oh
Alex is just you I think we're alone now. Did I scare everybody away? What happened?
Why does everyone like leave it once when I like start talking? It's me. It's me, bro. It's not you. Oh
Well, it's gotta be me my man. I love you
well
Alex, you know what?
But no matter what
You're gonna access the calm out of my cock. You're gonna fuck it
Microphone a little bit can carry my good little bit, but I just a little bit cuz it's like it's a blaring in my ear
But I do want to tell you
Alex I
Know you're a real friend. I know you are okay, yeah, and you've proven that
And I know, wow, you went too far.
Someone that I really care about got really upset tonight
and they texted me that I'm never coming back.
Are you serious rain got that upset over that? No, it wasn't rain. It wasn't rain
It was somebody else that and I say I and I feel really really bad
Oh the guy the guy that came up that old man
And and also there's others someone texted me that was actually like I don't I never see them they never talk
Shit well, okay
Let's see. What are we gonna play? Can I make a new video?
Good
She's a work of art, she's playful and she's funny
This is Lilith Scorpiana and you're watching Psyche Awakens TV.
Psyche Awakens TV is a portal to the shadows of the soul where truth burns through illusion
and transformation demands courage.
Psyche rips open the veil of the soul, dragging you into the abyss where raw truth claws at
your core and transformation devours all fear.
It's a relentless plunge into that only the brave emerge reborn.
Enjoy!
Flesh and sky the vision now
Steady beam guiding from the shore
came a storm on wheels rolling in smooth with the mafia feels
Cuban cigar lit like it's temper, pizza in one hand
hot dog for dinner said psyche I'm bored had to switch the scene
left some poor woman screaming on live stream
trolled her down to the void and back then crashed my show like a heart attack
gotty made me
But we friends, forever my friend
He thinks he's God with the lowercase G in a wheelchair still stomping through the live feed
Bout of your king while smoking that leaf Laughing at chaos like it's comic relief
Brought spunky two now that trolls a gem Mean one sweet ones they all jumped in
Cameras glitch and chat on fire
Mott's begging me to cut the wire
But nah, I like my circus, I love this mess
Every troll's just a test of a mess
But we friends forever my friend you called me a fraud then defended my clown
Spam my chat then held it down
You got layers like a deep dish slice
under all that shade a
Heart made of ice and maybe rice so let's light that cigar
another night of chaos welcome to psych you brought the drama the heat fun and
weirdly it feels like you're the one got it yeah you crazy but your family now
rolling through fire still taking a bow no matter the madness no matter the
weather but we stick together
What's wrong, babe? Hi, babe.
One second.
Oh, excuse me. I'm so sorry.
can't see.
Tattoos that tell her days
Long hair flowing like a river's been
Sweet summer Dickerson, everybody's friend
Sweet summer, wild and free
Mother of ten with a heart that can see
Birth seven stars, let her love shine through
hold you true she walks the back streets where shadows fall helping lost souls
who thought they'd lost it all prostitutes addicts she takes their hand
Thank you.
I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done, I'm done
brand new don't leave guys please stop leaving where you're leading me don't leave me
I'm gonna delete all the beat of biscuits on okay let's see it for the first time
the premiere of the cult of psyche it's a cult of one really I can't get anyone
to join it maybe Alex wants you but
Okay, that was the wrong song, that was the wrong song.
I accidentally made that one, I'm sorry.
It was another song, that was based on my Vedic Astrology.
Let's see how we're doing it.
Okay, so making it, okay.
How about, oh, let's see the fish taco song.
But the night was wild, the cards were true.
Well, Psyche's in his speedo. Stars and stripes parade. Fish tacos on the table. Another wild charade.
He's hitting on straight men. Come on, lose that shirt. Meanwhile, Vita's on the hotline. Yell until it hurts.
Pretty pages dodging simps. Like dodgeball in the gym.
Man at a drag got gonged off, didn't even swim
Summer spunky Marcy flashing, chaos on the feed
And here comes a porn bomb, oh lord
He's purring.
Christine's with Fuzzy Bear.
Arthur's stirring pots, like he's cooking up a scare.
Truckerado rumbles in, salmon's chasing views.
DJ Electra's cartoon face is breaking all the rules.
Piranha's got the trolling.
We've gone too far. We've turned the trolls into our own memes.
Welcome to the show, where every wild night becomes another end.
I have one more. I just want more. I was gonna play the song. I just did
We're fine. Oh no, I'm sorry.
Ah!
Where is it?
It's all fine now.
Sorry. Sorry.
I don't charge anything for anybody.
I don't know what you're talking about.
That's what I call donations,
because it's dough, and we're in a nation.
Okay, I put on my, like,
guys, you wanna see how I put my waist to this phone?
Oh, you're charging McQueen for your ear pin.
Yeah, well, just you have to see a,
you have to go to one of those hearing doctors
and take a little test.
Oh my gosh.
I'm a priest, am I?
I can show you my like priest license if you want.
Why is it so bright?
I hear it like, oh my God, there we go.
Ooh, look, I'm in the Vatican.
Kinda.
Do you wanna see the picture?
I'll find the picture of my uncle
giving the gift to the Pope.
Hold on a second.
Hi, babe
So my dad had a brother he was like my dad always told me about his brother he was like this genius, right?
He actually was his half-brother my dad's mom was married to this other man and
They were in a canoe accident the canoe overturned and the father died and that was like in some other state
So my aunt moved or my grandmother moved out here, right?
And, and do I see it?
Ooh, I haven't seen those pictures.
Okay, anyway, I know it's full name, hold on.
Anyway, they moved out here,
and then it's like, the guy was like 10 years older.
He didn't really like my,
I don't know why he didn't really like his,
like his little brothers, his half brothers.
You know, which is kind of sad, but.
Because you know it having the little brothers when you're growing up that much younger. Let me see obituary. It's an obituary and
My dad was like he was like he was so brilliant my dad had my day everyone was really smart and
Like my uncle my other uncle was like a professor of Middlebury
Okay
Middlebury's in Vermont, right? There's a whole Wikipedia article about him too. Let me just see
Hmm. I'll find it and um, but I always heard about him always. Okay, so
Hopefully this is it
He looked a lot like my dad too
He was he was really brilliant like
It says it says his name was Howard. Okay. I won't give his last name
He was a cannon. It says the Second Vatican Council and a visit to the Archbishop Michael Ramsey to Pope John Paul VI in 1966
established a new relationship between the Anglican Communion and Roman Catholic Church, and Howard was one of the observers of the council.
A further fruit was the establishment of the Anglican Center in Rome.
Root later became its director.
So he was the director of the Anglican Center in Rome.
Wow.
He was born in Illinois.
His father died in a drowning accident a few months later after he was born.
He and his mother moved to Los Angeles.
He attended Hoover High School and after graduating from U.S.C. at 19, he became 19 years old.
That means he started at 16 or 15, right?
in college at USC. He became a teaching fellow and instructor at the American University in Cairo,
Egypt. The bishop of Cairo, Jeffrey Allen, spotted his gifts and encouraged him to study theology
at Oxford. In 1952, Allen became principal of Ripon Hall and supervised the ordination training
there. Ordained by the diocese of Eli in 1953, Eugene was the curator of Trumpington,
Between 1954 and 1966, he was the first chaplain and then dean of a manual college.
Cambridge was the center of creative theology and he contributed an essay to the book Soundings
that posed radical questions to the Church of England. His philosophical essay entitled
Beginning All Over Again called for a re-examination of the place of natural theology and the role of
the theologian and the life of the church.
The paper was based on his wild lectures, which he gave in Oxford in 1957 through 60.
They were never published in the same fate befell as 1972 Oxford-Bampton lectures.
Okay, from 1963, he was an Anglican observer at the Second Vatican Council.
He became friendly with Bishop John Moorman of Rippon and became an examining chaplain.
He also fulfilled this role in other four other dioceses.
In 1966, he was seen as a rising academic star who's appointed the new Chair of Theology
at University of Southampton with the expectation that he would build up a theological faculty
of excellence.
However, he set the post as a base which he could operate a wider front.
Hmm reminds me of me. This is revealed in his extramural activities
He served in the Church of England Doctory Commission, which procured produced reports on some subscription into that 39 articles
Prayers for the dead which were submitted to this 1968 Lambeth conference in which he was consultant
He sat on the Anglican Roman Catholic Preparatory Commission
6768 this produces a series of agreements on the Eucharist and the ministry
He was involved in setting up the Euclid Medical Institute
at Tontour, New Jerusalem.
This brought together students and theologians
from many churches to foster eucanical understanding.
He was a frequent visitor and lecturer for years.
OK, so what the fuck?
I mean, it's like, wow.
So I have an uncle that was really brilliant.
I just want to find his picture.
There's a great picture.
I do have it on my tablet.
I have it on my tablet.
I know I do.
because I had the favorites. So I'll show you. He looks like my dad a lot, especially my dad when
he was younger. He's a good-looking guy and he's with a Pope. So I have this picture. Let me see.
Photos. Okay, there we go. Google Photos. Favorites. Let's see. Hi. Okay.
Here's the favorite section collections favorites
There he is okay, so hold on I'll show you just to show I'm not a bullshitter guys
There he is
We for madness we for madness there is the pope presenting a birthday gift you're singing
Elf had a movie. Oh, yeah. Elf was a movie
Whoo, I am sweating. I'm hot under the collar
Michael Cain me perhaps perhaps
Okay
You're in the shower you're saying you're in the shower typing and listening to the radio
Okay, I have a guy from Nigeria trying to call me all night. Oh my god. I'm not gonna take a call from Nigeria
I mean, I just like I love Nigerians
Some of them are cute, but I'm just pretty many it's scammed
Whoo, please don't bring up showers. You're still scared from waffle stomping. Oh my god
It's a hard work doing the Lord's work. It is very hard work. Gosh
It is oh my god
Wish I had like these are my legs. They're so skinny
Right
Just oh my god, I'm just a good rabbit
They're they nice into my hair. So my legs don't have any hairs on my side my hair. So oh my god
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry, but it was just a flag. I'm wearing the flag as a
That was spiky. They're spiky or sick spike. Yeah
Yeah, that was me in the Pope you oh, I shout I take a bath once a day and I wash really really good
with the, let's see, how black chicken soap.
Oh my gosh.
Psyche, Psyche.
Am I crazy?
I don't know if I'm crazy.
Guys, I only had like, I'm only,
I had to go back and I have a beer left.
I only had one other one.
Hey, look, it's called Smash.
It's called Smash.
Oh my gosh, it must be green there, it's yellow,
but that is good enough with the camera.
Trippy, huh?
Okay, I am patriotic. Oh
My god, I'm so sorry. That was what am I? What am I doing? I don't know. I'm so weird. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry
What what would you say?
The shiny chicken AI image. It was funny. I
Don't know why he's so upset. I think he even liked the song though. He was like, oh wow. It was like
Kind of funny
Maybe I'm not such a bad guy after all
Sorry duck lips
Through the chaos of I'm so true. That's all because of every single one of you
My sweetheart Persian Queen
Delight with your laughs so loud
You light up tonight. Sorry. That was me page with the heart and the jokes that land
Blonde bombshell with a beer in
We don't want to flop, now we laugh, we read, and we climb to the top, so thank you for the chats, the laughs, the love
For the super chats, rain, and I'm sorry
More like sprinkling a little bit, but whatever
You're seeing crystal. How'd I know that?
I'll be the song
packages of spy
Hey, good morning
I'm just going crazy. I'm sorry. It's okay. I just I just looked at your show. No, I I'm going crazy
I woke up today to a bunch of angry comments emails direct messages stemming from this
Q situation and
All I did was recap a couple videos and give my commentary. It's not like I was in the situation
And this woman who's involved, I've never even heard of her, but I had to put out my angry statements already this morning, so I've been up for about an hour.
Why are they mad? Because everyone wants to villainize Q right now. And on one hand, justifiably, because he can be horrible.
I've always seen within him that he's trying, okay?
He has come at me in the worst of the ways,
but I forgive him because he's gone through
some really, really, really major things in his life.
Right.
and I know that too and also you know it was it it was bad but you know you can tell a second later
he's like god forgive me right it's like he he has a hard time controlling his temper that's
what it is and he has a very like limited filter um he says exactly what's on his mind it's to his
You know hoped that he would figure his life out and you know, I
Just don't think that he is lying
Completely in this situation
He put out this public statement saying he lied about two elements of what he
talked about
having gone through with this living situation that he was in but he didn't say he was lying about everything and I mean
I was surprised to have even
gotten any feedback in
regards to what I said about
The videos because that was like an impromptu
sort of little recap
But I don't think that he's lying
I just don't. I think that this is a situation to where you have some people doing something that they shouldn't be doing and he does have a big mouth.
So.
Yeah, and I mean, I agree. I mean, it's like, we've always been cute. When I met him, you know, he said something kind of horrible to me, but then I just like, you know, I still liked him. I still like thought he was like, redeemable.
He is and a lot of a lot of us can be sometimes, you know, because we
Is very complex beings and it's like we're not all just one thing we can be pushed to different
Air the different parts of our room our brain our mind. We have reactions. We're triggered
we lash out sometimes and
He definitely lashed out and it's you know, I thought he would be a little bit more forgiven for it, you know, but
There's something going on because I've never heard of this woman that he was
Living in the home of all this time. I I've never heard of her before
BB
But I it was this woman named BB though, I never heard of her I've never heard of her and
The only person I tagged in my commentaries was Q because I know his YouTube channel
I don't know what her youtube channel is or if she has a youtube channel or anything
So how would she have even found my commentary that quick?
Unless like she's like looking to see what anyone and everyone is saying about q
So in the way that she pulled up on him and that little truck that was crazy. That was weird like how
I was like I was like that's like a one in a million chance of like knowing exactly where the I guess I guess
There's like a tent city there that everyone knows about in the area or something. I
I thought he was standing on a bus stop
But that was weird and just she looked crazed. I don't care. So whoever this VB person is
I have not said whatever her name is nothing
Okay, there's no reason for her to be coming at me
when I'm not the one who put together the montage
of what happened.
I didn't even know everything that I'm glad I know now
because I don't think that
he's being treated fairly in this.
I just don't.
I think that he did witness a bunch of meth
and no one wants to talk about that, but.
Yeah, well, I know it's like those.
Tensities are just full of drugs and it's like that's how a lot of people end up in a tent city, too
It's like we used to have them all around under the bridges usually and then that's where people would go to buy the drugs
You know, they go into the bridge and then they talk to somebody there and
That's a huge source of their income. You know, it's like and then like the drug dealer there is like a celebrity in the community kind of and
but
I mean, that's he named the dealer, okay, or at least the dealer's alias and
Yeah, yeah, so I mean he didn't see he only apologized for two things in that post and people are like, oh
That's a pretty minuscule apology.
He just noted two specific things.
He did not retract everything that he said
and he shouldn't if he was being honest
about what he dealt with
because I think that they're trying to put him on that.
Well, I know it's like, I think everyone there,
he said that they just are all doing it all the time
in that area, right?
Um, I guess it's like that's how they pass the time and it probably eases the pain a little bit
You know, it's not an easy life
Living in a tent on the side of like a city road and the you were right when you said
You know a lot of those people were like probably very like a lot older than him had been there for a long time and then here
Yeah, I'm good looking guy that has like he's going to a job and it's like he's all they can just see he's like his potential right
Yeah, he's not dumb. He's a smart person
he's
He's just been dealt honestly a bad hand. That's why I think that would be good for him to go into the military
Just like leave all this behind
Join the army have a career in there then you can get out and get
Other really good jobs and you know you get all the benefits and he should do that
You know because he's he's not doing anything right now to where it you know
it seems really productive or anything
and he's gonna end up in trouble or end up in jail.
You know what is my, like the thing
that kind of wore my heart is that
after that whole horrible situation,
which was pretty horrible, right?
But he like, the first person you ran into
was looked like a drag queen,
like, you know, in front of some sex shop.
And this was like his friend, like this is like,
he's like, hey, Michael, he had a big smile on his face
and they're taking pictures and stuff.
And it's like,
He's not like a hateful person. I mean, it's like he's not like oh my god
It gave her he's like he this was his probably he probably hung out with this guy and stuff and
Was cool with them and stuff and the guy likes him and it kind of wore my heart a little bit. It's just seemed like
There's just seemed like a lot of stuff going on there and can you imagine how difficult to be on this like, you know, I know
I mean, I didn't when he was telling about what happened to him. I was like
You know, he he he was downplaying the magnitude of what he's been going through
So
And yeah, Alexander McQueen. I said minuscule. I haven't used that word in a while. I had the opportunity. I
Had to use it, but yeah, he's he's gone through a lot and
I just I just feel like
Um, you know, let the guy have his birth certificate back and whatever mail or paperwork
He he needs and just part ways and don't talk to him anymore
and you know, you know, let it be just let it be because
I don't believe that woman is innocent. No way. Sorry. Uh-uh. Yeah, I mean she didn't
look like some kind of like you know angel when she pulls up you know it's like you kind of tell
what he was saying. Get in the car! I was like no don't get in the car run run!
Hey, I don't know what would have happened if you got in that car because she had kind of like a smile on her face like
I'm feeling crazy. Yeah. Yeah
So get in the car get in the car right now right now and it's like I would have maybe run to is like
I don't know what's gonna happen in that car like especially after how they parted and stuff
I was surprised like she was that's the person to come to his rescue
Kind of seem I would be maybe suspicious if I was him too, but uh
There is something I don't know but but it looks like he hasn't like his like a different place and everything now and
I hope that she leaves him alone.
But did his parents pass away, like both of his parents?
Yes.
Yeah, and so like when he was younger,
and that was like the thing that was, you know, traded,
I don't know why he loved it exactly
and like why he didn't take that one shirt with them.
But that was maybe his father's shirt, you know,
and it's like that maybe was one of the last things
he had at the spot.
So there's a lot of stuff.
Right.
maybe making consideration of why he overreacted or and stuff like that and
you know and sometimes when people are on drugs they don't feel pain as much so hopefully that
guy didn't go through too bad of a situation but you know the guy that he sprayed but I don't know
I think that we should consider that there was some kind of
Very sentimental thing there that he felt was just traded away for something and
He last out for a second. He regretted it and I
Feel like he's living a nightmare. Oh, yeah, that would be imagine imagine just like you know, he's like
Yeah, lost his place to say he ends up on the side of like a road and I don't know what say
It was it was a Nevada or California or something. He's in California. He's in the San Bernardino area. Yeah, it's not the
Best area in the world, you know, you saw the area was like there's like the sex shop with the glory hole or something
And yeah, I wouldn't yeah. Well, I mean, that's probably where he could afford, you know
Well, yeah, but luckily he found a place to stay though
Like and he's like he's like I got lucky and like he met somebody and I
Think that there's something see I'm looking at the time frame of
how he was explaining him having the problem with this woman, VB.
He was living in this house somehow that she had access to for months by himself.
But then all of a sudden she was there and it seemed like she was like demanding a lot of his attention.
I kind of think that he was meant to be her side piece.
Yeah, well and the he-man saying that he does not speak highly about me and just leave it
I did hear that he like maybe put my father who passed away his photo up on stream one night
I didn't see any of this. I don't know for sure
He didn't say the first thing he ever said to me when I met him was
Go unalive yourself or something like that and more harsh. Yeah
I hope that he makes it because he's he doesn't have a lot of fans because he's been so horrible to
people I mean you're just another you're another example of how horrible he's been yeah I mean he
he said that he wanted to kill me he wanted to assault me I knew he didn't mean it you know
but he said it and I was like what in the fuck is wrong with you but um
I don't know. I don't know. I just, I always have felt kind of bad for him.
I know and I feel that, I mean as I feel that too and as like even no matter what, how bad people treat me sometimes it's like I try to see like
Why are they doing this? Like why like what's happened to them?
And it's like usually some kind of trauma and it's usually lashing out about something
That's not about me. That's not the truth about most people that lash out at people. It's like it's really it's not about
People that lash out at it. It's about them their own
baggage and securities or whatever so
But you know I do
I wish, I hope, I wish for him that he gets on his feet.
He...
There's there could be great things for him in life, you know, there could be it's like
But life is like a game and it's like, you know, he needs to stop streaming and stay away from people on drugs
That's that's the key just do that because
We're around will determine that and it's like if you're just in that environment
It's very hard not to get pulled into the environment you're in it's like, you know, yeah
It's it's hard, you know, it's like you when you're in pain
You're like anything to make the pain go away anything anything that will make me feel better for five minutes
Even if I feel bad after that
people just don't care so I
will just
like
I'll just postpone judgment on him
Like I'll let God take care of the judgment on him, you know, and yeah, and I think he probably has a
relationship with God that the way he was talking
Or he and I think he will be forgiven
For that I just want him to be treated fairly. That's that's it. You know because he's not an angel and
I don't want to overly defend him or anything. It's just that he is you know, I I view him as being
pretty young okay, and
Just considering how I know certain things can traumatize you
I'm amazed that he's been as resilient as he's been so
Well, yeah, so if he's out there, you know, it's like I just
You know, you can do better you can do better like I hope you've got a place to stay like and
Treat the person that helps you or treat the people that help you
With respect and well if it someone helps you
You know I mean she didn't she didn't like let him live in her place for I think nine months, and that's a long time
It is and no matter what if you know he's TVP
No, she cues him up to take stealing her dad's heck straw hat or if he trashed the place or whatever. It's like, you know
She knew he was there and ultimately we make make decisions
I mean she wanted something out of him. He needs something out of her, right?
It's like there's probably some kind of fair exchange up until it wasn't right
Um, and just, but, hope she, she can let it go and uh, yeah, I, I think he's felt really
bad about what he did and sometimes people lose control and it's, you know, he's like
in a really bad situation.
It's not, it's not fun.
One time I did like spend a night on the street with some people.
just out of
There's a weird situation, but I spend the night and I but I got to see like that
Like that life a little bit like just for that even if it was for one night and it's like not a life
I would ever want to live. It's like it's difficult and I just
Wish the best for those people and it's like, I'm you know, and if we have a place to live and we're
Relatively happy. We're lucky, you know, we're very we're blessed. Yeah, and we yeah
But how are you doing? It's so good to talk to you because we had the we had the best time last week, huh?
Yeah, I wish I I wish I could have like, you know, like
Spent like a week or something down there, but I couldn't do that
But it was cool. It was really cool. I mean I had it's it's so
You never at least with me. I've never known what to expect, you know, when it comes from meeting someone
online to offline
but you are exactly in person as you are online.
Thank you.
Yeah, you're cool, so.
You're cool too, oh my gosh.
That was fun.
I felt like I got out of my immediate element a little bit.
I kidnapped you and took you to Hollywood, and.
Oh my God, and I hadn't been in Hollywood.
Even like Hollywood's like 23 minutes away
and I haven't been there for,
You know years and years, but it was just
But it's different than it used to be. I mean like like some areas were better
but only like that touristy area that the other areas have kind of
Gone downhill. Yeah, I mean in the 80s. It was
Kind of similar and then it really cleaned up in the 90s a little bit and then it's now it's gone now. It's like a
It's got the Beverly Hills style
place and then as I walk out of that and then it's like
you know, there's like a lot of homeless people and
Poverty and the next to opulence and it's like a bit it's a big
It's an eclectic mix, but it's like too extreme of a mix now. It's extreme like very extreme. Yeah
But yeah, I did at the best time
And I didn't want to do like a similar thing to you where I went over I kind of tried tried to a little bit
but uh
I'll just say
This is a great woman. She's like, uh, and you have a huge heart and you're just
Oh easy to talk to and I don't I think we're birthday twins. We know, you know, yeah
We're kind of we're almost
We're off. Well, that's well that was like a big motivator and meeting you because I never I've never met anybody else in my life
Who has the same birthday as me?
Meaning like the month and the day
So there's definitely something to Astral. I mean, there's I've done it. There is you know, there's something to it where there is a
similar
Frequency there's like a similar like it was just like I never met somebody so easy to talk to I don't think it's like just so
Where it's just like, oh, yeah, I'm just comfortable around them instantly. That's how it was with you. So
And I know a lot of people were like, you know,
I think Sam Mann and like, who was Barry?
They're like, whoa, did you take,
did you take a shower before he's met her and stuff?
And I was like, I was like, I was like, I was like,
what?
Why would they even ask you that question?
That was, and they were on separate times,
but they, but I was at both of their first questions.
They're like, did you watch your ass?
And I was like, yeah, I was like, but I usually do, you know?
But yeah, I, I don't, I am,
I do try to like if I go out be a little bit nicer, but yeah
But I'm I am you're right. I'm a big homebody and
Just comfortable with my home and you know sometimes a little bit messy and just cuddly with my cats and stuff and
But if I seem pretty normal when it comes to your level of
You know just
Being like a normal person keeping yourself together, you know, I wouldn't say you're the neatest
Yeah, but it works for you. I mean if it was oh so horrible
It would be you know, it would look different than it looks in your
look yeah, and and I am yeah, I
I do try to I will actually I'm a lot better than I used to be and so it's like so for me. I'm like
Well, I'm doing pretty good like but it is also like being on camera every almost every day
It helps it helps me like you know
Sometimes it's like people are a little bit harsh
but it's like it does kind of shine a light on you and you're like a little I'm a little bit more aware of how I
Look and how everything looks and I want to do better
And I'll say, I'm inspired to do better
by everyone in the chat and, you know, people,
I don't know, it's like, but people that see me,
like, I know you do see me.
And it's like, and you actually met me in person as a lot,
you know, and you also wanted to meet me in person.
Very, and I've met, I've known people for a lot longer
that had no interest in meeting me in real life, right?
And you were like, like,
Wanting to if I like a person I want to meet them in person, you know, if I met them online
I don't want it just to be like I only know you online because then it makes me wonder like are they even real. I
Really you never know because people on camera can be very different that there's probably streamers that are like
Not at all like that. I'm exactly like I am like I'm all
You're the same in person as you are on the internet exactly the same
I'm very comfortable in front of the camera and I used to not be but like when I was little
I was just kind of like shy in front of the camera
But it's and I never used to like to hear myself or look at myself on camera now. I now I love it
You know, it's like good good
So I'm a I'm a I'm very that's why I do this so much. It's just so I'm very comfortable and it's like
You know, there's people that there's there's negatives that have been to it
Just like you know yesterday, which was the kind of more difficult day
But you know, then I'm just the people that do support me like
It's they shine so much brighter when I see like how negative some people can be. It's like the people that do love me
Some people I think are just looking to be negative like what I was talking about before it's like
Someone was just like watching my channel like oh, I can yell at her about this
I mean some people are looking any like any like a little like weight like any like kind of like
Cracking the anything that is what they're they're looking to like
And I show everything and so it's like of course like it's like they'll see
Oh my gosh, he has like, you know, blankets piled over his couch and I got so oh no, not blanket. I know
He's like, oh my god, like some somebody I won't mention but they're like, oh my look at his couch
There's blankets piled up on top of I'm like, well I sleep there
Those are my my blankets that I sleep on right is like it's not I mean I do have a bed
I kind of prefer the couch because I like to like, you know sit in front of the TV and yeah
I don't know it's your house
Have a blanket on their sofa or like, you know depending on where they watch TV like I'm in my bed right now
I'm just like, you know in the bed watching TV. It's comfortable
but I mean, I don't I
Think that these people are just trying to mess with your mind really. Yeah, some of them are and is like
Yeah, I would be like, oh my gosh like
If other people are participating in that I like, I would sometimes think, oh my God, they were just pretending to like me and it's because I have a lot of trauma where it comes to like some people like being fake with me or something like that and I'm kind of
can get suspicious with people and then it's like but I do feel the love to from people and so it's like and I really a little paranoia is natural.
Yeah, and I think it may be a little bit healthy because there's there's some things that are
Are not just paranoia. They're they're like, you know, they're
action, there's things that you know are possibilities with some people but
You have to choose your circle wisely, right? And yeah, keep and
But it takes time it takes time to do and you know, you got to learn lessons along the way and
all that stuff and you don't beat yourself up
when things go south.
And I know about Capricorns is like,
we're gonna get, like our, like Saturn is like the teacher
and he's like the mean teacher,
but isn't like, aren't the meanest teachers
and not at the end of the year?
You're like, wow, I learned so much here.
It's like, I mean, they really can teach you
and help you a lot.
Even the most difficult people,
We'll teach you the most about yourself and it's like and so I appreciate even the even the difficult people in life because
they probably taught me the most about myself and
That's why I can't really hate anybody because I'm like even like the worst person will be like
Like it may be like a crack to me or for me and it's like, you know, it's like and then you
You can you can but you can see yourself
And some and how they see you sometimes and it's like wow
It's always good to get a different person's perspective
Of yourself and to see yourself there's somebody else's eyes and then you see okay
Well, it's not just like me in my head all the time. It's like
You can see like there's you're like a person one person can be a million people because you're all your yeah
Yeah, you're a different person that everybody you interact with
you have another person coming in let's see mason's here mason you want to come say hi
have you met mason in person oh there he is mason yeah there he is hold on
i need to get my there we go how are you doing mason hey mason psyche what's up
does this shirt really look that bad that i can't wear it again mason you don't wear it every day
No, no, do you wear it a few times a week?
Sometimes okay, sometimes, okay
You know what you're fine. You're fine. You like that shirt, but
Get another what's wrong with it?
Nothing. What's wrong with it? What did it start out as white and blue because it looks a little bit gray now?
psyche look
As it was see it looks like it looks like the American flag got washed out a little bit, but um
You look fine. You look. Yeah. Oh wow. What's going on? There he is. Yeah. Mason is a, you're a super model, right? You look fine, Mason. Don't, don't, it is a nice shirt. Alex said it is a nice shirt, so. Yeah, I think it's a nice shirt.
We know you're walking, you're walking, you know, you know.
Psyche, look, you see me walk it, right?
Can you see me walking, Psyche?
Look.
I see me.
I see you.
Mason, you're fine.
You know.
Where's that?
Oh, that's beautiful outside.
And if you don't mind, what state is that?
It looks kind of warm is it a hot is it like that's outside so I can that's outside my window psyche
I'm looking outside my window. What state is that? What state?
What state do you live in Mason I live in Louisiana, okay cool cool
Wow. So you were here. Yeah. So, but Mason's a cool guy, but, you know, you've been a little
controversial lately, Mason. I have to say, he was hiding people in my, or you hid thing
that is you're picking on him last night. What happened? You're a model.
No psyche. No psyche. I wasn't doing that stuff on purpose. I want you to know that I wasn't
trying to make this stuff happen.
It was an accident. You had some kind of like, you're saying you were messing with them or
something. How do you know how to mess with people?
You're messing with thing that is right. No, I was just joking with him psyche. I was just like playing around with
Well, I think you're forgiven. I think you're forgiven
But uh, do you know do you know Alex Alexandra?
Yeah
Yeah, so yeah, I want you to get
If nothing else, I'm gonna get you a tambourine for Christmas or something and you need to get back on the drums
I think that drumming is good for you. I think you love drumming and it's
It's good. It's good focus for you to focus on that and so whatever it is
But you should get even if you get paint you can get a paint bucket and drumsticks
And you know it's like the thing is like psych looks like you that I used to have a drum set in a police to play drums a lot until I got rid of it
I mean, I wasn't trying to get rid of it for real though. I know but you sold it because you wanted to buy some other stuff, right?
No, I just didn't have any money psychics. I have a job at the time
So I needed some money, you know to survive and stuff like that. I need some food and other stuff, you know to survive
Okay
Well, you're you're you're a nice you're a nice guy. I think I still think you have innocent heart
but uh, and I think you're I think you're pretty intelligent too like you're because you can play music and that's
Some kind of high-tech. He also has a very good memory. Yeah, he has a almost photographic memory. So
Sometimes people are given like towns and interesting interesting areas
Oh gosh, let's see he didn't oh, so he meant things that you didn't find my channel. You were sent. What do you think about that?
Psyche, I don't know how I found your channel. I just found it. You know what? I was I mean, I don't remember how it happened
No, I didn't meet you somewhere. I mentioned I'm beat as
Mitchell and be his channel. Oh psyche. It was beat us right? That's how I found you. I think first right it was beat us first
Yeah, but how'd you find her like that's kind of just weird to just find her most of us know each other around here, sir
Psyche, Psyche, how does that all of a sudden just happen?
That's what I was going to ask too,
like how can I just find somebody to handle
and just get on somebody to handle?
I don't know, I don't know,
that's what the question I have, I wanna,
I'm interested.
That doesn't make any sense, no Psyche,
it doesn't make sense like to me and stuff.
If it doesn't make dollars, it doesn't make sense, right?
If it doesn't make what, Psyche?
It doesn't make dollars, it doesn't make sense.
I don't know, it's a bad question.
Yeah, it doesn't make sense, Psyche,
so it doesn't make dollars, right?
Right.
Well, you're you're a good you're a good guy. But uh, yeah, I'm chatting, you know, Alexander and I'm Alexandra and I met last week. You know that?
You talked to her another time I was on here with you, right?
Yep. She's really good.
So there's another time he talked to her. I was on here with you when he talked to her another time.
Yeah, it was like maybe about two weeks ago. Probably something like that.
I'm gonna get so I love you Alexander. Thank you for having me. Have a great day Mason. Have a great day psyche. Okay. Bye. Bye
Yeah
Well me son thank you so
Thank you. So is it true you want to really deal with me though? Like are you just saying I don't I don't Mason. I'm like
I'm a weirdo. I'm like
I think it's funny. I think it was funny. I think I thought it was being funny when I was saw when I was hitting on
I thought it would be funny that everyone thinks I'm weird for it
Yeah
Well come on up guys
Yeah, so but I really do think you should like try to like play the drums you want me play drums again
So I keep that's what you're trying to tell me right? I really need to get up back on drums again. Yeah
Because you know what that's like if you because you love doing that, right? Is that something you yeah, that's something
I'd like it. Yeah, that's like you that's something I do that's for my I have a talent and that's where my talent is
Yeah, I think that you should continue to do that
And so like you that's something I want to get back to doing do it
Do it Mason and but you know I was just
I'm sorry, I was trolling you a little bit because I was trolling you because I was trying to be funny
by hating on you, but I know you're a straight guy and you're gonna find a really cool woman one day,
I bet, right?
Saki so it doesn't really matter. I was gonna ask you a question doesn't really matter if I'm a mod, right?
I don't have to be a mod you don't have to know
It's like it's actually a lot of pressure to be a mod
And then you have to do like a lot of work and it doesn't pay very well
it actually pays zero and so it's basically a volunteer position and so I
Think that it's better that you're not because then you can say whatever you want like, you know
If like, you know Alexander's a mod and so he has to behave himself
Yeah, he doesn't believe but he has to behave himself and okay
Yeah, and so I want you to feel relaxed enough to just be yourself and not have to worry about
On the chat. Are you but what why are you picking on?
Thing that is a guy. Why are we why are you worried about thing that is like? Why are you? Why are you playing with him to give a?
rivalry
No, psyche. I miss no psyche. I'm cool with him. I'm his friend and stuff like I'm with doing stuff. Okay
Well, cuz he's not a mod and then so he was getting hit you were you hit him several times and that wasn't like very nice
No, psyche. No, psyche. I'm sorry. No, psyche. I'm sorry, man. I didn't mean that for real
Pretty good. Look at he he's giving you a smile. He gave you a smile. Yeah
Well smash
Smashers this close. No, I'm just kidding. But have you made some friends in my chat?
Like I'm which I whether she has to go because you know Natalie was here last night and she's a really cool
Cool chick, you know
And so and you introduced me to her and so now I made a new friend and so
Wow, it's like we never know who we're gonna meet through who and why and what but I think you're I think you're a good person
So I can tell my brother like what happened. He was playing bass, but you said you didn't want to get copyright
Issues or something like that. Yeah
Well because like about half hour after he came on after you I played his clip and it you know
He had your last name on the screen, right? But that was on here. I didn't put the name up there
It was already on his video
Um, yeah, I got two emails and it said a privacy complaint
So I don't know if it was him or if it was somebody pretending to be him or something
But I got a privacy complaint and so I was like that's interest. That's weird. I actually was so he doesn't
It does psyche like you don't know how that happened. I mean it doesn't make sense again. What's it give?
It doesn't make sense. It doesn't make sense
but
I don't think it was you I I don't really even think it was him
Maybe it was somebody that was just to saw that somebody had the last name up or something and was trying to mess with me
I don't know but that was it was weird a little bit weird
So I can't figure this out because um, I was just trying to let you see what he looked like
You talk to him about it, huh? Did you talk to him about it?
I didn't get a chance to talk to him about psyche because I don't know what happened to him
Like he doesn't talk to me like we used to talk to each other all the time
But we don't talk to each other like we used to
Your brother special
No, he moved on psyche he has a girlfriend I think or something he like his he moved on with his life and stuff like that
He moved on because he seems like he's really talented on the base
No, psyche we were like close and we were close for many years and we used to talk to each other a lot and stuff
But ever since he has his girlfriend now
He seems to like be with her and stuff and doesn't want to be he doesn't want to be like a
Didn't want to be bothered or anything like that anymore. Oh, yeah
I mean, that's what happens with guys like they meet a girlfriend and all of a sudden
They dump all their friends and they so I can what so I can you moved on right?
That's what it was right? He was gone
He moved on but you know what he shouldn't move on a hundred percent because you're his brother
He should always like love you and be able to talk to you right when did you last?
No, so I got that's what I thought but no when did you last talk to your brother?
It was like a couple years ago. It's like the last time I talked to yours. It's been years. Yeah
He doesn't like you anymore or something or he just doesn't talk. No, it's not that it just it's just he says
He says his girlfriend gets involved too much. So he doesn't have like
He can't get involved because his girlfriend tries to you know, stop him from you know
Doing what he wants to do and stuff like that
Basin your his brother and so the brother is like family and so
To hear that is yeah, but you know it's like he won't even talk to my mom
That's his family
Rebellious person. No psyche. He's been a rebellious person like he wants to rebel and stuff like that. I understand
I understand well, it's you know, it's just a little bit like she sounds like kind of controlling or
What isn't she like about you guys?
Like the, or like the fan, like, why, why does he-
Sikes, Sikes, Sikes, because my brother's girlfriend
doesn't want us to get involved with this life
because she thinks that he should have a new life
because he has her and stuff like that.
But I don't see things that would-
I know, well, you know, that always happens
when you get a girlfriend.
All of a sudden the girlfriend's running,
I'm just kidding.
Oh, gosh, you guys.
No, that can happen, that can happen, that can happen,
you know, but sometimes the girl,
Makes the guy change for the better and she's like tries to I just hope that uh
She's not like trying to keep him away from the family because I think everyone should always still love their family
You know no psyche
He does live stream sometimes and I can still chat to him in the chat though
But he doesn't like talk to me like on a normal like a daily basis like he used to
He used to talk to me on a normal basis, but not anymore
Is she like a controlling person or like like a like a little bit that she mean or she mean to you and stuff
She wants he told me what happened with her
He told me that she wants to control his life
And she doesn't want him to be back with people that he used to be with because she wants him to start a new life
That's the story he told me about it's like when I was
Even if a family
Talk to each other. There's just still is it's like your family is there there are people like that like you grew up with
there are people that you grew up around and they're always gonna be comfortable around your family and stuff and
No, thank you. No, thank you. I don't think he has a problem with me
I think it's just his girlfriend is the one that doesn't want him to get involved like with that. It's weird
I don't know
Hey, yeah, this is Mason is you just was prolific panel. Oh my gosh. Come on. Come on raining coolers
Yeah, well
You know Mason
How'd you get your name? Do you know what your name means?
Huh?
You know what your name means
My mom's my mom's the one who gave me this name psyche the name I had the Mason, you know
I mean a Mason for a name
Why'd she get what you give me Mason? What's that about?
She she told me because she saw she told me because she saw somebody on TV named Mason Capwell or something like that from a show
She watched and that's why she gave me that name because she liked it because the first son
Does anybody know what soap opera that was or was it a soap opera was that Melrose?
It was some kind of TV show
It was from a show called Mason Capwell or something like that. That's my mom to him
I've never heard of that show, but anyone heard of Mason Capwell?
This show? Okay, but okay, well that's interesting, well, you know what, that's how I got my name.
Yeah, so I guess I got my name. I asked about it. You know the Mason is a Mason. You know a Mason is like what?
That's a worker. So I get me the brick worker or a cement worker or something like that
Okay, a builder of a Mason is someone that builds something. It's like so I think there's something called a Mason or really like
The our wire into the word Mason and it's like somebody does like bricks or stones or something like that or cement
Yeah, see man
Me man, it sounds like the Beverly Hillbillies a little bit
Hey, wait, where'd you go? I don't see it. Oh my your drum. You're showing your drums like you what? Oh, you disappeared for a second
I think your camera clipped out for a second
My real name is I was told the same thing from a soap opera show. Well, my name is I
Won't say my middle name, but my name is John
And I'll say mental literature is our so I was probably named after JR my dad always called me JR from Dallas
And there's a there was a show called Dallas and so I got my name from a soap opera too
The show is called the show is Ant Barbara Mason Caldwell
There you go. So I guess you got your name from a show just like my mom got my name from a show
Yeah, because there's a show called Dallas and there's a whole storyline and it was called who shot JR
And I'm J.R., I'm J.R., you're a J.R. on your crew?
Yeah, I'm J.R., and uh, so you're M, hold on, let me think of your last name.
I pray your last name is, but what's your last, what's the first letter of your last name?
Siq, you talking about my last name?
It starts with a letter P. It's like you want me to write in a back chat?
You want me to write in a back chat?
I remember now. I remember now. It's a yeah, but you're MP. So that's like it's almost like military police or something like that
Ron is a Mason. Yeah, but it's in different Dixon than a
You're not a free Mason. Are you?
I've never heard. It's like I don't think that's what I am. I mean, I might be I don't think I am no
I'm not I don't think I am so well you probably know if you were but yeah
There's some, there's people called free Masons too, and they're builders, um, right?
Masons.
Yeah.
Are you in the Lover?
That's the thing that is.
Huh?
Are you Mason the Lover?
Yeah.
So you can say that, yeah.
You are?
So when's the last girlfriend you had?
When's the last girlfriend you had?
When is the last girlfriend you had?
It's been years ago. So I keep it like at least like it's been like seven eight about eight years
That's really how long it's been. It's like eight years. It's just had a girlfriend. Why is it that long? Don't you have tinder?
No, I don't have anything like that. It's like I don't have it. Well, you know what tinder is?
You know what that means? Yeah, it's like it. It's like a website, right? Yeah
Yeah, you should go on that and then you take a picture of yourself for this like smiling and
put on a clean shirt, and this smile on a picture,
and then it's like you'll start meeting women.
So like you said, put on a clean shirt,
like you mean a shirt that's different?
Or just take off, or just be shirtless.
Do you have a, are you like really ripped
and like have a really good time?
So like you want me to have no shirt on?
Are you serious?
Yeah, yeah.
Can you take it off?
No, I'm sorry.
So like you really want me to.
I got in big trouble because I said, I was, I was just, yeah, you don't have to, you don't have to, are you like ripped, are you like muscular and yeah.
So like, yeah, I have a little bit, yeah, I have a little bit psyche, but not that much. I'm not, I'm just average, you know, like a normal average, you know, guy.
Okay, well, that's fine. That's fine. As long as you're not below average.
No, I'm not fat. No, I'm not fat or anything like that.
Do you want a girlfriend?
Huh?
Yeah, I mean eventually but whenever it comes though, but it's like they're not they don't just come like usually
They usually you have to like approach women like they don't they usually disappear like um
And you're not supposed no are you blocked of course you're not blocked page page. I love you page page
I don't know why you're not modded. I don't know
Why would you say are you blocked page?
Page you have never said anything or done anything that you know page Mesa
Well, I'm sorry page, huh? No. No, you don't get paid is really
Yeah
Paid you're not blog psyche. Yeah, thank you. Why would they say that though? Why would they say that they're blocked pages?
It's like a friend of mine
Like you know, and it's like I don't know
Why she would think that but?
I do, I do have an idea. Maybe. Why, but no.
Here. Hold on.
Psyche, you saw what thing is, you saw what the thing is said.
He says, you are the lover. Mason, the lover.
Yeah, you're the lover.
It's amazing. Do you see how I'm dressed tonight?
Yeah, you were like that yesterday, right psyche you dress like that yesterday
Last night yeah last night minutes. I've been just been on the show with this hole
This is my new my new outfit. Do you like it? Oh, yeah
Yeah, psyche yeah, yeah, I'm dressed like a priest
So like you do you have a different shirt that I could actually put on that I haven't wore yet?
I mean like why I have one or do you have one you want a mine?
Do you have a shirt you get you have a shirt you can let me borrow or something like that psyche that I could wear that I could put
On yeah, just put your dress in the back. I'll send you a shirt if you want
Okay, if you put your dress in the back chat, I'll get I'll send you a shirt, but what you like that one just wear that one
Where that shirt
Sike you're fine Mason. Oh, that's good man. I love McDonald's
Yeah, yeah, and uh
Don't let anybody make you feel bad or like, you know
We're like that guy Carl. It's like that guy Carl made me feel bad when I was on here before and I was talking to stuff
remember that
Carl, who's that? Oh, yeah, Carl. Oh, yeah, but Carl is yeah, that's I think an ex-boyfriend of somebody
I know but um, that's Venus
Yeah
Why do you mean he made you feel bad, but why he was yeah, he's a little he's kind of weird, right?
Who's kind of weird it's like Carl Carl. Yeah
Yeah
So, but I thought he was kind of nice to you. I mean, it's like he was kind of just conversational
But yeah, he was a little he's a little bit just of a but it was like he was being
No, it's like he was being good for a while
But then all of a sudden at the end he started changing like weird and stuff like that and say it's a weird stuff
Yeah, a little bit, but you know what?
Sometimes you have to ignore people because
You're gonna meet some interesting unusual people in the panel verse. Hey Paige
I want to show you something if you can come up for a second
I'll talk to you one-on-one if you don't mind, but I have something to show you. Oh
Do I have it? Hold on. I hope I have it. I hope I have it. Let me make sure I have it
But if I don't then I'm sorry. Oh, I don't think I have it. Okay. I don't have it ready
But I will have it ready. I've seen I'm a surprise for you, but I have to show you later
You I think you'll like
So, Mason, are you going to start your channel?
Well, you want me to do that?
Like, yeah, you think I should?
Yeah, you know why?
Because then you can have people that like you,
like, like, like you, and then want to come and talk to you
and stuff, and then you can, like, chat with them.
And I'll come visit your channel, too.
And I'll show you how to start it, too, if you want.
Um, and then...
So, like, you got to help me out, though, with it.
I will.
Well, I've helped a bunch of people start channels. It's like it's not too hard. I say I just got to help you get to 50 subscribers
I think you will be able to just do the show probably
It's like who's in the cuffs?
Who is in the who's what?
It's like who is in the cuffs who is in cuffs who is in cuffs? Oh
Alexander put me in handcuffs one night and
It was me and Alexander's handcuffs.
He's a police officer and he threw me in the bushes one night.
No, I didn't know that.
It's like, I mean, he put you in handcuffs for real?
Yeah, I have a video of it, actually.
Let me see if I can find it.
You wanna see it?
Do you like cartoons?
Yeah.
Oh, you do?
Okay, good.
Well, this is perfect then.
I mean, this is good.
I'll pull this up.
we see
So I keep yeah, the thing that the thing the thing that is says I come talk to you
But you time me out though so I can't I'm not gonna do it anymore
I mean so I can't want him to know I'm not gonna do that anymore
Okay, then that is he says he's not good. He's not a mod so he can't time you out anymore, but
Um, but you've got how'd you figure I had a time people out though? I don't I still understand
It's kind of like it just happened when I was going through those different things like on the channel. Why why why him?
Why did you do that to him?
It is like you're like yeah, I did
I didn't mean to do it like it's a bad thing. No, it's like yeah
I was just trying to joke up like you know try to make them see that I was at the end
I was just gonna say that I'm playing around it once it I was done doing that
I wasn't trying to do it for real though. I mean like
Do you know how to unhide people as a problem because then it's like if you hit him
And then he couldn't be unhidden and he won't be able to talk in the chat and like no one would know
Like yeah, I won't do it again though
I mean I can't do it anyways like you said so I'm not a mom anyway, but you can
You can you can block people it's one bothers you though
You can just block them and then you won't see their their their message. Okay, so you can just say yeah push name
Just like that. That's like you deal with the mod
But you can just push their name and then hide them and then it will just be hide hid for you because I want to talk to thing
That is I
Yeah, and then he was like not able to talk in the chat. He had to come and tell me that he was hidden and
Yeah
He thought I maybe did it, but who's you?
You're trying to thank you, but I don't want him to take it. Thank you
I don't want him to take it seriously or personal though. Like I was doing that on purpose. I was just
I think he's okay. Do you forgive him? I think that is you forgive me. So I think maybe it was probably innocent, right?
Was it innocent?
Yeah, thank you. I was innocent. Yeah, not not important. Okay
So is there any who are you interested in now? Is there somebody that you're interested in now as a date?
You know, I'm not not me. Yeah, do you have it? Do you have a girl you like?
So I guess beta available
Yes, she is I
Suggest so I guess what about beta though? Yeah, I think you should date her
Think he'd be perfect for her. It's like I want a chance with her. I don't think
What do you guys think in the chat? I think that's a good idea
Well, what is she what does she say? I'm sorry Mason. No, don't don't go over there. Don't
Don't Mason Mason
No
Okay, well, yes
I'm I'm turning a little bit too evil right now. Hold on one sec. I need to find the video
Where's the where's the Alex between video? I can find a whole I can get it from a lecture
Where's my discord?
Will you like be that like you but you haven't even said you haven't seen her in person
No, I've only sold her on what it's like you on on on on YouTube. You didn't see her like in person
No, it's here in person
But you see a picture
No, it's like you only seen her on YouTube like I said like I didn't see her on in person
I know but it means did you see her picture or you just like your voice? She doesn't have a very nice voice
I've seen her on video like on camera like what she was talking stuff, right?
Well, she just has a picture up. I mean, it's just her picture. Yeah pretty much yeah
Well psyche. Yeah, it's not a day. He may have says this is not a dating app
Oh, yes, it is. Come on. Hey, man, man. Hey, man, this is this YouTube is for everything. Of course you can date on YouTube
What do you talk?
You can meet wonderful people to date on YouTube. Let me see if I can find the
So if you want me to write my last name in the back chat though, or what I know what it is
I know what it is. There's the P. I know it sounds like it sounds like the name of a fish
I know I know
I know. I remember now. It's like, I'm not going to say it out loud. But yeah, I know you're loud.
So like if you were to say it out loud, that'd be called Dawson, right? I shouldn't be Dawson. I think it's called, right?
Yeah, that's why I can't do it. Oh, hold on. There's a cartoon. You're going to see the cartoon?
Yeah.
Okay, hold on once again. Okay, I got it. Hold on. I got it for you.
This is what happened last week. Okay. Hold on a second
Thank you. That's not true
It's like you what he man said that's not true though. He says he has a
Stalker paperwork and you're sending him to arrest another that has nothing to do what's going on. It's like I
Have stalker paperwork. What does that mean? I don't understand. I'm very confused. I didn't send you anywhere Mason
Did I ever send you anywhere?
No
didn't see innocent okay let me see um okay I need to share my screen and we'll
be right with you I don't know I don't know people are so weird let's see so I
didn't do anything wrong though this time I was just you didn't you didn't but no
I think I know I think be it it does have a point for no don't bother her here
Yeah, that's you right. Yeah, the cartoon. Yes cartoon. Yeah, okay. I'm gonna play it now watch
Alex
In the bush, I'm gonna fuck the shit out of you in the bushes, okay?
I'm gonna, in the trees, but on the side of the highway, I'm gonna fucking give it to you.
I'm gonna make my fault and just go on my way.
That's Alex.
That was Andrew.
Yeah.
So, like, you're actually trying to show me a video like that?
Well, what's wrong with that?
They're I didn't really get it psyche. I didn't get what it was about
That's Alexander McQueen. He's a he's a police officer in New York
Hold on. Yeah, but does he said it was supposed to be about you though psyche because you're in it. Oh
He man, I see I see he man. What happened at the church
Or no, sorry, um, Mason. What happened to that church?
How are you why were you at that church that you wouldn't leave the church
I was at the church hanging out Saki. That's why I got that charge on me the trespass charge
Oh, why were you hanging out there at the church?
I just I knew people there like people that I like that were my friends and stuff like that
But I'll talk to them but they they told me that's not what the church is supposed to be about though
So that's why they gave me a charge
We're bothering a we're bothering a nice lady at the church
No, I was just hanging out there those like I was just talking and just you know being there and just you know
Staying there for a while makes us stay in there too long, right? I was supposed to leave
Sunday on a Sunday
It was like on a regular day, so I could just any other day
That's weird like why did I have church? What?
But why are they usually people just go to church on a Sunday?
and then usually people
Thank you son Sunday. Yeah, but psyche
I think is I think is everybody wanted everybody to leave and I would still stay there though
You know try to talk to the people that were even I'm in there
Was there like a nice lady like putting out the candles that you're talking to
No, there's people I knew there though
So I feel like people I talked to like that knew me like friends and stuff like that
But I don't know why I got it
It doesn't make sense to me to this day still though so I can why they would give me trespass for that though
Well, because if someone asked you to go to leave
Then you're supposed to say okay, and then like just leave and then or else they might call the cops on you
You're supposed to yes, but it was sake. I was think yes, I guess what was I think?
I think I was just hanging out there and staying there too long when everybody's supposed to leave that place
But I was still there and stuff like that if everyone's leaving and you're supposed to be there like why wouldn't you just leave the church?
Because I had nowhere to go like and stuff and I had somebody there that I couldn't find anywhere else though
Because they don't ever hang out would be anywhere else. We just hang out at church
Okay, well, you know, I think maybe
From now on if someone says
It's time to go home. It's time you have to go home, right? I know it has been a week, but it's like still I mean
Usually it's like a youth group or something. It's not usually a good dulls. I don't know what's going on Mason like
Like like what was going on at the church that day like?
There was there's people that were just you know, hang it like you know
There's people after church was done. There's people that just you know, like like walk around and just stand with each other and just all have like you know
Like a like a all chat with each other
Like they would just you know, just relax and hang out with each other and just talk and just have like a time
You know just to hang out so so what I just want to know what happened
So you were talking to somebody and they say you know time to go home and then you said no, I'm just gonna stay here
And that's what it was.
Yeah, Psyche, I was ignoring what they were telling me to do.
And he said, hey, church is over now.
So everybody's supposed to get ready to leave.
And I was just like, OK.
And I was like, I hear what you're saying.
But really, I wasn't doing what they told me to do.
I was just like, yeah, I hear you and stuff like that.
But I would still just continue to do what I'm doing,
though.
It's like just talking to who, when other people are just
sitting down, standing up with each other
and just being with each other, I
would do that with them and stuff like that.
Okay, well, you know what, next time you have to go,
you have to like, you know, say, okay,
and even if you just are like standing like 20 feet away
from it outside, it's better to listen to like,
was it like the minister or like, you know,
who was telling you that?
Like, I believe.
It was a person, it was a person that said,
charge of the church.
I think it's like the priest, right?
Or pastor or something like that.
Okay, so if you see someone dressed like I'm dressed right now, you need to listen to them, okay?
You mean because they're more of like an authoritative, like, figure, right?
Yeah.
It's like, like, they have contrast, like, they're empowered.
You might own the church or just be a very high person, a high ranking person there.
And so if the minister or priest or whatever is like, oh, it's time to like, you know, blow
out the candles and lock the church door.
Besanke, not everybody was believing those.
There were some people that were still just in there too.
So that's why I was doing it as well.
Who but who wasn't staying there like was it just a priest?
Those people that knew me there like you know friends that I had in there in the church that talked to me and stuff and hang out
Okay
Well, and but what have you learned about?
Flirting with with women, what do you learn that it's like not always
Good do it. Yeah, psyche also psyche is also not a good thing for me to talk to women while I'm in there
Right psyche because I probably don't know them that good
It's but that's the only way to get to know somebody psyche
No, it's like he's the only way to get to know somebody there is to talk to him
If you want to get a girlfriend you have to get to know them though, right?
Not the best place unless you're like really religious. It's like usually not the best have you ever heard of like a bar or like
You know like a restaurant or like McDonald's even right didn't like hang out with like McDonald's people
Yeah, but yeah, but psyche the other places
I just go just to eat like because that's what you're really supposed to do there
But I mean I know you're saying you could do other things so if you want, but I see at a restaurant
You're supposed to eat right that's what you're supposed to do the rest
But also better church are supposed to do is pray and then reading the Bible
and then, or leaving.
That's the three things you can do at a church.
That's the only thing.
Yeah, but Psyche, I get more,
but yeah, Psyche, I get bored at that though.
I don't always just wanna go to church and do that.
That's why I just hang out and talk to people and stuff there.
I know, I know, it is, it is, it is.
But Mason, it's, the church is really boring anyway.
I mean, it's like, that's like not the best place to just,
oh here, we have a guest that is.
Yeah, but Psyche, yeah, but Psyche,
another thing is, I don't really get many chances to,
you know, talk to people when I'm there.
I can have somebody to hang out with.
Hey Mason, hey Syke. Hi, what's up? What's up dude? Yeah
Yeah, I'm just trying to like, you know help them out a little bit too because I think
We arrested twice at a church because they they took you to a jail
And then it's like you can't really meet people there at the jail and then yeah, but psyche it's not really like
Yeah, but it's like you're not really like major with that what I did though. It's not like I did a huge crime or something
I'm really in trouble though
It's like before the police come you want to like listen to the
Authority people in the place, right? You would so it was like someone says leave. Yeah
Yeah, you should just go outside. Yeah
Go home and stuff like that Mason. Let me just mention something that's kind of related. Remember the other I don't know last week on
betas
panel
You were complimenting a lady there constantly and she voiced it that she was getting a little uncomfortable with it and you kept going and kept going, remember that?
Yeah.
Okay, but you remember when I was trying to talk to you and explain to you that you know the first time is nice
It's a compliment. It's nice women or ladies like that. Everybody likes being told that they're good-looking or whatever
But to keep going
Especially if it's the first time you've ever met them
Yeah, I mean I wasn't trying to do anything like
I believe you, I don't think you meant any harm,
but you need to understand her point of view too, right?
It's not just what you're thinking.
You've got to think, well, what's she thinking?
Does she think I'm being aggressive?
Does she think I'm being weird or something like that?
You've got to consider that too.
But thing thing that is I was just giving her like, you know compliments. So that's all I did that day
That's not like I said it wrong. I get it. I understand all that and like I said, you weren't being mean or anything to her
But it gets it can be obsessive. It can make you look obsessive. It can just be creepy
It can make her feel like she's just
Like an object like I told you that day
It'll make the person just feel like an object. It's like you don't give a crap
And he's just like the way I look Mason also like I noticed about women is like
They get complimented all the time by a lot of different guys. And so it's like
It's like sometimes
Like less is more with that. It's like, you know, it's just like, you know
It has to be really genuine and the short and then it's like you're like you let them
Decide and come like you what was I supposed to do though?
I thought I was just supposed to be nice and that's what I was doing was being nice to give a
Yeah, but it's like it's like be nice, but then it's like let them come over to you and stuff
And if they don't then just like go to someone else, I guess, right?
Okay
Yeah, you don't want to bother them, right? It's like if you say even twice is bothering like one time maybe is
Okay, like if it's like a genuine
And you're just being friendly, but then it's like more than one time. It's like, yeah
I guarantee you Mason even if you're the best looking guy in the world
If you're constantly telling a girl like every, you know, two minutes, you're just you're beautiful. Oh my god
Oh, you really look pretty and all that. She's gonna think you're a creep too after an hour or so. She's good. This guy is
too much
Yeah, I can understand that thing that is I'm gonna try not to do it like it's like as much anymore
and if the minister if the
The preacher tells you it's time to leave the church. It's time to leave
I don't want you to get in trouble again because it happened twice, right?
Yeah, yeah, and you don't want to get kicked out of places and or like have the police call on you
You don't want to know you don't want another
mug shot because then there's three mug shots and it's like pattern so you want
to be you want to like end it now and end it now maybe meet somebody online
that's interested in you that writes to you first and then it has an interest and
then play it really cool like
Just pretending that is yeah
Thing that is how come you're not, uh, how come you're not modded though you should be modded though
No, no, I don't want much like has given it to me before he's offered it to me since then I honestly I don't want it
What what makes you say that though thing that is why don't you want to be just don't want it? It's it's one of those things where
Mean you appear in a room if you're wearing a uniform when you when you come into a room people are gonna just look at you and be like
Why is the guy in the uniform like why is he in uniform with the five other people in uniform?
Like who do they think they are what's going on the thing that is how does that have anything to do with being modded though?
That doesn't have anything to do with that
It's a metaphor. It's it's I'm trying to explain
It gives a little bit of an air to that person and I don't want to make it sound like it's a bad thing for everybody
I don't like it. I don't like the way it makes me look or the way it makes me feel when I come into a chat
Okay, other people have no problem with it
Bless them. They can have the wrenches. I don't care
I just don't want it. I I I'm more of a blend into the wallpaper kind of guy, you know
I've said sit at the back of the room and just kind of be quiet and just observe
Yeah
Right, so the thing that thing that is I just got to calm it down when I talk to women you're saying like and I I shouldn't just keep
Complimenting them when I talk to them. Yeah. Yeah, definitely
Not not persistently and you know like
Where it's just it's like a machine almost. Yeah, it's just just do it. Just do it a little bit, right?
Like you're in there not that much there. There's also the circumstance like when it comes to church like
You know people are saying that's not really the place to go to meet women
Unless you actually go to church and yeah, you can meet a woman in church
But you're going to church for the church and if you happen to meet someone there the relationship goes slowly usually
You don't go there to pick up or to meet someone to hook up within a couple weeks
Right. Yeah, but think that is it's kind of hard to just wait for a relationship to happen when they're at church because it takes a
Lot of time and effort to make it happen
That's why you don't go to church to find a relationship. That's that's what we're saying if it happens
thing that is I'm saying that there's a place where there's people that you can actually meet them because there's people there and stuff like that
So why not meet them? Yeah, yeah, and like okay fine meet them
It doesn't mean you have to compliment the women there every every two minutes, right?
It doesn't mean you have to precisely, you know
Batter them with questions, you know a hundred questions in ten minutes
Right, you meet them and that's it and then as days go by as you see each other more and more
They become more familiar with you you with them. This is how relationships go. This is a relationship
Yeah, it's not it's not just constantly telling them that they're beautiful. There is that
But it's not it's not just that
Yeah, right, I'm not trying to write
Like I'm trying. I don't want to embarrass you or anything like that. Like I want you to understand
Then it is I agree with you. I'm just saying like I just don't know how to get a girlfriend nowadays, though
That's why I do some like stuff like that sometimes. I'm not I'm not the teacher on that. That's for sure
I
Mean not that I haven't had girlfriends. It's just I
I'm not good with relationships myself. Nothing's really long-term. I mean, I mean
Thing that is it just seems like it's hard for me to get a girlfriend and there's nothing wrong with me
It's like I don't do a thing to come. I mean I might say, you know compliments a lot like you said
But it's not like I'm saying anything like hateful or mean or anything like that, but I don't I
Understand I think you're innocent in it the way you approached it. I think you're just a little naive on it
That's all and I think you may have a bit of trouble
Understanding like thinking that the other person also has thoughts
Kind of thing like they have feelings too. It's consideration like is the word you you're where you consider with the other person feels
Yeah, I think you maybe maybe that hasn't been
Homed yeah, I
Think you're right. Yeah, I think you might be right about the
It's the way it appears. I mean I could be wrong
The thing that is what do I do though? Just like I don't know what to do I
Don't know I don't I can't tell you what to do, but I can certainly tell you what you shouldn't do
Miss Mason when what when was this when did these things happen? It was a years ago or is it recently?
So, uh, psyche this stuff happened like in 20, like, uh, 16 or 2017 and it's been a long time and you haven't been in any trouble since you haven't had that problem since but you know, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
You know, do you drink at all or do you go out? No, no, I wish I don't go to bars like I don't really drink
I don't drink alcohol. You don't have to drink
But it's like that's kind of good not to drink at bars. Don't get too messed up and you can like be in your be out of
Do you have a church that you go to are you a regular church goer?
I was at the time that when I was doing all that stuff that happened before like with the
Trespass, but I don't go to church anymore though. Well, if you're interested and get involved again
They do have social stuff that they do
That's that's usually a good place to meet people because it's out of the church setting
It's not it's not as preachy and all that and it's just a nicer wholesome time. Let's say
Okay, yeah, because you know what we're not trying to like pick on you or anything. It's just like
Everyone has to learn how to like, you know navigate in the dating world and yeah, there's there's better
There's it. I think maybe the you know going to an app like like a dating app, right?
And then just having a nice picture smiling on the dating app and like
If someone writes to you or if you write to somebody and maybe they'll write back, you know, you never know, but it's they and that is
Okay, I'll let me know leave again. He must talk. It's okay
Whatever
Yeah, yeah, I was gonna say like there's something I was gonna say to you. I can't remember what I was gonna say, but uh
There's something like
Oh, yeah, when I did that hide in stuff like or no time in you out of stuff like that
I want you to take it. I didn't want you to take it like I was being mean or I was trying to be like okay. I
Want to try to understand or anything like that. I understand you don't have to keep going on about it
But just understand it from my point of view. It was annoying. I'm not mad about it. I'm not whatever
Don't hold thing that is how how is it thing that is how is it annoying those I kept doing it like I would
Yeah, because every time I wanted to type in chat. I I
Couldn't I would get the red X saying you know you're you've been timed out
So it's annoying. I couldn't say anything. That's why I had to finally hop on the panel and just say I mean just
Chill on the timing me out. That's all
I could join a community, right?
Yeah, look at what Paige is saying, and I know He-Man made some suggestions too, book club and stuff like that.
These are places where you can go, where you don't have to be in the bar scene, the nightclub scene, you know?
But other people go to those places too thing that is like a bar stuff because people are they get in fights and stuff like that there
Yeah, yeah, I don't know. I didn't like the bar scene from meeting girls either
It was cool to just you know to look at girls and chat with them just play around for
Need a girl for a relationship. No way
They're gonna fight when you're like talking to their girlfriend and that'd be kind of dangerous for you
It's like if you like we're talking to some girl that had a boyfriend and then you come over and say hey
What are you doing? Right? So you want to make sure like so thing that is there's no way
They'll get they'll get all weird and stuff like right or mean I mean a bar is a different setting
It doesn't mean that you can just go up to all the women and just start hitting on them. Okay. You you will get slapped
You will get punched in the face. You will get thrown out
Okay
Yeah, it is more um
It's more common for pick up pick up lines or you know in all that trying to hit on girls
It's more common in nightclubs and bars
For sure
Doesn't mean you can just go nuts
Yeah
Right. Yeah. Yeah
So I mean I got it where to go I feel for you man. I know it's tough. It's tough to to meet
To meet someone so that you really
Especially thing that is where did psyche go? He's not there anymore. Um, maybe went to the bathroom. I don't know
She put a cowbell on him so we notice when he wanders away and we don't hear it anymore
Amazing you know what I think there are
Women out there that would like you I know it's like and it's like I don't know who she is but I think that
There's gonna be I think more of like a shy a shy type and because you're so like
Extraverted you know you're very extroverted and it's like and so you know like maybe the library or something
I mean, but I'm trying to think I don't want to bother but if library entails you to leave you leave the library
Yeah, but maybe like some kind of like a little bit more
What are you you know or maybe like a concert that'd be good like there's girls like the thing that is
Come on. Hey, why are you always asking me?
I have something to tell you think that is I'm gonna say there's somebody there's somebody that told me to calm down in the chat
But what did they mean calm down? I am calm
Alex told you that um, I don't know. I don't know specifically what he meant
Well, maybe he meant calm down as far as hitting on girls or something
Yeah, go on so I didn't know it's good. He's good. They have a lot of questions and that you're like open to like
Learning things but like you should listen to like the good advice that you know people will tell you some good advice
but uh
You know, but you're really the best way is the internet because there's a lot of people there
And so there's a lot of different few kind of people and it's like you're gonna find somebody on the internet that is like
Interested there's gonna be somebody that's gonna write you and then it's like then you know that they have to be interested first
I say wait for them to be interested in you
and I know it's like you've been waiting a long time,
but you have to also put yourself out there a little bit
and talk.
So I can't, I wasn't trying to cut you off.
So I can't, I wasn't trying to cut you off
or whatever, talking and stuff.
Don't worry, don't worry, don't worry.
But find somebody that like comes up to you,
like, and put yourself out there in social situations
and like, I don't know if you like, you know,
drink it all or anything, but,
or go to a concert and you're, you'll just like,
Because you're a nice looking person and no, it's like yeah, I don't drink though. I don't drink beer
I don't drink alcohol. That's why I don't go to you can like just get a soda
Do you like books me like soda like soda? Yeah
Do you like reading you like reading do you like books sometimes sometimes?
Yeah, that's so much. What do you like to read more? What's the last book you read?
What was the last book you read?
Oh, it's been a long time since I've read a book, like years ago.
Dr. Seuss, or was it like, you know,
hey, checkers, guide to the galaxy?
What was it?
Wait, Psyche, look at something, though.
Like, Queen Natalie said something.
the queen Natalie's in her
Natalie's awesome. You know Natalie is probably a good person to talk to you too.
It's because she's a nice a nice um sweet person and she might have some really good advice and
she's a woman. I mean she's going to have the female perspective. So it's not married or far away.
Or maybe someone not married is definitely you want to find someone that's not married if there's one that's single
Maybe someone that is far away that you could just talk to you on the internet. It would be okay
But yeah, you don't want to find someone that's like
unrealistically far right so I can sustain away from people that are
married right don't the boyfriend I don't want you to get beat up by
somebody or like like have a angry boyfriend or like have a her like over
controlling boyfriend right
No, not controlling boyfriend. Yeah, exactly. But you know your brother fan your brother seems like he's he's
He's really talented, but he's he found a girlfriend and
So I think you can too
But you don't want to find
Someone as early as controlling as his girlfriend make sure you someone that like lets you do what you want and not try to control you too much
I guess
Maybe psyche. I don't like psyche. I don't like anybody controlling me, but there's people that will though
Yeah, well, I mean if it gets down to it, you know, it's fine like have a controlling girlfriend
Maybe she'll like you know help you out a lot, but uh
You know
You can't you have to stop with the stop with the women with the boyfriends or the husband's okay?
Yeah
Yeah, because they definitely will not be will not like that. It's like that's like they're off the market
You know this is called off the market means they're not available and then the
You have a good heart you have a good heart. It's like someone that likes music
I'm thinking like a concert if there's any concert you can go to our coffee house where they have like live music
And you can jet and it's like and then it's like open and you know all night and so I mean yeah
Somebody says I need a good listener or a deaf one
Okay, a deaf woman find a deaf woman
You know or a blind woman because a blind woman doesn't care what you look like a deaf woman doesn't care what you talk about right and then
So yeah, maybe someone with a disability
So it's like yeah, I hope to find some way that will like me though. So what that will get it
Yeah, I think that's I think that's gonna be a good option for you
Like do you have is there are any events for like
Let me see like, you know some special events where they like they bring people together and stuff like are you need any groups?
Or any kind of like besides a church group or is there any kind of like social?
Group you can be part of
I haven't really found one yet.
It's like, I haven't got into one yet.
Look into like, what is it, meetup.com
has like different group meetings.
Like there's like different,
or like some kind of social event.
Like look for like, you know, and it's like,
and then leave when they tell you to, and it's like.
No one talks to you or whatever
It's called it's just part of the game. You know, it's like you just go it's a numbers game, right?
And so it's like it's gonna be a small percentage of women in general that are available, right?
So maybe like, you know, two percent of women that you meet are gonna be available
And just focus on that psyche. Yes, I
Should I should play in a band right like if I don't have a drum that to play in a band yet
But somebody said join the band
Well, you're not I mean you might meet girls that way but not in the band most likely so until you start gigging in stuff
You're not gonna be meeting girls
Or do if you had a pair if you if you got some kind of drum
You got even a pink can with the drumsticks and you were like, you know really just say God
You're gonna have people coming up to you and
Socialize and like watching you and like that like that then they come to you
But it's like usually the men approach the women, but
They're not supposed to over approach them.
It's like they're supposed to, you know,
just talk and then see where it goes.
And I don't know, I think maybe you need a friend too,
a friend to like with you to help you a little bit.
So like you are my friend though,
I thought that's what you are, it's like you're my friend.
I am your friend, but I'm not like there, you know,
as I can't be there.
Yeah, you need a real life like in real life right there.
In person.
It's like yeah, I don't have one though right now though. That's right. Well, are you into voodoo?
Yeah, I mean Mason there's lots of groups like meeting things these days
It's way more than it was like 20 30 years ago. So I mean you gotta look around
Um, the other thing if you're if you're gonna be talking to women in like chats and stuff like that and YouTube is
Even married women like people get a little flirty and talk use a bit of innuendo and chat and that kind of stuff
You can't take that as them
Showing interest in you, you know, like I mean people just cut loose sometimes and they just like to joke
Okay, so that that's another little nuance that you're going to have to get a hold of
Yeah, wait, I don't understand. I didn't think you would
Sometimes people just like to have fun in the chat and they'll say stuff that they really wouldn't say in real life to a guy right there
Okay, that's what I mean
Natalie says, don't take it seriously.
Yeah, she's, and if there's a married woman that is showing interest, she just sees you
as like a one time only thing and probably will not want you calling your house and stuff.
So you know, you're going to want to find, find someone that's available, I'd say find
someone that's looking for a boyfriend, I'm thinking like.
I'd like the book club idea, like the concert idea.
I'd like a coffee house, but I think you really need
a male friend or a female friend
that is comfortable with you and stuff,
and that can help you navigate a little bit,
because I think you need a little bit more experience.
What about art, Mason?
You like art at all?
You like painting or anything like that?
I haven't really done it that much,
but I've seen it before.
Would you like to do it?
You could take a class on that.
I could I could try to do something like that. Yeah, right like there's tons of like
Events like like that you can go to and it's like so it's like people go there to meet people or they go there to socialize
And so they're expecting to meet people
sometimes when they're going to church to just want to like have a conversation with God and stuff like that and
You know, it's not the place that's best place usually for dating, but
And you just I would say just bring something with you. Do you have a buddy decent you have a buddy that you can hang out with look at prayer
Cooking class that'd be great because you're doing
Psychiatrist friends in the past but now I don't have as much friends because I'm growing up and stuff like that
And they moved on or that they're adults and stuff
Yeah, they have like wives and stuff, you know, in its heart, it's not easy,
Maison. It was not going to be an easy thing. But so what do you really want? What are you
really looking for? Because you can chat with a lot of people in this like bullshit with people
online. It's not usually the biggest deal because you're not usually like even in the area. And so
it's like, they can always block you or something like that. But you want to find somebody that
and it has interest in you too.
It has to be a mutual interest where it's like,
what do you mean they can block you on stuff like that?
You said they can block you.
Online, they can block you in the chat and stuff like that
if you go too far or if you bother them too much.
And so you wanna find somebody that wants to talk to you
and there are people, and even if you don't wanna date
in real life, you can find like a pen pal.
Sometimes there's a lot of people that are kind of like,
looking for people to talk to.
Um, you know that also don't know a lot of people in real life and it's like and they like to they like to talk
You have to find somebody that you can have a good conversation with and it's back and forth and not just like you
Asking them questions and stuff because some people would get maybe
Overwhelmed I think offended me like offended by it, right and or overwhelmed or just like it's just too much and it's like they
They'll get annoyed, but you want to find somebody that maybe he's asking you questions and like somebody that
It's showing the interest in you you too, right?
Saki, I had people that have done that to me before like I have people that like me in the past
But I haven't had ones for a while though now. It's like it's been like years
Well, have you been like just inside the house alone a lot?
Yeah, yeah, well get out there, but it's like no more going to no more going to that church, okay?
Are you working right now Mason?
No, okay
Oh, that's a good idea, like a job.
If you had a job basin, is there a McDonald's hiring?
Because there's probably nice people that work there,
or like a fast food restaurant.
So like, I don't have a job right now.
I didn't get one, because I wasn't able to find one, yeah.
Have you applied to McDonald's?
Yeah, but I never got a hired though. I've been waiting to stuff like for them to get back to me
Okay, there's a website called snag a job comm s n a g a j o b snag a job
And it's like a lot it will be a jobs in your area that are hiring and then it's like if you work with somebody
You're gonna be pretty on doing your job and stuff like that
But after work and stuff you can say or maybe you can say we can go to lunch at work or you can develop friendships
you just need to develop and also
You don't have to worry about dating so much.
You want to find, first of all,
you want to find some friends, right?
You want to find a social group.
Yeah, right, and it's like or just people and
Really like to talk to you because you want that you want this eventually, right?
Like I don't really like want to date anybody. So I'm like, yeah, I don't really talk to I like I'm just on my show
but uh, you
Like you have a good, you know, you're a good talker and stuff and you like to socialize
And so you need to find people that want to socialize and so
Saiki, I thought that's what you like to do though. You like to socialize.
I do, but online and it's like, and I don't really, I mean, it's like, and I, you know, I
I flirt with people and stuff, but it's like, not in a too serious of a way.
Because it's like not, like online is a kind of different than real life. It's a little bit different.
It's like, it's not the same as real life.
What makes it not the same though?
Well, what makes it not the same
is that it might be a long time
before you meet them in person.
And then it's like,
because I know you want to like have a connection
and like a physical connection, right?
Eventually, and it's harder
when people are all around the world and things like that.
But if you just want to talk to people,
yeah, you can talk to people all over the world.
But yeah, that's what I'm talking to you psyche because you're somebody that likes to, you know talk sometimes
But I'm you know
I'm just like some
Random guy. I know you're looking for like a nice
Pretty woman, right?
Yeah
Yeah, and I don't need to take an advantage of either because it's like, you know, some people might just try to try to like
Be interested in other things besides you you want to find someone that likes you for you and someone that really likes you
And you want to find somebody that's interested back
And not like you have to know it's not like that's like I get what you're saying
But it's not it's easier said than done though. You know what I'm saying let's get that the life is life is not always easy
You know do you have a pet me son?
Uh, not with me. I mean not on me. Not on I mean they're not on you
But it's like do you have one around is there you're one in the house or do you know it has to look for it though?
It's like yeah, that's a bond. Yeah, what do you have you have a dog or a cat?
Huh? Give a dog or a cat. I
Don't have either one right now. Psychiatrist. Yeah, you have one around you
So I can have them outside, there's like I see cats outside like by my place where I live like there's cats outside the window stuff
Well pet a cat like like go put out some food and stuff and get some cat food and
Play with cats. I don't know
And then maybe you'll find someone that likes cats and they'll say oh, there's a guy play with cats
Volunteered something do a walk-a-thon or something like that volunteer for some charity work
You're talking about like community service or something like that. Yeah, some kind of charity
Yeah, ones especially walk-a-thons because you can meet lots of people there
What is a walk-a-thon thing that is what what do you do at a walk-a-thon you walk
I think you walk up or you walk you never hurt where you get pledges
We're if you do like let's say it's a whatever 10 mile walk. I don't know what they are
Yeah, so you get like you know 10 cents per mile and then so you get a dollar
From that person that pledge and you know
But I'm not even talking about the pledges. I'm talking about the other people that participate
Especially if it's like a dog walk-a-thon and you have your own dog
You're gonna meet some women there because then you're all you're doing the same thing
And then you have to like walk around the track and stuff
And if so they'll probably like they won't probably walk with somebody like when the same pace look for someone walking this
Same pace as you and it's like you look like just chat and
I think just chatting with people at those kind of events,
like you'll meet somebody.
There's somebody out there,
there's a lid for every pot I've heard people saying, right?
So there's a lid for your pot.
I mean, it's just like, I don't,
I think you might have to go to a specialty store.
But you know what, Mason?
I know you have a good heart.
Just don't creep people out by being too aggressive, okay?
you want to be playing cool and like have someone come up to you and like want to talk to you and like
but you have to be out there more you can't just be sitting at home you know if you really want
yeah you mean so it's like you mean you have to actually be doing stuff to actually get things done
right you can't just be at home okay to be out in the world and like
meeting people because there's because sometimes people say dating is a numbers game because if you like talk to like a
Thousand people there's gonna be like ten people that are gonna be interested
You have to talk to the thousand people and you'll find that ten people in there and then you can decide from that 10
Yeah, but psyche. I'm not trying to get it up psyche. I'm not trying to get in trouble with anybody
That's why I don't really talk to a lot of people because
if you just talk
nicely and
Feel the conversation and feel it's it's hard as I'm saying have a friend
Supervised
Right, okay. Yeah for you and like they make and say oh it's time to go and stuff like that and or or don't
It's I don't think she's interested in you have someone that's gonna tell you the truth and like help you in person
Do you have someone like that?
So does experiment with it, like experiment with what goes on and stuff like out there
in the world?
Yeah.
But yeah, but experiment, but I would say experiment, but just let them come, let them
show interest in you first, and then you know, and then you can feel comfortable, but don't
be overwhelming for people because especially women don't like to be over, because they
Yeah, they we've been are probably they have ten times more people talking to them than men do so it can be harder
But there's that there's that special woman out there for you. I know I know there is and like you may not just kind of give it like a
Chance right like to see what happens
Just go out there and meet people just edit don't try to make don't necessarily try to meet somebody
for dating? Just trying to meet somebody to have a conversation and like a good conversation
and then might go somewhere from there. But if they're not interested, you'll be able to tell
you know they'll be looking away and they'll be like trying to like you know they'll be on their
phone and stuff like that. You'll know when they're not interested but you'll know when they're interested
and then you can kind of
Have an easier time with it. Okay, but and don't don't overthink it and also just be happy being being alone too
But if you get lonely
You can just talk to people in chat rooms and stuff
And there's a lot of
How would I get a psychic? How would I get lonely though? He said I might get lonely
But how would that happen?
Maybe I can only just be in the house and stuff and not talking to people on stuff
So you mean it wouldn't make sure like
You socialize and and
Either go out or talk to people online and stuff
Online is a good thing because it's like you mean a lot of people and there's a lot of people
It was some people will be interested. So like have you ever given Mason a reading? I don't have you had a terror reading Mason
No, I never had that done before
Yeah
You can do the reading Mason is good talking to you again. Yeah, it's good to talk to you
I'll be in the chat cycle talk to you later
Okay. Oh, here it is. Okay.
Well, thank you thing that is, I think thing that is gave advice and thank you chat to thank you. You know, we we care about this guy and we're rooting for him. Oh, wow. Look at this queen of cups came up. Okay.
There's a queen of cups. There's somebody I you know, she's having maybe it looks like some coffee. What is that?
What is that or actually blood? Okay, but this is the horse like what do you do the card readings?
Like what do they do though? Just tells you like a story. It's about a story
About the energy it's gonna be like some maybe something have you met somebody in the past like this a woman in the past like a really
It's kind of emotional. Maybe a little bit emotional and
over a drink or something like that this might be the past the recent past or it
could be the present or it could be somebody you're about to yeah somebody
right to meet. I used to have like somebody in the past yeah like a woman I
used to be with before. What happened with her? I don't know I don't know it just ended though
because we've moved away from each other and we don't see each other anymore.
So that might have been like that that Queen of Cups and it's like that she might have been interesting
We have the page of swords. Okay, so this is like people are watching after you and there's like also somebody really
good with words and
It looks like like she has a few people
Interested to and it's like but and she looks like
She might be interested there's like I think she might be how do I say this is a good communicator and a good
Good talker and somebody that likes to talk and it's like but
You also may have felt like
How do I put this this is a tennis because this is a tennis swords the tennis swords is like, you know feeling
maybe rejected rejected or like maybe hurt with words or something like that and
I
think that
You might have some
You might have been hurt by some people. Okay, you might feel like and maybe you trade but it's like maybe you expect too much from them
Let me see
So like you don't get lonely though, right? You said I might get lonely, but do you ever get lonely?
I really, I don't because I have like a whole a whole a lot of people community. I have a whole community. Yeah. I have a whole I have a lot of people to talk to you and so I know I don't get really lonely because I always have I need to talk to somebody.
There's always somebody there always. Yeah, it's like you're my friend still. Yeah, of course. And I always talk to you. So you can talk to me like if you want right.
This one says the Three of Wands. It says you left your castle and are now on an open sea, a place of doubt.
And let me see, just progress on, just progress is being made.
But progress is being made. Okay, you're a sea of doubt and...
Deception but progress is being made. Okay, so the three the three of one says it's like you may be going out into this
Like dating scene and stuff like that and it's like but it's like you may have some self-doubts
You may be alone for a while, but it's like even just putting yourself out there
There's a progress being made and it's like that's a good thing. It's like because it's like that's
You're growing as a person, right?
And so it's even if it's not fun or difficult you're gonna gain experience. What else do we have?
Okay, and there's like a lot of people you are interested in this is like the aid of pinnacle
This is called the apprentice
It means you're gonna start improving improving and like talking to people and there's maybe there's gonna be a lot of people a lot of people that
Are gonna pass you by but there's gonna be but also don't get too hyper focused on somebody
Okay, but you know
Like you mean don't let somebody over control the situation like right like a
Also, this is like someone's gonna like maybe like if you're their princess, it's like somebody can maybe like
Teach you some things and so it's like you maybe you'll you'll be like us just like listen to some good advice
I think some people are giving you good advice. What else do we have?
We have the lovers and so I think that there will be something right like the lovers
There will
This guy is like a kind of a big guy and it says love is grand but always
needs to trouble okay so just know it's not going to get more simple it's not going to be
easier all of a sudden we find somebody it's like not easy to be in relationships all of a
sudden it's like your brother then all of a sudden your brother's girlfriend's like oh you can't
talk to your family anymore all this stuff right and so it doesn't make sense like yeah because
this girlfriend wants to get trolled like you know like everything he does now and he won't get
he she won't let him talk to his family which is me and my mom and stuff like that yeah right after
Yeah, but I agree with you so I agree with you so it's like it's like it's gonna be hard and it's
like you're maybe there's gonna be a lot of people like along the way you're gonna find somebody but
it's like not necessarily gonna be easy but it's gonna be you're gonna be in that relationship right
I think there is a relationship where I'm gonna pull a few more for you
Okay, eight of cups. It's like somebody somebody like far away kind of been approaching and it's like because you see them
You see them in the kind of like in the distance right there
There there maybe somebody like kind of further away from you
So maybe it could be like a long-distance thing that you're talking to them over the over something else
And also we have the magician so you also have some skills. It's kind of looks like you too
You have some skills you have musical skills, right? So musical skills. I'd say definitely if you can
Try to get some kind of drum drum at least if it's the one drum, right? It's tambourine
Okay, you know you love drumming and that's like a big part of you
If you're called Mason the drummer and then there's gonna be people attracted to that talent
You also have the ability you have the ability to to manifest the relationship. What else do I have for you?
Okay, this one is called the two of wands.
It says, are you prepared for your journey?
And so definitely someone's gonna come along
that is evenly matched with like the same interest in you
that you have of them.
So this is kind of a fire, a fire energy,
but also kind of like you will be attracted to someone
and somebody that you'll be able to have a
Kind of an equality with because it's a two, okay
Yeah
We have the which is this?
five of swords, okay five of swords is like
There's gonna be maybe some competition, but I think you can win the competition
but you know
There there may be some people that you will have to beat out for this person. Okay, let me just do two more. Oh
You got a page of wands and this says new ideas new energy limitless potential and free spirit
I think no matter what happens
This might be the person you're gonna meet to it might be someone younger than you
maybe a fire sign, but uh
It's gonna be something new someone like a new person that you've never met before because it's like about new new person
somebody that actually like will
make you passionate or, you know, get you more motivated
and bring out some kind of passionate energy out of you.
Okay, someone that I think you're really attracted to
I see coming, okay.
Yeah, and also with the three of cups and three of cups is about socializing. It's about
You know, I would say maybe he's not even like one person like maybe if you know a couple or something like that
Because then you have the the guy and the woman can give you good advice about that
And then you can go out in a social situation
They might be able to like, you know bring some people your way. I'm gonna pull one more advice from Mason
The emperor so you're gonna come into your power eventually you're gonna like you're gonna learn so much and you're gonna be
You know, you're gonna grow a lot because this is like a lot of Kings energy and
You're gonna be able to I don't know if it's gonna be like some kind of success. You're gonna find like yes
You know what strange what?
Natalie was being weird to me before what she was trying to be naughty and stuff
I could show me her, you know body stuff like that
Psychonist that right though because she's a married woman and I was even explained that to her. Okay. Well, let's
You know what I I don't I don't know about that, but I think she was just you know, I think she was
Being very I think she's being maybe very friendly and maybe you misunderstood. I'm not sure but
Yeah, you have a psyche. Why would she be I'm saying it's like why would she be show me her body when she's already a married woman?
It's like she doesn't need to show like
Sometimes it's like sometimes people will just be more free and they're more like comfortable with their body because it's like we
And as a society we're like very oh, you know, it's like, you know, you have to keep covered up
And some people are just like just just free with it, right?
But Natalie I mean like what I'm saying is like what?
Natalie's doing no it's wrong against God because when you're married you're not supposed to show
anybody your body like another guy that's out there like another.
A little bit judgmental about it I think that she was being friendly I think she was being
friendly and you know I don't maybe she and I don't I don't think she it was too I don't think
she was trying to seduce you or something I think she was being friendly and I see thank you
I didn't mean to, I didn't mean to interrupt you.
It's like, I didn't mean to interrupt you.
You didn't, but you know what strength means?
Strength is like, you know, see he's throwing the line of fish
and then the fish is calm down.
Like, you know, just like throw something out there.
Like, you know, maybe buy a drink or like, you know,
something that could break the tension.
It's like, and also you have some kind of inner strength
and be positive that you can make progress and
But, you know, but don't be too aggressive, you don't want to be like, you know, go rest of the line, you want to give the lion his treat and stuff like that.
And maybe if you feed away, you know, see, he's very careful and then see if the lion comes up to you. Okay.
So, yeah, some good advice for you, you know, I see that there's love in your future.
You can agree with me though, right?
If you're married woman though,
you're supposed to keep that stuff
just for your husband though.
I don't want to judge.
And it's like, you know, some, there's people like,
I think my mom's bachelorette party when I,
not our bachelorette,
I think when she had her baby shower,
someone hired a stripper at a baby shower.
And I don't know if there was,
people were getting in lap dances or whatever,
but it was like, you know,
sometimes people just have fun and let loose
and it's not like that big of a deal,
but it's not supposed to be like,
Saying yeah, it's not supposed to be like anything. It's too serious. It's supposed to be just like just fun
Maybe she's maybe she's like giving you a little thrill and then you can see what you want to do or something
No, but no, but the weird thing is like, you know, I agree with you
I'm seeing the weird thing was she said this stuff too with it
She's like, oh, I want you to be in bed with me because my husband's not the one that's giving me the stuff
I need in bed
She was he was helping you she was trying to give you some confidence maybe because she wants you to have some confidence and
Be able to approach somebody else. It's not gonna be her, but she was gonna like
Maybe something something to make you more confident and you know just like yeah, but psyche. Yeah, but psyche
Why would she tell me that stuff though? Like oh my husband's not giving it to me in the bed
There's a time to like, you know
Think it was a kind of a private moment. It's like you're supposed to go. Shh. It's like it's like you're not supposed to
Tell that's a that's a maybe it was a thing to like make you just feel better and it's like I don't think it was that serious
So let's not talk about it, but yeah, I think okay. Let me see
Okay, we have ace of pentacles. There's gonna be some kind of new beginnings for you
Okay, there's new beginning. I see this and there's something something someone is gonna hand to you
that you could take with you, but not her, right?
It was like something you could take away from it,
like some kind of lesson,
but not, you know, hey, Spunky, what's up?
Hi, sweetie, how are you?
I think, yeah, yeah.
But, you know, sometimes people will,
People want to help you out and stuff so so yeah, but you know she
You know because it's like she's far away, and it's over the internet. It's not as serious, right? It's yeah
Hi, spunky, but you know what Mason? It's like you're gonna get
something to
Something to get the feeling of something and it's like, you know, and she was giving you she was giving you a tip
She was giving you a tip to like go. Yeah, but psyche psyche listen to me. I'm not saying anything wrong
Okay, don't take it like I'm saying something wrong right now
Yeah, and I'm not trying to I'm not trying to get into like any kind of you know mix up with somebody that's married because once you're married
You're supposed to be with just that person you're with right, but why would you why I don't get why she wants me?
Whenever I think it's a misunderstanding. I think it's a misunderstanding. I think it was
She was being very very friendly, okay, and it's like it wasn't meant to like you know
And also you want to you know
Sometimes we have these these fun experiences like people will like you know go out to a bar
They can be married and go to a bar and then
Hi, hi, what's up, Sam? Yeah, they can be friendly and stuff like that, but it's not serious
You know, it's like just kind of like to like
Give you a little confidence. Okay, and so it's gonna take that confidence if you got any confidence from that or got an excitement or something and take that and
Learn from it, and it's like
Psychia I don't understand like why would she would say that kind of
it's okay you know what it's a it's like it was a kind of a party kind of thing it's like a party
atmosphere and it's like you know everyone can go kind of uh she wants to have fun it's like you're
saying she wanted to have fun it's fun over the internet it's like not too serious because it's
just over the internet you know it's like so it's it's just kind of like less serious than in real
life and it's like people can like kind of have fun so there you go so now I have a dance to do
and just remember that we remember all that stuff okay okay okay are you good or yeah it's like
yeah i'm good i'm just saying i'm just confused for a little bit right now not with what you're
saying but just what's going on with the you know things like okay especially one
Especially when, you know, Natalie wants to still talk to me and she doesn't she doesn't really
She's a really good friend because she cares. I think she cares about you and she understands you and
She knows like she I think she just wanted to help you
Get a little calm and she's not shy, you know, it's like I don't think she and I don't think it's like, you know
It was like that
Serious, you know, it was just like kind of like a friendly joke. Okay, and so there you go Mason. Yeah, I
Want to do a reading for for um for reality Nancy. So is it okay? We just hang up for a little bit and you can come back later, okay?
Who me psych yeah, you go in the chat you might have going in the chat for a minute
I want to do Nancy's reading eyes. I just want to make sure I get all her energy that okay
Yeah, so I can want me to come back later. It's what you're saying. Of course. Of course. You're always welcome back
I just I mean I'm gonna wrap those but yeah, you're always welcome Mason and it's like I hope you but I think I gave you a lot of information
And it's like I need you to
Just think about what I said, okay, and think about the things that thing that is said because we gave you a lot of good information
Okay, yeah, I'll think about what you said and what thing that is said
And it's good to practice in the chat to go practice in the chat, okay, okay
Okay, I think people in the chat will talk to you and it's like and then and everyone in the chat
It's like if he goes too far you just tell oh, okay
Yeah, we'll just tell him if you go too far just tell him and it's like then you can help him out
Maybe give him some more bites. Okay, so Nancy. Let's see what I got for Nancy.
I hope you like that, Mason. I did my best. I did my best. Okay.
Reality Nancy. What do we got for Reality Nancy? And I know Nancy best before reading before and
it's like I've gotten off track. I'm sorry about that. Okay. I'm gonna give you a good reading.
Okay. Yeah, go play the stream again. There's so much good information, Mason. So it was a
Okay, I'm gonna go with Nancy, Nancy, Nancy, Nancy.
Okay, Nancy, you got the queen of pentacles.
This is like, you know, this is someone that is materially,
things are coming to, someone that's attached to the earth,
someone sensual, I mean, I think this is you,
this is this queen of pentacles is you.
It's like, this is like, you're brave enough to manifest
these things in the, in the, fix my collar, yeah, I'm sorry.
You're able to manifest these things in the physical world.
Also, you know, you know this one's she's she's wearing a mask. I'm gonna fix the color. There you go
She's wearing a mask. She's wearing a mask, but it's like it's like a bird, right? And so this is all almost like
You have these thoughts that can go off and turn into things
Okay, because your thoughts will turn into things. It's really good manifestation power. You've been really able to
Make your make some of your dreams come true. Just
by letting them fly, right?
What else do we have?
Oh, King of Swords, okay.
This has an absorbing person with intellectual authority,
okay, and traditional.
King of Swords, this could be like a Gemini,
or an Aerosine, a Gemini Libra,
or a Capricorn Aquarius, right?
And let me just turn this down.
He has a big brain, okay?
Aerosines are very smart.
They have a quick mind.
And this could be something so we have a king and a queen
I don't know if you have a man, but it's like and I don't know if you're an earth sign either
But it looks like there's like gonna be a really good communicator
Talker with you. I don't know if he's gonna. You know, he has a big brain. I
Don't know if he's gonna be if he's a bit too nerdy for you
Ten of pentacles. Okay, so this combination could lead to like some wealth some like generational wealth
Especially with the like the queen of pentacles
Manifests things the king of swords can like things of things and since she can bring them down to manifest them
So I don't know if you have that combination. You might have that all within yourself
But it's it looks like it will lead to some wealth for you. Okay, and also this is like it says the ten of pentacles
It's like there's a lot of there. There's a lot of there's a lot of people there, right?
But ten pinnacles is like this generational wealth card. So it's like surrounded by people and also like maybe helping a lot of people
I think you like are helping also other people to manifest
Okay, okay, you can do this, okay?
And you've also been really able to keep balance a lot lately too.
It's like you've been like, even if there's been waves in your life,
you've been able to go with the flow kind of and maintain a balance
even if it's been crazy, okay?
I see that.
This one, it says a journey toward equilibrium.
You're trying, yeah, it's like, you know,
it's gonna go one side, it's gonna go the other side,
but you're really, you're the balancing part of it,
and you're able to,
reminds me of like Libra energy, okay?
What else do we have?
We have this suit of wands, eight of wands.
So this is something that's gonna happen really fast
for you, some kind of information communication.
It says change is coming,
something is in the air, action, the time is now.
where will you be when the big event happens, okay?
So this is something that's gonna come really fast.
I don't know, it's like you're gonna,
I see you're like calm and balanced
and something, some big energy coming fast
and it's like, what will it be though, okay?
This is a, okay, 10 of wands, okay?
Um, maybe like it seems like 10 of wands is usually kind it says it's yeah
Obviously, I just thought I saw I thought burden and it's like this is on the card
It says burdens is who will carry the burden? Okay, so it's not necessarily a bad thing
But it's like I do think you carry a lot of other people like and you maybe you carry a lot of stress
And maybe that's what you're trying to keep balanced of but it's like maybe a little heavy of a load
It's eight of ones and ten of ones. Okay. Yeah, something coming really fast and you feel like you have to carry it all
But you don't have to, you can always put it down.
And the burden is just burdensome
because it's like all these wands, but it's not heavy.
Okay, because it's one, it's like a bunch of sticks,
but it's like, you carry stress a lot, yeah.
And so that, and you might feel like lately,
like a lot of stress is coming to you.
Okay, but you have that balance,
you have that good equilibrium, okay?
So you're able to carry it in like a balance
that load on you, okay?
Ooh, and we have a king. Is this another king? Hold on. Yeah, we have another we have a king of wands
And so this is like another guy. This one says vision honor leadership ultimate masculine energy
So this is like a really masculine man
Coming towards you and he's like kind of maybe like a little bit dark a little bit a
Little bit fiery passionate somebody that's been really you passionate. I'm not I'm not sure about your relationship or whatever
This king of wands is like he's really passionate and fast so fast making decisions. Okay nine of cups
That that I think this guy's gonna help you relax a lot
Nine of cups is like all of a sudden it's like just like not
Not sitting up worrying. It's like just relaxing and being able to like
To to finally relax about something. I don't know. I think this person was gonna help you relax about something. Okay
Doesn't always right doesn't all oh, yeah
None of these cards mean something bad like none of them. I think there's always like a pot
There's always it always a shadow and a light to every card
I like to I like to look at the light side. What is this? Okay?
We do have a tower coming. It's like so you're gonna relax. There might be
Another sudden change. I see like some kind of sudden change and not necessarily a bad change. It says
They were young healthy and sorry young healthy wealthy beautiful
Free and in love until tonight reminds me of I'm just seeing Rocky or picture show
I'm hearing Janet Janet like damn it Janet
And then this is like but it's like some kind of like in a dark and stormy night and like going to is like some kind of
Don't the car breaks down or something coming to some kind of house for an adventure. Okay
Ace of Swords, and that's the truth. This is the truth truth card. Okay, or also you're gonna learn the truth
This is something will something big will happen that will show you the truth
Okay, yeah, because the ace of swords is it's a sort of truth, right? I'm gonna do three more
Ten of cups this will lead to a lot of happiness for you learning this truth will like lead to like
Your ultimate this is like whatever one wants and this is like the 10 of cups is like basically just not
Because you already got the pen 10 of pentacles 10 of pentacles and the 10 of cups that is like
the happily ever after kind of thing and this is like also
It's been some family something in the family stuff will really improve. Okay
Something there's some relationship that we healed maybe okay, and then
Seven of swords
You want to protect protect your happiness there might be somebody looking at it a little bit jealous and wanting to take it
Okay, so you want to protect it? Okay, which you can do
Seven of cups is there's gonna be a lot of options for you a lot of options and they're all gonna look
Appealing there's gonna be a few whammies in there. There's gonna be a few, you know
cars behind the curtain like they're so you're gonna want to go tour with
You're most attracted to you're gonna you will find
The car or the the good curtain you'll find the good curtain. Maybe it's a
New house or something. Okay. Oh the world you're gonna be ending this cycle too
Successfully and this is so I'm now I'm thinking of like things are getting wrapped up
I'm getting the idea of
You came for this lifetime to like tie up all these loose ends
It's like you're getting a lot of karma done in this lifetime like in it
So you're gonna be finishing the cycle going into a new cycle a new life
The Empress all four Queens this will lead to you this ultimate
It says she's she has everything a woman needs and in abundance and she's the one
With the forces of the mystical realms of the universe, so don't forget this you are all the queens in the deck
You have all the elements you are the you and you will be the ultimate Queen
Because you will come out of this cycle whatever the cycle is you're gonna come out of it
With everything you're gonna come out with everything you want it, okay
Just protect it and do one more card one more card for advice advice for Nancy
The chariot and that this is the car car right it says
The warrior drives at night under crescent moon. No hands on the wheel. He sears by force of will and so
Wow, that's gonna be a powerful combination
I need to pull one more card for that because the Empress plus the chariot is like you're gonna be in this Empress energy
Which is all the Queens all the elements and then it's like you're gonna be full speed ahead about something
I want to find out. What is that? What is she full speed ahead about? Can I get an answer for that, please?
What full speed ahead to what what is she going towards?
The sun ultimate happiness. Okay. That's the ultimate happiness
Empress versus chair because it's on I don't think there's like even a better combination, right?
It's like it's like full speed ahead
Towards your ultimate happiness. I hope you like that Nancy
Play this back. Okay
Think about that. I hope you like that
How's everyone doing in chat?
Thank you, Alex, you know Alex did sponsor for you know, I said another hour, but I I'm
I'm sure it's been an hour, so I'm gonna keep continue going because I still have another half a beer
Hope you like that Nancy. Let me see
You see I need to close this thing. Oh
Where am I? Oh there I am, okay
Oh, nice read. Okay. Good. I'm glad you did. You're welcome
You want to you want one spunky or Alex or anybody. Oh, we have a guest Queen Natalie's here
Oh, it's gonna come up in a minute Natalie's really awesome. Yes, you would okay. I got spunky too that one's for spunky. Let me get these
Let's see, oh here, it's this one.
Yes.
Hello, I was just wondering, can you do me the reading, please?
Yes, it's Bucky, I'll do you right after, OK?
I got you right after, OK?
And then I got you, OK, let me get to you.
It's Bucky.
I'm curious to see what cards I get.
Mason's second skin, OK.
I got you, OK.
Hello Sean!
You're the Hierophant and so there's been some kind of like...
Interest in like some kind of higher tradition or something like that. It's like or a really strong connection to God
I always think of this as the God card
It's like some connection to God and also like this like also seeing God or like, you know this vision like
He sees through the material world through your very skin it says okay, and so this could be your energy or
Also someone looking at you right, but this is like the higher the higher fan is this connection to the higher
This is really good connection to the the divine that you have and you're able to see through the veil
Right you can see through the veil and I know that but that makes so much sense right now. Okay
You said we had the five of pentacles you've been feeling like maybe left out of something let's out in the cold or like you know
excluded maybe from something
The five of pentacles you can always like go knock on that door
but
Maybe feeling like well this woman looks like she's kind of a she's kind of a seller or something like that like feeling kind of
like left in like
In the basement or something like that, but it's like I don't think the basement door is locked
And so it's like, you know, I think you can like leave that but maybe even
feeling
feeling like a little bit
Separated from something
You also have, okay, what is this?
Give me three of pentacles.
Okay, three of pentacles.
You've been working really hard on something
and some people are taking notice.
You've been perfecting some kind of craft
or you're working on something
and then you've improved so much.
Now people are wanting to work with you
about with this particular skill you have
or something like that.
It also tells me that it's like,
from the five of pentacles, it's like,
Maybe you're feeling left out, but it's like someone's gonna see someone's gonna see you someone's gonna recognize you someone's gonna
Someone's gonna want to
Pull you out of this. Maybe two people. I do see like a few minutes. What does this card say?
Okay, it says they work together to create perfection. So this is we're also working with some people you could possibly working with some people on something
To create something really cool. I'm not sure what that is. What is that?
Okay, so we have this is the what of sorts oh the five
Five of sorts. Okay, so this says a brutal victory. Okay, so maybe you
Maybe there might be some some kind of competition with these people
But I see you coming out as a victor of it and it's like because you know the truth
And it's like, and then you have this she has a head right there. See she she ends up with the taking the taking the head
So she so she definitely has
Victory on that, okay
And we got another five five of wands. And so this is also some kind of like competition or something
And I do think you'll win this competition. It's like but it's like a friendly competition. It's like not like
It's like it's like maybe a fight, but it's like a it's like a good nature fight. Okay
I'm gonna do a few more
Okay, well, there's been some heartbreak too. I see like, you know, three of swords is like some kind of heartbreak or some kind of like, you know
Some hurt in your heart
Yeah, because uh, yeah
Heal, but it's like it is very it's like, you know, this pierce the heart and it's like difficult
We have the wheel of fortune that's gonna lead to something
Your luck is gonna improve. There's gonna be some good fortune
Not it I think it's I think it's from I think from this competition that I see it's like there
There could be some some good luck coming from that and fortune. Okay, and it's like so the wheel of fortune will go in your favor
Okay, and then
We have the seven of pentacles and it says look upon my world, okay?
And it's like this is like mastery of your environment and also like, you know
Coming almost a center of attention and there's all these hands reaching up towards you. It's like and it's like almost like
It's like you're not you're in a really good place and you're you're in it. You'll go to an elevated place, right?
Or and it's like there's gonna be these hands reaching for you
And it's like because they're you're gonna have you carry this light and they they're seeing this light and they're like
You're bringing things up from worlds like you're bringing things up from maybe maybe the lower worlds
Maybe take you remind me of that woman on this statue of liberty. Yeah
Freedom freedom and it's like you're like you're calling people to freedom and you're like
you're like saying, hey, like, come here.
And it's like, people want this.
And it's like, and you have this actually,
you have the freedom.
And it's like, maybe you can bring people to freedom too.
Because the statue of Liberty is like calling
everybody out to her, right?
But that does look like the statue of Liberty a lot.
Because she does this carry the torch and the light, right?
And it's like, and so pulling people,
Out, out, out, out.
We're also the key.
You know what?
That is my personality, exactly,
because I try to save everybody,
including fallen angels, you know?
So that is my personality, to be honest.
Yes, like helping people redeem,
like helping people that were maybe in some kind of hell,
and it's like,
Leading them out like they see the light like showing people the light and helping helping helping
We have the king of pentacles. It says the man who has everything. Okay
So this is like, you know a man with the Ableton manifests
Materially, but it's always I find it's always like the king of pentacles always has this this queen of pentacles
Helping and manifest it's like the I think the woman is like like really helps that process of
manifestation, okay, and so
The person has everything. It's because of the queen. I'm sure
New journey the fool look at the and it's like the fool. Oh, yeah
But it's like also, you know taking the leap of faith it says take the step so there might be some kind of new journey
You're gonna be barking on to you and I get like maybe some kind of new path
but
In a leap of faith that you should take, you know
It's like because it can be scary and it can be like oh what will happen, but it's like it's not really falling up a cliff
It's like
Falling into space like I think everybody that that is comes into this world comes as the fool like and
So it's almost like going to a new world, okay?
But we have the four of pentacles this is called the collector, okay, and so
Well this particular card has he's collecting
These women, but it's like I think you I think you can collect some kind of
something you can collect these attributes or you can
something
in the physical realm too and that
you that
You find a lot of her and you find easy to come to okay. Let me see you just three more
Temperance. Okay, but take it easy. Okay
Stay balanced. Don't go too too far to either extreme and stay balanced. Okay, and
this one says your life is in the balance and
Earth and water
Spirit material life and death everything and moderation. Okay, and so it's like
Don't if you're if you are collecting something or I
Almost get the feeling of collecting souls or something like that, but not in a bad way
But it's like it's like be in moderation. It's like because I think you're very very powerful and it's like
Yeah, yeah, so you can keep so
Balance and also like it's like alchemist car too. It's also the earth angel car and I okay, and it's like but being able to
Transmute energies positive to negative negative to positive not positive negative negative to positive like I'm being able to turn
turn something
By combining some with something else into something really good and also ace of cups, okay?
And so this is like this new thing handed to you
It's gonna make you really happy and it's like a cup of blood right there, but it's like there's some kind of
some kind of thing handed to you,
because there's this hand handing to you, okay?
And so this is like some new blood,
it's a new life, something that can grow into,
something that can make you really happy, okay?
I'm gonna pull two more.
Ooh, we have the Nine of Pentacles. It says in the lap of luxury. Okay. And so this is the Nine of Pentacles
It's always this it's a woman and it's like I know you're Capricorn. This is a very
This is like three and the three of Pentacles is Capricorn, too
But so the Nine of Pentacles is almost like three threes. I'm a Capricorn. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and
This one is so this is like just abundance around you. There's gonna be abundance and all good things around you
Oh, he's growing around you. I see like birds flying to your finger and stuff. It's like I'm seeing like snow white right now
I kept having a Robin visit me. Oh
Robin
It was so strange
And it visited my sister as well. It's Robin. Wow
Robins red is a red red Robin. Yeah
The virtue of the messengers, you know,
you also have the, we have the nine of wands.
One says survival is a matter of perseverance
and vice versa, perseverance is a matter of survival.
And I think you are a survivor.
And it's like, I think no matter what difficulties
or anything you go at it, you're just so strong
and you persevere, you're gonna get through
any kind of obstacle, you're gonna also
What is this is it like?
I'm not sure what horror movie this is from but it's like a like a it's like a closed door
But it's like you will be able to get through it. You'll be able to get through because it's not not a
Not like a solid door. It's like, you know, I'm just made of these sticks and so
Also, I would I see you're protected. You're like really protected and
But you are a survivor. This is God does protect me a lot. So I mean, I've done stupid things in the past
Where I've got drunk and I've been messing around with demon and right side
And I don't get possessed one day and then God sent these policemen who were angels
Don't rescue me
Did you pray for them or did you like or was it like no, no, it's just being stupid
You know like playing chicken was saying
Chicken was saying and I'm saying look at my soul saying it's a hook
There's like a team
There's like a team behind you of like angels, you know, like
You will face like a lot of these other other entities and it's like and so it's like
Back up. I'm gonna pull one for you
Basically, I was testing the devil
Yeah
I was testing the devil's power
Is there something like also like keeping you up at night or something like that because and I because I see like you know
You're awake in the bed like and then it's yeah, I'm awake most nights
Just I'm very hyperactive my mind works over time
So I don't get sleep. I'm gonna pull one more
Okay, and then we have the, what number is this?
The Six of Swords, which is like moving on to calmer waters.
It's like, you know, it's like, you might be like,
you know, having an intense time
and like a lot of stuff happening,
but it's like,
I don't know if it's necessarily a physical move, but it's also like it can be in the astral realm
It's like there's not only progress, but it's progress from the rough waters to the calm waters
And so I believe that you will be reaching these calmer waters that you've been looking for and like that
I don't know if it may be a move
Physical move or something, but it's definitely like moving away from something into something else
And it's like the thing that you're moving to is gonna bring you a lot more peace. So
I'm gonna pull one more one more
Okay, four of cups. And this is just like very, this is like very in control. You're coming into control of your emotions and also being like being very intellectual about something. And I think maybe this is the advice is to like Africa varies from to be honest.
Because she's very serious. She's very serious about something like very serious, but also like
And also like look there's there's an entity there too in the dark like right there like bringing something to like something
She's been like hmm and then it's like there's gonna be a
You bring you a gift like it's like it looks like there's some kind of I don't know if you can see it
I mean turn off my my my background a little bit because I can see the cup clearly
Yeah, okay
Hello Mason
here we go. Don't worry, I'm not angry or upset with you for telling all my business.
It's like, remember you described the other night and it's like someone in the dark and
it's like someone in the dark and it's like bringing, there's bringing something, they're
bringing something to you. And uh, just, uh,
But it's like keep that balance and the four is a good balance card like you know
So keep that balance of like rationality and spirit, but yeah, there's like there's a gift being brought to you right there
like that will like like
Maybe surprise you because maybe I don't know if you're
You still need something you're there's a lot of rationality, but there's something that's gonna also something handed to you
I mean keep really happy right there. And so
They look out for that
Okay, I think that yeah, I believe that's it and let's see
And also it's like you're looking she's looking in the opposite direction
Like she's looking in the other direction like it's something over there. It's like right over the other shoulder
It's like right over it's like right
Right, right. It's like so it's like maybe you're looking at something
That seems far away, but it's like right behind you. It's like right behind you. So it's something that's like
Also, but I think it like the thing this one is like
This satisfaction they bored him and then someone bringing you the fifth cup, right?
Or the fourth cup because you got those three cups that you have already
Like and it's like yeah, I've had that I've had that I've had that and it's like oh there's some there's you're like
I'm bored with that. No, there's something that's gonna like wake you wake you up into like excitement again about it
So just be ready for that cup to like appear and ready to take it because it's like, you know
It's like from boredom to there's gonna be something that's gonna make you excited again
And this was what this can grow into something. I hope you like that
Play this back play this back and like look at the cards and also, you know
See what they see how you feel about it because you are also like extremely psychic. It's like I feel it
It's like I feel your energy. Yeah
There's been times where like
You know like when the radio station when
Like it's Tom comes to the radio
Sometimes it comes to my mind before it goes to the radio. Oh, it does. Yeah
How are you good are you I'm pretty good it's been a little crazy, but for me
Yeah, I'm sorry. Well, I had um
Someone's been sending people looking for scrap metal to my house yesterday. Oh
That's nice. Yeah, I got woken up by it with like and they also said
Oh, make sure you knock really loud on the door and keep knocking because my grandfather's inside there asleep or something like that
Oh my god
But
Let's see. I got one for Spunky too. This is Natalie. This is Natalie's in England.
Hi, Natalie.
Hi, darling.
See, Mason introduced me.
But we should drop down while you give her a reading.
Thank you, Natalie. I love you. Have a great night. We like to read.
Let's see what we got for you, Spunky. How are you doing? Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm doing better. Justin came back around.
I apologize. He did. He's sitting next to me now.
See.
Hi, Justin.
Hi.
Hi. Okay.
That's good
And oh you see I'm in my I'm in my my priest outfit today. Yes. I love it. Someone said you look like Count Chocula
Father psyche father psyche
We lost psyche Ari sorry sorry. Oh, he's back. Yeah, I accidentally
That of my mouse, okay
Look at your is never gonna believe that
Too bad to my city too, so it's like oh
Yeah, unfortunately heard them squeaking and like then I heard a crunch. Oh
We got first spunky, let's see
Okay, so we got the ace of pentacles. Okay, so this is something being handed to you like a new beginning
It's the ace of pentacles and it's also something that will it's like a seed that will grow too
It's like but it's like, you know, it's been handed to you so it's in your hand
Okay, something that's been handed to you very recently. What does this say? It says
Man of
Manifesting your material goals, okay something that okay, so you're going to be
Materially you're getting what you wanted. Okay. You also have the three of pentacles. Okay. This is they work together to create perfection
Okay, and so this is working together with somebody
Okay
We have the six of wands which six of wands is a victory
So it's a win and it's his victory at all costs, but it's like it is it is the victory though
Okay, and so
And this is what it's movies is from
It's the one where he wears those glasses and you see he sees the truth about things
So you have also I would say some kind of like site beyond the veil where you can see the true
Character of people or see the truth about people that not everybody can see
And then you're it will lead to a win. Okay
Yeah, I'm a pretty good judge of character
Two of cups. So this is like a cheers. This is like also romance. This is like coming together with your equal partner right there
And then some kind of romance and the two of cups is like this
it's like they love each other at the exact same amount and
So it's a good. It's a perfect match. I'd say, okay
Seven of wands and so this is fighting off fighting off something
Okay, and I said this one says trapped and but who is the monster because it's like Frankenstein plus the town people and so
It's like who is like the mob the monster or the or the monster the monster, right?
But the monster is only trying to defend himself, right and yeah, right?
but um, but it's also it's also being on the defense, but it's also not
Because there's a nine, which is very, nine of ones is very similar, but he has like a bandage around his head.
So it's like that's like kind of traumatized. And so this is not traumatized. This is still like
your confident energy, okay?
And in
being defensive for like a smart reason, okay?
We have the Queen of Wands. This is Courage, Confidence, Independence, and Determination.
Okay, I would say that those qualities fit you. It isn't
Norman Bates' mother and everything, but
it's a Queen of Wands. It's like, you know, coming into like this great mastery of your passions
and also
being able to
Be courageous at any circumstance that comes towards you deep being brave and laughing in the face of
adversity I would say laughing like laughing and also like a strong determination
Yeah, that's you the high priestess too. I wish I yeah, I always pull that card. Yeah
So the high priestess it's a you know this is well number two but you know the
high priestess and she's kind of a nun a nun in this deck and she she knows
everything just but it's like see in her heart because it's like that the fire in
her heart it's like that it's like and I almost see like that
Same, it kind of like mirrors you right now to me for some reason.
I see that very strongly.
It's like very, very strong.
Okay.
And so you know, and you know, you're like very psychic intuitive yourself and you know
a lot of things and you hope you hold the truth too.
And then we have the Night of Wands.
Okay, this is Passion, Adventure, Impulse,
and Inspired Action, okay?
And so this is like some kind of new movement forward
and it's almost like more, it's like more inspired
and more passionate than I was.
It's like a new rise in passion, okay?
I hope maybe a call to adventure.
Maybe, okay, we also have the Page of Cups.
Page of Cups is like, it's some kind of like very,
usually it has like a cup with a fish in it,
maybe a fishy offer, like, you know,
but also the cups can grow into something
that can make you very happy,
but yeah, you can filter out the fish, right?
And then, or put the fish in a tank.
The star, you got the star power too.
You know, like some kind of brilliance in your mind,
and then pouring it out.
To others pouring out into the world bringing good things to the world
Good energy into the world. It's like and also you're bright
You're so bright that it's like you have light to spare and it's like because this I think the
This is like not only of just water
But also of light that you're able to share and it's like and it's just like abundant and it's coming from that
From from the top of your head like I see the crown chakra starting to like open up like the very top of your head like like opening up
Okay
um six of pentacles also it's a spirit of charity it's like you're super generous and
know like who where to give it and it's like and it's like also this indicates that you'll
have this abundance to have enough to share so it's like look it's like this one is like pouring
out and this one it's like it's like all this is like all just being able to give and it's like I
And so you're pouring that out into the world.
Hey man, you may feel like you're stuck a little bit.
It is like you're, but it's like,
this is also like seeing things
from a different perspective.
It says, we dare you to look at the world
from his point of view.
Okay.
And so maybe putting yourself in someone else's shoes
or taking some time to be still
and to just observe in a different,
A different state of mind and a different point of view. Okay. Yep. Absolutely. That's why I'm a forgiving person
We have a
Night of pinnacles and this one says slow and steady wins the race. Okay, and so
The nine the night of pinnacles. He's kind of like a little bit of his he's like the he's a he's a
It's a slower moving energy, but it's like
It's like the turtle and the turd is in the hair that wins the race, right? It's like and so
Maybe something's been feeling like it was kind of slow, but it's like ultimately is for
the for the best and then
Judgment is being called it's like this trumpet is being blown
It's like put down your pencils the test is over and it's like it's time to like you know
The carmer's gonna be divvied out or something. I think the judgment is will be going in your favor and pull three more
Okay, and you might not necessarily
See but you this is a crossroads in this one. What does this say it's featuring?
Okay
Wow, this is by my glass. Okay, this one says
Okay, it says featuring indecision dilemma and potential risk, okay
So there may be something you don't have all the you don't have all the answers about it
And it's like maybe a risky situation
But you have to have the faith about it because it's like
Because you ultimately hold the scissors where you're able to cut away what doesn't serve you two more
Okay, it's a gate, so we have, okay, well actually, okay.
So we have the Knight of Swords.
Let me get through the glasses again, where to put them?
No, here we go.
This is very small. It says this one's featuring ambition quick thinking and a drive to succeed
Okay, so I think this is this reminds me a lot of the when we just pulled
Yeah, see because it has these three right there. And so those three qualities will get you through those those three right there
so I would say
The indecision is related to something with ambition
the your quick thinking will solve the dilemma and then
the potential risk will give you the drive to succeed, okay?
So there may be a risk,
but it's like you're willing to take the risk
and that will give you the power to succeed.
Ultimately, the King of Cups is like this,
the King of Cups is someone that's mastered their emotions,
is welcome to the world of the emotionally balanced man,
okay?
and so that's me yeah okay Justin said that's me and I was like no that's me yes well yeah
and it's like but it's like and then with the two of you I can also be like the
balance in that and also like after like you know imbalance
The the balance and the calm the calm after the storm. It's not I didn't I was usually the calm before the storm
I get the calm after the storm. Yeah, absolutely. It's over
Yeah, yeah, and so and then so it's like calm you're gonna be going to calmer waters and
You know also, I see just like very balanced and very very confident and also
No, all the negatives will lead to positives like the negatives will lead to positives like all the
Indecision will lead to like making a decision, right? It's like not being able to decide. We'll like it will push you to making this
Yeah, you need to make it a sum
So that's it. So I hope you like that. Thanks. Thank you. Appreciate it. Oh
Pleasure. All right. I'm gonna hop down. I'll be in the chat. Bye honey. Love you too. Bye
That was fun
Would
Jamie's Cowboys, what's I hope you and Mason are doing okay like oh
My god, I smell my tiktok open. There's a really cool guy on tiktok
He's always really nice to me. He's a straight guy
on tiktok, it's really funny like um
You can give away. Oh, sorry. Oh, let me see you can give away on tiktok. You can I need to fix my collar
You can give away these like gifts, right?
And then, but you know, I like, you know,
there's a lot of hot guys I'll take a second.
So if I give them a gift,
there we go.
Even a straight guy will be very thankful, right?
Hey, Paige.
Paige is here.
I wish I could show you this.
Let me see if I can, I don't have almost one.
Thank you
Page I'll have to tell you that I was surprised for page, but it's like I
have to I have to wait a little bit but
To be a good surprise, but I hope your page. Have you been on your channel?
I know I know you've been really going through some stuff. I'm sorry
What's under my hood?
Alex what do you want to see you don't want to see that you don't want to see that you know, it's my speedo
But I
Showed it a few times. What's under my hood? It's like what's the same thing that's under a kill? Oh my god. I'm going too far
But I just step on oh my god
It broke my glasses
Fuck well at least they were only three dollars that's why I buy three dollar glasses because it's break fuck
I just, maybe I can glue them.
Hopefully I can glue them.
Oh my God.
Well, there goes my glasses.
I'm gonna be wearing my Jeffrey Dahmer's from now on.
I felt a snap.
Damn it.
I love these glasses.
I need to order some more.
Let me see how they broke.
Oh no.
Well, I can actually wear them like this.
They still work.
It's just like they're more like monocles
or something like that.
I think they still work.
You don't need to work like you don't need to fucking other side of them. They think they're perfect like this, right?
They're not they look fine. Oh
Shit
Well, they were cool
Well, whatever. That's why buy everything on Timu, right?
Just buy everything on Timu
$3, you know, I can buy another pair. Okay
That's why unless you unless you have like titanium glasses then
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. We're fighting it. Let me play some kind of happy song.
I'll get the mood back up.
Let's see.
I need to make more songs, huh?
I have like three albums full, but I know all the songs already. Let me see.
This one.
Got that one.
Let's do this.
Psyche yes, I know you told me it does not let the chat bother me
But there's people that are actually saying like weird stuff to me and mean stuff to me and I can't take it
Okay, amazing. Maybe sometimes you don't have to read the chat
If it gets too much, but but thank you. I was just being normal
I was just trying to have a normal conversation and just trying to relax and chill and hang out and stuff with you
Don't get upset. Hold on one second. Let me look at the chat
But psyche they're saying stuff that's like like me and hateful
That's why I was saying the stuff that I said to them if you read it
Natalie and I are friends okay, it's a calm down Natalie give advice for mason
Time out to meet hanged out Mason for a minute. That's I was gonna tell you something about that
It's like yeah, I did nothing to deserve that
I was just trying to have a conversation that somebody said something to you know upset me and make me mad
But I didn't want to get that
They're trying to get the other try to get the best of me and stuff like that. Okay, I didn't understand any of that though, man
Okay, you know what?
It's like yeah, I have mental problems. Yeah, people don't understand that it's like I have mental problems
And I can't help it. You know I'm saying sometimes. It's okay. It's okay calm down. Okay, you know what I?
think that I
Don't I don't see like
People will who was something's going bad?
Mason threatening to beat up a female. Did you threaten somebody Mason?
No, I just told him to leave me alone. They want to stop. So I said just don't make me, you know, get mad as much as I said
Yeah, well, okay. He might have thought Jamie's Cowboys is a guy because sometimes I thought of the guy. Yeah, psyche
I thought I was a guy. I didn't think it was a woman. Okay. He didn't know
Guys, you know, it's the internet sometimes we can't we're not like in the same in the same room
We don't always know he didn't know
So he was a mistake. So I got it. No, that was a woman
Okay, can you can you apologize to Jamie?
Yeah, we have a cycle. Can you tell that person to not say anything hateful to me if I do apologize?
Walk him yourself
I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at everybody, I don't want to laugh at
You know, it's like, I'll be here, like I'll always talk to you and stuff like that.
People that will, um, yeah, I think that you, uh...
Maybe people misunderstood I'm not sure let me look at it. Let me see. I wasn't trying to psyche
I wasn't trying to do anything wrong. Seriously. I was just trying to be myself
But there's people that say stuff that I couldn't believe they would say stuff that I never even imagined him saying to me
Like what did I do for them to say stuff like that to me? I'm just I'm just hanging out just being normal
Just chilling just relaxing
They see you're very like, you know, you got really really upset and stuff like that and then maybe you'll say things that you don't
You come out of your income did you type them faster than you then you're thinking right right?
I know I know I know you don't mean it and stuff like that. You're not trying to be like I don't mean any harm
It's like yeah, I really don't mean any harm. Yeah guys guys he
You know, he's he doesn't he doesn't mean it like you have to like give him a little bit of give him a little bit space
I think he has good intelligence and
He's like I have good intentions. It's like I don't mean any harm or anybody
He doesn't I don't I don't think he I don't think he meant to harm me. He's upset the guys and guys you know what you want to
Be tread tread care tread tread more lightly. Okay, this be the
Mason you know what it's his experience and it's they'll make you stronger and you learn
sometimes maybe you say something that maybe offend somebody and then it's
like and then they'll get and it's like especially in my chat too is a little
bit gruff for
Crowd sometimes, but I don't have to get skin Mason
What'd you say to her thick skin? She said thank you. So I got in here that like out of here with Natalie
You have to get big make you have to get thick skate skin in this world
I mean, I gotta be tougher than that now you're saying I have to be tougher than that right with words
Yes, you have to be very tall very tall
I'm I'm I'm not a strong person though Natalie. I've been with my mom a lot of my life
So it makes me do I am so that's why I am that way. I
Think your mom was probably pretty strong, you know, I think your mom was probably
You've not
Let's not cry about it. You've had it really good
You've had life really good
And it could always be worse, you know
Yeah, it'll make you stronger. I think it's like being able to like, you know, deal with some people that maybe are not like the friendliest always, you know
It's like I have to deal. I deal with some not friends like you. How do you deal with that though? What makes you have to deal with it?
Well, you know, it's like
don't always deal with it the best way because everybody has feelings and
everybody sometimes gets triggered and stuff like that and sometimes people
will even say things that they know that will upset you and stuff like that so
you just have to say you know like I don't you have to not care what
necessarily if people say bad things you have to just say you know I'm a you
just know who you are and nope know you have friends and
I didn't see that going on, but Saki Saki. Can I say something man? Yes. Yes
I know I could always have it worse like Natalie was saying, but I'm not really I'm not trying to expect anything worse
But people are making things worse for me with some of the
You've got you've got clean clothes on your body you've got a warm house you've got food in your belly
just don't think about the dreaded bad things because your life is pretty good
you look like you have a well life you might not be really
Natalie I could Natalie I can't put up the hate though from people though I
don't like anybody being like disrespectful to me well even Jesus was
hated so there you go you're not gonna get everybody who loves you or likes you
Yeah, no people could do no Nellie people could do what they want. They could like
Some people of these chaps probably wasn't brought up with any love
Maybe I had my mom Nelly. I had my mom in my life and I've been raised the right way in the
Maybe maybe somebody's jealous of your life
Might be jealous of it
Love them, you know
Mason, like when someone says something bad, you know, you just either you can block them in the chat if they sort of said to you
You can like say yeah, but psyche. How could I do that?
So I keep looking at you that don't say time me out though. I couldn't say anything more than time me out
mods mods
Can you not not time Mason out and just like tell me and I'll talk to him something but just say
Or just say Mason chill out if he goes too far or something like that
And I think just say it in a nicer way because it's like he's not
He doesn't like people talking to him in a in a rude way. He doesn't understand and you know, it's like I haven't been that way
Everybody I talk to you psyche. They take advantage of me, but people like to talk to me too, but they're not being that way
Okay, I'm not taking advantage of you. You're making out that I'm taking advantage of you. You asked but no, I never said that
No, nally. I never said that you have nothing to do with pictures
Nally has nothing to do
Nally has nothing to do with you. I'll tell him
No, it's not your fault now. You have nothing to do with it. I'm just being nice
Natalie's no Natalie. I know you're being nice. Natalie. I know you're being nice. I'm just understanding people Mason
You gotta understand that
Everybody's nice in this job because not everybody's not a nice life
Some people can understand that
So
Nelly I don't have a problem here. I'm trying to explain to you what's going on. I'm just trying to explain to you
What's going on?
That's what I'm doing about it. You don't want to learn to love people that don't love you
Is it even if you don't have a wrench mason you can still click on your name
And then if they bother you it says block and then you don't have to see their chat. Okay, but what's I do?
I have to be I have to be a mod
You don't have to be a mod, no, you just click it is like I don't have to be a log. No, you just click on their name
It will say report or block and just click on block
And it's like you won't see any of their any of their chats and then
Then it's like they're got it's pretty much gone. And so I do that
I do that because today I was in a chat and it's like everything everyone was saying most people were saying was kind of bad
But yeah, it really bothered me.
I would just block and then I don't even see it.
And then it's like, it's not even like relevant.
And so, but you don't have to, you can just block.
Because I know maybe you block as a,
if you block as a mod, it blocks them from the whole chat.
You just block them as a regular person in the chatter.
It'll just block them from you.
And so,
but how can I do this?
Like if they taught me out though,
cause I can't say anything or do anything.
It's having you out, you can still do it.
You can just, you just click on their name.
and then put block.
It will say block and then you won't see their comments
and then in everybody in the chat, if he bothers you,
you can click block two and he's not gonna say,
you won't see your comments and so he won't see you.
And so, you know, just like do that, okay?
Can you guys do that?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's no big deal.
Don't cry.
It's like, I don't know.
It hurts.
Like sometimes it hurts when people say mean things,
but it is the internet and they can say anything
and it's like, you're not in the same room.
So,
I know it's a little harsh, but sometimes, yeah.
You know, there's there's gonna be people good people like Natalie and
Nice people and you want to just see the nice comments and stuff like that. And if yes
Psyche, that's what I'm expecting. I'm expecting to see like the good things. I don't want to see any bad comments Psyche
I don't want anybody to say something
Anything about all the bad comments, but you can you can like just block the person
Like how they're talking and then you just block you just push block and try it you can try it on somebody
And I don't even block it myself. I just block it from my mind and just ignore it. Yeah, or you can ignore it
You don't have you have to block it. You just like don't read it if it says like okay. Just like okay
Because
Yeah, so I can I could do that
Yeah
It's not that it's pretty easy and it's like, you know
It's easier
Being comments and if they're mean to you, but you know
I do I do think, you know, Mason's a little bit sensitive and so everyone should like, you know, just
Fillings I keep yeah, it's like it hurts my feelings
What's it, you know, and it's like but you're you know what it's gonna make you stronger, too
And that's what I really want for you
I really want you to be able to like go anywhere and like have anyone say anything and you're gonna be okay, okay?
I know yeah, okay
because
Wow, I got stronger being I got a lot stronger dealing with
Not everybody is going to be in a good mood. Some people have had shit in their life.
I think he's going to do that. I think he's going to do that.
Yeah, I mean, he's a sweet guy, but, you know, it's like water up a duck's back and ignore.
And people, if he bothers you, you can block him, too.
And it's like, nobody won't even know, you know, it's like...
And so, not in a mean way, but it's like, just like...
It's not in the comments because his comments can you know, it's like words can hurt sometimes
Some people need
Kindness, you know, like I
Believe in kindness and it's like even if someone bothers you. It's like
Try to be as kind as you I know I'm not always
A lot of Christians because I think
a lot of Christians are very piloty.
I know, well, it's like so funny, like Jesus,
like the message of Jesus is so different
from a lot of the modern day followers
or the people that are out there.
It's like,
Well, I don't think Jesus would have cared for a lot of his followers, you know, they're a little bit
Jesus said be kind and be be gentle
He brought a message of love and I really even if no matter like what religion I am or what I believe
I think he loves you regardless and there ain't no bloody hell
That's all I lie by television and all bullshit and churches because they want to make loads of money
You have a good heart, you mean it's like and it's like I know
It hurts it hurts me to see him upset and
You know, maybe I hope I haven't been too hard and it's like, you know
I've been told like oh, he's not like don't it's like this community is too harsh for him
But I think he's gonna deal with harsh harsh
Yeah, he's got to learn and it's like you know and then you can learn it's like you just don't deal with
You don't have to see the comments or you can ignore it, okay, you don't know first-left school. I left school early, right?
Mason you're in the middle. Yeah
This is been really dumb right like I had the IQ of a ten-year-old when I left school
Didn't add the rubbish education I did
Because I was autistic and they didn't realize I was autistic
So they didn't teach me properly
To a way that I understood
well
Now I taught myself to read better. I taught myself by doing you know like
crosswords puzzles
Right, I used to buy a take a break when I was pregnant with my oldest son and I learned knowledge by
Googling and like fucking looking in the dictionary for what this word means and I learned
Yeah, and it's really
Because I think I don't think I think anybody or everybody has
some and some kind of
Brilliance in them somewhere. You know, it's like there's some kind of you have to find where that is
It's usually in their interest and then it's like especially autistic people. They'll find maybe like
Pure interest, but focus on those you know focus and it's like I've seen so many brilliant people they have and they just have a brilliant
ability, but
It's like you know we're expected to like be these you know know everything and stuff like that
Sometimes people are not as good in some things and really good at other things like his brother
His brother is like a really bad singer, but he's a brilliant bass player, you know, it's like and so I know there's like
There's brilliant
Find the brilliant find work will find the light somewhere in life, and then just go towards the light and focus on that
That's because the world is like page said it's the devil's playground. It's not a kind world always. There's a lot of
Negativity like what are we supposed to like I had people within the negativity and then it's like what are we supposed to just keep them and like a little
You know dark place and it's like in one place there and like oh don't go out and talk to anybody
Hard life fucking helps you learn it gives you wisdom man
yeah, and
It's like you know, I've had to learn the hard way about a lot of things that I'm not that's smart and something
I'm really mean. I know it's a bad example, but I'm thinking a world war two right
a lot of people to survive they had to pretend that they could make metal in the world war
Nazi camps they had to pretend and they had to learn new things to survive so if we have
to do that in life then we have to do that in life we can have an easy life for years
Right, and it's like, you know, and there's like you can like sometimes in life you you learn or you get dragged
You know, you get dragged along, you know, it's because we're all gonna hey lecture. What's up girl?
What's up? Thank you for the bracelet. I love the bracelet. Electra. Electra. DJ Electra sent me this bracelet
Protection yeah, this is like a protection bracelet
Um, and I felt it working right away. And it's like
I love it. Yeah, these purple stones and it's like it was like I was like, oh my god
it's like how will this fit but I was able to like roll it over my arm and it's like it's perfect for my little wrist and
Just having and also I got this outfit today in the mail to you and I got this outfit and almost like rosary beads, right?
And it's like I don't like
You know, it's like kind of special is it was just
You know, there's a lot of positive
There's great people in the world and it's like just like I know a lot of people and it's like and I know some mean people
and some people are mean to me and
You know, it's the people that love me that
They really matter. It's like the people that don't like you. They just know you understand you. Okay, and so
I hope he's good.
I hope he's good, but yeah.
And you're really good to him and, you know,
it's like we all want to protect everybody and stuff
like that, and it's like we can't always.
And so,
sometimes like a little bit of adversity is a good learning thing because it's good to deal with it because they'll you know
We'll all face it everywhere, you know, it's like there's always gonna be somebody that is not quite wanting to be understanding
There's always mean people too
Who is who's who a troll it was smash
Smash smashes. He's a he's a bald guy. And he actually you know, he was
Yeah, he's a good he's a good guy. Yeah
I would think that he would know this but apparently not there's several layers of
Yeah, I know all about autism, you know, obviously Nathan has autism
doesn't mean he can't learn things in life. Right and that's why I don't like I don't want to say like oh
you know exclude this person or like he can't he can't be in the community and like to treat him
differently than I want to treat him uh I want to treat you know I want to treat him as part of the
I don't want to exclude people because it's like that's going to be worse off. It's going to make them sadder
I mean, I aborted them, but I have a spurge syndrome which is high-functioning autism. So it's not like
Doesn't delay me or anything
Yeah, and there's also memory. I remember things back from two years old, you know, my memory is really good and I
I remember very spiritual stuff like Lucifer and, you know...
So do I so do I like I'm like I'm like obsessed with Lilith and I know the Bible about Jezebel and
and all these weird things that people will be like what what are you like focused so much focused on
Jezebel's spirit reigns around the forests basically basically that's why I always say that I feel like
When I do the generation of Lilith, I'm always like,
she's in the forest.
I like, I always see her in the forest.
And it's like, it's all these trees
and it's like, it's this wilderness.
And it's a-
I'll tell you something I remember as a kid's like,
a dog intervened.
So, you know, you know, Jezebel was trying to get me
to go to the woods, right?
When I was told I could ride my bike on the street,
but I wasn't allowed off the street.
And I lived in this little village, and it had a forest in the distance, and something
was telling me to go to the forest, obviously Jezebel, right, in the spirits, and it was
tempting me to go to the V, and guess what was at the end of the road?
A brown spanglin' with brown eyes, and it wouldn't let me go past.
and I tried to fool the dog trying to go past it and it nicked my arm.
It didn't ravish me, it wasn't an aggressive dog.
It was like, go in me little brat.
There's a Jezebel in the chat.
She said, I just got a ringing in my head.
I just got a ringing in my head.
I think...
You know, I probably would have ended up dead in them woods
If I would have gone to them woods and I think gone into beans using the dog
Spile I believe it I believe it and it's like
Little things like that as a kid and I remember
Lucifer tricking me once, he got me chasing, he got me running over a potato field half-naked
and I wasn't dressed fully, I drank a bottle of Brute, do you know what Brute is, it's alcoholic aftershave
back in the day, I drank that
And obviously I was a bit loopy. I ran up a potato field and my older brother was trying to chase after me and get me.
And I was getting these hallucinations that if I chased the rainbow, like in Care Bears, I'd be able to get into the kingdom in the sky.
They were chasing the rainbow to get on the rainbow like fucking rainbow bright.
Yeah
Chase that rainbow and it's like no the rainbows are
Not as solid as they look, but you don't do it. It's like chop. It's like when we were kids
We we had chocolate cigarettes
You know when?
It's like in our day that we're encouraging us to smoke and encouraging us to buy facts and
Drugs and everything because all the sweets and the the candy
Drugs, it's like very powerful. It's it gives you a high. It's like the sugar is like a drug almost and
It's almost like training for drugs. That's when this candy
It's like not good for you. It's like, you know, it's just but right I understand I understand
And maybe that's why I'm high functioning something.
I'm high functioning something.
I mean, it's like I don't necessarily,
I've always been pretty able to function in the world,
but that's just by luck.
It really is.
And maybe because I'm able to ignore certain things, right?
But still and also some people are very spiritual and it's like if you have like your foot in the spirit world
Some people will think you're crazy because everyone a lot of most people are just straight in the physical world
They don't see spirit. They don't
They don't have an understanding of it
But there is like another world. It's it can be the world of imagination. It can be the world of something but
Hey, you know how you like future and prophecy, you know the four horsemen of the poc
Oh, I don't know why my spoon, you know the four horsemen of the apocalypse. Yes
In Revelation 9 there's on about four angels that's going to be loose
for a season and a time and
There's gonna be the four we know the four awesomen the apocalypse or pestilence war
Famine and death right, so I think that's what for angels that are to be released are the forewarsmen of the apocalypse
Do you think they're here or are they
If we have war, I mean, and, you see, angels are not like human beings, they're invisible, right? It's like...
It says that God created visible and invisible beings, principalities, blah blah blah blah.
Well, angels are invisible sometimes. We don't know whether we meet an angel, that's why we're supposed to be good to people because...
We don't know if we'll meet an angel of God by chance.
You don't know if a homeless person who says,
I need a drink is an angel.
And if you refuse to give him a drink of water,
you don't have to give him money,
but just go into the shop and get him a bottle of water
because that could be an angel asking for a drink.
Or, you know, in an angel, it's like, basically God will, you know, um, um, Paul, oh, Paul is here. Paul is a good guy.
Welcome, Paul. Paul wants to hang out.
I don't know, I must green gone black.
I don't know.
Hey, Paul.
Hi.
Hi, Si.
Hello, Natty. Hello.
Hello darling. I'm into the future but I'm into like Bible prophecy as well
and I like to see like the signs and the seasons and stuff.
So it's very complicated book though laughing. Oh, yes
That's why a lot of people get bedazzled when they read the Bible because
It's like what the fuck everything's symbolic
everything
Power what they call it. Yeah, it's like right. It's like we're happening right now like Jeremiah
Revelations, it's all like happening if you read it. It sounds like the world today
the daughters of Zion or Haughty and a lot of people are getting their secret ports shown
being porn revenge and everything and they've been Haughty in the background and they're all
you know he's letting their secret ports be shown
Yeah, well, that's the revelation. That's right. It's like we're seeing everything now and it's everything is being revealed
you know
It's a bit people that you know
I see things that other people can't see doesn't necessarily mean any if they're crazy or they're anything
It's like hey psych. Yes. Guess what like you know like if one day like like yesterday
I ate really less and then the next like right now
I'm like my stomachs like flat. It's like weird like one day. I eat less food and like my stomach is flat
It's really weird
Yeah, because you're stomach is like it's like a bag, right? And it's like and so whatever's in it like it can make it bigger
No, like I like I really cut down my food yesterday
So and but now I'm like wow if I do this every if I do this like a couple days a week
Well, not couple days if I just keep going that way
I'm gonna get like really skinny. I'm gonna be like you
You know, I'm I'm very skinny and so it's like, you know, it's always gonna be a healthy
Thank you, well, I'm sure you're looking good, you know
Has anybody ever spoken to Dora in love? I think he's the most ignorant prick on this planet. Who is it?
Doray love
He's the rudest boss. Are you talking about like a Riley Martin son? No, the preacher Doray love
Okay, Dorian love. No. Oh Doreen. Do you know a Doray love? Okay?
L O V E
Doray love, I think it goes I think he goes for Christ for ministries or something
I think a lot of like
He is a terrible preacher
I tried to go up one day and tell him
I was saying, what about this verse?
What about this verse where it says
That when you die, you're in the grave
And he's being bossy, he's telling me what to do, he's being rude, he's saying go to
this verse, go to that verse, go to this verse, go to that verse and it wouldn't answer my
questions.
about so sweet.
Why are you wearing a father's uniform?
I was just curious, is that like a Halloween costume?
Why, I mean, why are you-
No, I'm an ordained minister, and so-
Oh, really?
Oh, wow, I didn't know that.
Wow, nice.
It's my priest costume, it's my priest outfit.
So if I wanted to get so if I wanted to get married to a Chihuahua, you can you could like get get me married to a Chihuahua or something
Well
Dora I see Dora. I love it looks like he's an lgbtq
Yes, yes, he's so rude
Is judgemental is rude it doesn't know the Bible properly
It thinks everybody goes to hell when there's no hell that exists.
I'll tell you something.
Have you ever heard of television?
Yes.
Tell our vision.
Tell you what to see, that's what television means.
Television.
It gives you dreams about, you know how these people have false dreams about heaven and hell,
they saw this celebrity now, do you know how they get the visions of hell from the television?
They believe the television that there's a hell and there isn't.
Right.
Aren't they like man-made? These are all man-made religions like Islam and Christianity. That's all man-made.
No it's Islam. They are the crescent moon at the top of their temples, right?
Did you know the crescent moon means the Queen of Heaven?
Wow, like a sarte, a sarte.
Yeah, it represents the Queen of Heaven.
That's Virgo. Virgo is also the fallen. She fell to the earth, right?
The Queen of Heaven is here.
Basically, the energy manifests in the physical form
And that's but we are part like of the spirit right the spirit is like the spirit of the form of the earth
And it goes into the physical form is like the physical body is like a cup
Have you ever seen the bloody
Videos about the Catholic Roman Catholic Church?
They're not as mission as you think they would be well, yeah Catholicism is very
Well, the cat's holic, right? It's like it's got the cat. There's nothing about a cat involved
and
Also, the Catholic Church they use a lot of magic and they use a lot of it's like a combination of a lot of different
I was trying to force people in their beliefs, right?
Yet the Bible says God doesn't force anybody to do anything
so
Obviously, it's a false
Right, and a lot of these human-made doctrines are false and it's like we're
I mean some of it. There's like a little bit of truth in things that we can find
But a lot of it is just mind control programming
and to
AIDS is a man made
What about Joel Olstein? What about that guy? Do you think he's cool? Joel Olstein. I don't think he's cool. No, not Paul's prophet.
Siq, what did you say? Yeah, Natty, I got it. Thank you. What did you say, Siq?
It's like about it's like a it's like a money-making thing. It's not really religion. It's just like
He was kind of I kind of I don't know. He was kind of cool. Well, yeah, I mean he's good-looking and he has nice words
Have you ever watched Casper?
It's kind of weird when I turned them on the first time I seen them it started pouring rain like crazy
I don't know if that was that kind of some kind of sign or something
It was like out of the blue. It was like blue skies, right started raining like crazy crazy rain like for no reason
like for like couple hours
Interesting what you know, I think the world's a manifestation of our own mind and so it's like
you could have this whole connection that will cause that or there could be some kind of freak
nature. Can I ask your opinion on mirrors? It's like...
Mirrors, I think they're portals. I don't need to say mirrors are magic. When mirrors are magic.
They were the same technology almost as the television with today because it was like when they had the mirror
People could just see them people could actually see themselves, but it's not yourself. It's like an illusion and it's like
There's also a portal and things can come through the mirrors too, and it's also like backwards when we look in the mirror
We see the opposite image of ourself. It's like
What about Victorian houses? Do you like Victorian houses like, you know from like a hundred years ago and you like those old-style houses?
Well, yeah, you know, I like the black and white ones. What do they call them?
black and white houses
They're like they've got black and white. They got black stripes on them and they want I
Love Victorian houses. They're so I think what they called those bloody
Like it's like a checkerboard pattern or stripes
It's like stripes black stripes
Okay
I'm not catching it. Anyways, I'll catch you guys later. I gotta do some stuff. I'll see you guys later
Thank you. Have a good day
Okay, what is is it one of these hold on point I'm pointing out to me
Here we go. Let me try and find one
It's like, it's got black and white, it's like black and white, let me google black and white.
I think white are like, you know, it's like a piano, it's like these like contrasting things.
Oh I find it, I've always dreamed of having a house like an old English country cottage, like a fucking...
Let me start from my language
Terrible, it's where I've been kind of wanted it looks like a haunted house, but it's like oh
My god, it's so beautiful. I love these type of houses. I'm sharing
My brother-in-law was from Manchester
And so I went to Manchester and I was just like, you know, they have such beautiful
I'm sharing it in the basement side. Don't worry. You can look it's a house. Okay
Did in the private chat or where?
It's in the basement in the basement. Yeah
She's mad
Says Queen Natalie looking for truth
How do I find it?
It's in the basement the basement. Is that the back chat? Yeah
Okay, it's like a picture of a house
If I had any house my dream house, there would be my dream house
Something like this
You see
Is it in the private chat or the it's in the message. It says Queen Natalie's
Do you want me to show you the link? Let me get the link
You can put the link in the private chat if you want to or if you're your mod, I think so you can put in the regular chat
I love these houses with the black and white
More oh, I see I see I see I see now. Oh, here we go
You know the ones with the black and white fucking I want it
There's a house like that I can show you out the window. I actually let me see if I can see out the window
Do you like
Yeah, I have a house across the street that looks like that. I call it the witch's house
It's black and it has a white trim and it has like the beautiful art
And it looks just like I call it the witch's house because it has a purple board
I would love to put that up for Halloween and do like and haunted the house for the Halloween
You know
That's cool
If I ever won the lottery or fucking made it rich
I'd have fucking cauldrons full of candy for kids
The apples bobbing apples and everything on the garden, you know, I
Want a good community house, you know
Yes, Mina, so you didn't like the reading I gave you like I
Like I really don't remember that many people saying I didn't like the reading I gave you
But I guess you didn't I saw you tonight and I've got a drink where I'd like to visit shankam and Donna
And I'll rent a fun run on the garden and wait, you know what a fun run is, it's like
a big inflatable obstacle course, I've had like me and Shalyn and Donna and that to run
across this little inflatable.
I
Don't know because I have jittery drama glasses
Yeah
You would love about the castle as well
Yeah, I mean I love jumping on the bed you want slides and
They're punching bags and everything.
A little fun house, a little.
You like my kitty cat?
Where's my kitty cat?
A cat?
Wow, that's a different color.
I've never seen one that color at all.
Yeah, he's a ginger.
Is it Medigree?
He's like 16, 17 years old,
and he's like a little old man.
It looks expensive.
Well...
To the epitome.
I don't know. I don't think I'd agree, but you know, I just got him this year and he was like 17 years old and
Yeah
He's a good
Yes, he's fixed. He's 17 years old. So he's he's he's had girlfriends in the past. I think his girlfriend passed away, but
He's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he's a he
That's sweet. How many how many puppies the dogs? I think they have a lot of puppies
Terry says
One to five. I love you
Back in town
Mason says
I love to go out and come back in because my camera's frozen. I can't show you my dog
I'll be fine
Okay
Well, it's great talking to everybody and I'm having fun tonight. I still have another most of this last beer I have
Oh, yes. Oh
It's a big Yorkie you're a tiny
Yorkies over here, so they're like little tiny dogs, but it's a big Yorkie Bella. Oh
I have a cat nimble. I had a cat in Bella. I had a cat in Bella
Now I have Lola, but I did have a cat nimble. This is my family dog
She's plus anything, you know, she's a good dog you can
You know when you give her a haircut, you can just roll her over like a piece of dough and she'll just lie there relaxed.
She trusts me so much.
I love it.
She's my companion, you know?
Yeah.
I love dogs, you know, my mom has Yorkie.
She has a little Yorkie.
She had a Yorkie named Emma,
but Emma passed away, but she has another Yorkie,
and her other Yorkie has three legs.
And my sister also has a dog with three legs.
She adopted the dog,
because she's not the,
it's a little cute, like a little white dog.
And the dog has three legs,
and she just comes bouncing around on the front leg
and stuff like that.
My family's dog lovers.
I'm the cat lover in the family,
I love dogs and cats. I just don't have any dogs, but
Yeah, that's a adorable dog. And uh, yeah, she is beautiful when she's going out
The dogs are just like, you know, they are pure love and it's like, you know, it's like
They want so they just like love
People so much. It's like, I don't know if they've just been bred to love people or there's like a natural connection between like the
The dog spirit and the cat spirits and the people because you know I love watching these
I like watching these videos on Facebook, you know, I get those Facebook reels
where you've got these gentle dogs and they're being heroes
and they've got little babies going around giving cuddles and stuff, that's so cute!
Why have I have a whole album of my cats and I call it like licking because my cats would like just like at one point
They would all lick each other
Like and they just have all these pieces of licking each other or cuddling my cats look yeah now
I like those videos where you got dogs being heroes
I like I like seeing dogs saving
people
Yeah, I've also seen like a pictures of like or a video of it's like will a dog save the owner and it's like
There's like dogs try to save the owner like a little dog will
hear like a
About like a burglars and a burglars and the little dog will come try to attack it and stuff like that
A dog would give up their life for you, you know, that's not a good dog, so
Yeah, they're the best I mean so we're so blessed to have the cats and dogs which we
Cats and dogs are basically they're made for humans. Like they would not be here without human
Because a dog is dogs are all from the gray wolf all descended from the gray wolf and the cats are all descended from the African wild cat and
They were able to like find like the friendliest ones and start breeding them and
especially bred them to these very friendly domestic animals, but
They were they have this wild spirit still
And, you know, but they're made for humans.
Like they're just like, they're perfect.
They're made to be like our companions and our,
they love us so much too.
Like, I love, but I've had a lot of cats and they,
My cats are like my children, you know, it's like I love cats. I have a lot of cats
That's why I don't get a dog because it's
But you know what? I had a friend the other night
He brought over his dog and his dog was like this really sweet look like a German Shepherd
And the cats kind of like were curious about him and liked him and he was like here's with the cats
And he liked the cats and it was like
It's uh, I love cross species relationships where they the cats and dogs can get along, you know
I don't look like I remember Christine has like you know her dog. She showed her dog
It was I think it's a labradoodle or something and then it would play with her cat and it would wrestle around
It was the cutest thing and I was like, oh my god
Have you ever seen that video that was viral about a kid falling into a gorilla's cage?
Yeah, and it it picked up the baby and gave it back gently to its mom
They shoot her on Bo this did they shoot him? Oh
There's a new one. There's a new one
Okay, that's good. I don't know if it's real, but I keep seeing these videos of like
Lions as well. Oh
You're doing Daniel a line. Yes. Yes, sir
Hey, thank you. So somebody says something that's not true about me. Just don't listen to them, right? You see nor
You can block them so you don't see it anymore the coming will disappear, you know, it's like
So I keep, because they're saying stuff that's not true and stuff like that.
They're just making up stuff about me.
So I can, it's not even, I understand because, you know, people say things that got me that
aren't true.
And it's like, I get really upset sometimes, but you know what, people, people will say
what they want.
And especially if they think it a noisy sometimes they'll say it.
And so just ignore them.
So I can just try to get the best of me, right, to see if they get me upset or something or something, or try to see if they get me mad or upset.
It's trolling. You know what a troll is, Mason? It's like they just say things to try to bother you.
They'll just find whatever can bother you, and then they get like...
And the more you know, the more they're gonna do it.
Yeah, because it gives them...
That's why nobody's attacked me inside at the minute. We haven't even noticed anybody attack us.
Yeah, we're just like we're just chatting with each other and it's like you just chat with like the people that
Are saying nice things like you but psyche, but you're not like that though like you're friendly and stuff like that
And you're a nice person towards me
Well, you know what it's like
Because I love people and I think I see people's heart and stuff like that
But some people, you know, some people have had different lives and experiences with different people and will have different ways of talking to people.
So just ignore them.
They don't know what love or kindness is.
What's that?
They don't know what love and kindness is.
Yeah, but I know what it is though, Natalie. I know what love is about. I know what kindness is.
more gentle with him. Yeah. No,
it's not me being mean or
it's them being mean to me
though. I'll just be a normal.
but just you just thank God
bless you, you know. Yeah. Yeah.
I should be extra nice to them
and then it's like maybe they'll
say hey, I'm I'm getting some
love and they'll they'll
change. That's your cat.
Now that I asked you if you had any cats Natalie, but you said you don't have any cats
You only have a dog. I only want one pet
She has her dog. You should get some cats though. I want to see you with some cats though
I don't want cats.
I love cats. You would look good with cats. Natalie, you would look good with cats if you had some cats
No, because I'm thinking about what's best for the animal. I could only afford one pet
Okay
Yeah, a pet's a lot of responsibility and it's like, yeah, you've got vet bills, you've got, it's like, next year when I've worked out babies, I don't want cats all over as well, when she's having babies next year, because I've got to pay for, I've got to pay for the...
It costs extra money.
And then I've got to get the
dogs vaccinated when they're born.
I have to get them checked.
I don't want to be a shit
breeder. You know, I want to be a
good breeder.
Yeah.
Yeah, I had three litters of cats
and it was, it's a really bad
having the cats born
and then just like
the mom
Takes really good care of them for like and then they need a little bit bigger
The mom doesn't want anything to do with them and but I so uh, you know
But everyone likes Rudy though Rudy Rudy came in as an old man and they're like oh look at this handsome old man
You're a handsome old man
They like animals do on top of it and I like a lot of loving
He died. Oh, you like your ears pet. Oh, if I pet your ear like that like that. Oh, oh, you love it. Oh, you love it
Sorry, yes
So you seem to think Natalie's a cool person, huh? You got along with her and stuff. That's super cool. She's super cool
I mean, you know what I like? I like people with good hearts, people that are...
Naly, I invited you over to this channel. I wanted you to see about Psyche, Naly. That's what I brought you.
Yeah, that's what I brought you did, because I met a good person.
Thank you.
Rudy has like a, he has like a little, he's me out, he's me out, doesn't make much noise.
He has a quiet me out, he has a quiet me out, but he's, he used to be a really good hunter.
He used to, his mom told me that he used to take a rat and then he'd bring it under the
pool table and he would tear it apart, right, and there'd be guts everywhere.
My cats brought in two mice tonight. Two mice and I heard them squeak and stuff like that, but
That's
That's something that's like
You like Rudy Mesa?
Hey, it's like show me your cat. Yeah, it's like that's like let me see what your cat looks like
It's a little cat there you go
You know
He says next to me all day. He like lives on the couch with me
What's that Natalie
Natalie I don't really go many places though because I don't really like the way the people are out in the world
There's there's a lot of drug addicts and stuff like that out there bad people
Well, you're never gonna find a woman if you don't get out of here
No, I know that but that's why I get on YouTube and stuff like that now. You may not be a dating website, but you know what I'm saying
Yeah, but there are drug addicts on YouTube in the world, right? It's like you just want to find
someone that's nice and
Why do you think drug addicts are all bad people?
Because they because they do bad stuff now. They date rape people. They kill people. They shoot people
He's no for people. They do all that stuff
You know everybody is addicted to something you know I find like at most people
Because I've known many prostitutes who have been addicted to drugs and I've been friends with
Because I'm no other money
Mason
People they've ordered me take out they've been really kind to me
Not everybody's out there to be like friendly those like you so people just want to like use you and stuff like that take advantage
Stuff like that true and maybe it's like sometimes like you know
Some
You'll never make real friends if you keep thinking that way
There are nice people there are good people and it's even like people that might do bad things can still be good people
But it's like, it is something bad sometimes.
And it's like, people learn because they make mistakes
and it's like, they can do better.
Yeah, but Saiki, you're my friend though.
I have you as a friend, Saiki.
People take drugs because they are filling a void.
It doesn't make them a bad person.
By adding alcohol because I'm filling my body
with some sort of warmth.
Hey paper
Yeah, I mean it does drugs are horrible people
right
It's like a lot of people have just like they're you know
They have something missing and they try to try to fill it. It's a
Sorry, let me so go
Jeffrey Epstein for example was he a drug addict was he
It wasn't a nice person, no, it wasn't a nice person.
It's like, it doesn't have anything to do really
with what they do, it's how they act, right?
It's like, it's how they treat people,
how they look at people.
Like there are bad ones, but there are good people too.
And so you want to treat people, how they treat you.
You know, it's like, not just judge them
Hey, excuse me if I do have mental health problems pink bowbird. Don't be discriminated
So you turned in the father psych you turn into a father now your father's like awake instead of
Awakens, yeah
Yeah, burdo is like a little bit judgmental because burdo because people can look maybe judge burdo, right?
You just like people judge you first things you do and it's like I think you're a good person, but you know
But you shouldn't judge mental because I think God is the ultimate judge, right? It's yeah
I mean look at Jesus in around with house collectors halls and everything look at his disciples
They were not around wizards and all up because Simon the magician
Simon yeah Simon Magus. He's name is Simon Magus or Simon Magus and he he actually flew in the air and I think he like
Flu in the air. He was like the original claim to be Jesus care. Yeah
Yeah, people were so amazed by his powers that they thought he was something great
And obviously he was friends with Peter and the disciples
And I think they've he like flew in the air one time with like I think it was some like Judas
Maybe and somebody somebody peed on him, and then he fell to the ground
Bibles in the Bible ever say go away. You're not Christian
No
They don't burrow. Yeah psyche. Yes
So do you ever um do you ever check out like what uh cb was saying in the chat?
She said something like let me see. Are you gonna roll back? She said
Birdo, she or sorry. She said a mason is in love with spunky and her do you like are you in love with cb or cb?
So like you who is CB I never even heard a city only know who spoke on the screen see right there
See what I don't remember
So like yeah, I don't remember talking to that person. Are you sure I talked to that person? I don't I'm not sure
CB it did Mason hit on you because you know you have to
just just
To be a little bit be a little bit gentle with Mason, okay, but
You can be yourself, but be gentle. I understand everybody has the same
Kind of intelligence, right? It's gonna be different ways. I got like Mason has a I got a really
Good memory like he remembers a lot of stuff, right?
so so I actually have like a like a what is it called like a little attention to details kind of
Right photographic memory almost, right? It's called a photographic memory. Yeah. Yeah
And so sometimes it's like, with a camera,
it's like, sometimes you zoom really close
and some people are like the zoom really close,
some people are zoom far away,
but it's like if they get their sweet spot,
which is like the perfect vision.
Then they operate well, and so it's like some people just need to like learn that you know they need to like learn
Wait psyche wait psyche thing that is says right before Mason came in did you check out that out on panel?
He says something about on panel. Mm-hmm
We see right before Mason and I'm not sure we
You just be straight with the kids. Let me see. I
Not sure what he's talking about. Let me see. I'll scroll up a little bit. Let me see
But if I think he's a thing that is wouldn't say something means he's like really good like a you know a good guy
I'm so let me see chicken by earlier Nancy
on panel I
Think he's talking about a lady. He's talking about um, let me see
Are you in popcorn right now Natalie that looks like popcorn. Yeah, it's sweet
Popcorn, it's not it's not butter popcorn Daly. It's not the butter kind sweet
Yeah, sweet popcorn
I know I don't really eat much sweet popcorn. Let's just carmel. I like carmel popcorn. Yeah
This is my way want it way my way
You put it in the microwave, right? That's how you pop it. Yeah
It's sweet. It's got sweetness on it. Yeah, but there's different kinds of popcorn. Nelly, there's cheddar popcorn. There's a butter popcorn. There's caramel popcorn.
Okay. Hey, hey, oh yeah, Alex mayors he's talking about. Hey, Birdo, you know, sometimes on panels, if you're not allowed to talk, you know, how you have a big mouth, Birdo, you have a big, you have a big fat mouth.
Nellie butter kiss
You got little pockets put them in the mark with two minutes and 30 seconds
I've seen those kind before Nellie. I've seen those kind of popcorn. It's not the sweet con but seeing ones look like that one
Okay, psyche deal psyche do you eat popcorn or do you like popcorn?
I do you ever see Michael Jackson like getting popcorn. He's like
No, I never seen that I'm not Michael Jackson. No, it's like you're not Michael Jackson. I haven't seen him
Look at this man. No, thank you. I never seen Michael Jackson eat the popcorn though before you gotta show me or something
You have those in America smarties
That's that's that's Michael Jackson needed popcorn seriously. Yeah, so
Do you have those guys in America smarties? I never had that no
you know, and there's whisper,
you know, your mouth looks like a
butthole and that's what it
sounds like too. And so, you
know, that's all the Halloween
candy. I'm going to keep
because obviously, I keep
speaking a little bit.
Yeah. It's like, I know that
you're my friend, but I think
Natalie, she's my friend too.
Yeah, you have, you have a lot
She's definitely a good friend to you and I want to be a good friend to you too and I hope I am, you know
Yeah
Yeah, I want you to have some good good friends
It's like you see what I'm saying whenever someone calls you out you don't your dumb ass. Okay, so that's judgmental takes it as a
with all other level of stupidity.
So who's triggered now, huh?
Well, definitely you, I'm calm and you're talking like,
you know, like a big bird on crack.
And so, I don't know what to say.
Why does, why does Jamie Cowboys
always wants to say something negative?
Why does he never, why does he never say anything positive?
Jamie's a, she, it's a, Jamie's a girl in a,
and maybe she got bothered by something
and she's like, she's just like,
You know, but she's a good person, you know, and I don't think like maybe because you were calling her a guy and then maybe, you know, girls don't like that. But yeah, you didn't understand, right.
It's okay. You know, I don't understand everything. The world is complicated and stuff like that. And then I have like people like Birdo with a big mouth, like talking shit and stuff like that.
I'm not going to get triggered, I'm not going to run for my own show, and I'll start a show
on my panel if I feel like it, you know, sometimes I get to talk here and I don't get to talk
at other places, and so I feel comfortable with that.
So likey.
Yeah.
What does it mean when someone gets triggered? Does that mean mad or upset? That means that they something just bothers them and they
React in a big way. Oh Arbor is triggered. Okay. I'm sorry. Hey it goes come on up here and I'm sorry if I didn't bring you up earlier
Oh
Yeah
Yeah, and thing that it says not everyone's gonna like you in your life
And it's like there's some people who are like you and some people that aren't but it's like you wouldn't know the difference if like everyone
Just was friendly, right? It's like so
Yeah, psyche there's got to be some people in the world that's not going to always like you because then there's no difference between people you got to know who likes you and who doesn't like you.
Yeah, like for example, I don't like this person named Birdo in the chat and so it just keeps them out of it and never with them back in.
And then I don't have to read that Natalie Natalie. I think you're a good person Natalie. I think you're cool and stuff like that
I have no problem with you
But Natalie I want you to know I never showed anybody your pictures though
I don't know who told you that though, but don't listen to them now. He's not true at all
Yeah, and I don't like to I mean people with them
I like birds, but I don't like humans with the like a bird brain like burdo and so
It's just like ignorant and burdo who's it's like a like a loudmouth
Transsexual which is like there's nothing wrong with the transsexual but being a loudmouth transsexual you should understand
Not to be so judgmental and so go somewhere else go squawk somewhere else you
little chicken
or not even chicken
Big birds abortion basically that's what birdo is. Yeah, I
Agree, I don't like
Do you say bye bye birdo
Don't believe oh and yes Mina
Actually go into the band, you know
Black yourself in pieces. I'm not gonna bully you
Dumbass out of the chat, and then I don't have to look at your dumb
Cameras on voice his fucking voice is annoying
You know what I love I love the hide button on you do he crystal Marie. Hey, what's up girl? Hey, I'm CB
Jamie's not only his voice is annoying. Who are you talking about?
Yeah, burrow
You know, I'll just make a shirt. No, Natalie, I'll just make a shirt things are good though with us. Yeah, I never did anything
Yeah
We're not gonna get married. We're not with me talk
I mean, you know, I took kingdom. It's never gonna happen
I'm a husband remember
Yes
Natalie I understand you have a husband that's why I was trying to tell you about that because you got to be with your husband if you're buried
You were saying oh can you send me a picture of your mouth?
My tongue out or whatever
Now that did that was because you're being naughty. I was just being naughty back though
I was being naughty back to you. There's no wrong with being naughty
I never said there was
Natalie I never said there was there's nothing wrong with it. Yeah
Was that moment of me? I've been married 14 years
I've gave him two kids, I think I'm right to be a bit flirty sometimes, I think I've dedicated enough to my husband
But Natalie, I can't help you if your husband's not trying to give you what you want and stuff like that, you know
He does, I just like a little bit extra
He said in the bed now. He told me in the bed though. He doesn't do what he used to do with you
No, I want him to bang me on the table
Yeah
Mason you're being a little bit a little bit a little too revealing come on
Question me like I'm bloody on trial here
Amazing come on Mason. You're you're gonna learn Mason. You're you'll learn. It's like maybe I'll cool down when I'm menopause
Well at the moment I've got some women's stuff. It's natural for a woman to like male attention
Now you just want attention from men yeah, I can understand that though because you have your husband
Yeah, but sometimes you're showing your trouser area when you get an excited
You're not actually flashing, but no psych. No psych. I don't do form bombs or anything like that
You show me your feet before didn't you show me your feet before? Yeah
Everybody can be a bit noted there's nothing wrong with me
It's alright you've been walking barefoot
right? Beautiful big toes,
feet on the top. Don't worry
feet. They're touching the
ground. I mean, I mean, what
are they supposed to be? When
you walk around barefoot, do
me just your mouthful if it
makes you feel better. So,
she's like, she's like, she's
showing me her feet before on
camera. Oh, yeah. Hey, that's
Even though I'm showered and I put my socks straight on after a shower, my feet slant a bit at the bottom, because I've got home.
Now I can't look at it.
42 years old, my feet have been walking for 42 years and obviously I have a bit of hard skin so I need a bit of a pampering.
Yeah, and guys if you go get a pedicure like I get a
And then it's like my feet are clean for like 10 minutes
No, so like no, it's like I'm no weirdo. I'm just being real here though like that's what happens, right?
Yeah, you know what's best for feet the seaside
Yeah, oh yeah
You know like when you're walking around on them hard stones and the sand
Yeah, it was good for you
Yeah, I love uh, I love by the beach Natalie, so I live with you
Yeah, just keep walking on the gravel and all that on the beach. It's like using a pumice stone
Oh pumice stone. Yeah, that's perfect for like taking off the
Yo, what's up? Go say hi to Natalie and Mesa. Hi, ghost.
Yeah, I'm all right. Ghost, what's going on?
What up, Mesa? How you doing, brother? I'm okay, man.
I can't stay for long like I'm at work. I they called me in today. So I'm on my launch right now
Okay, I'm a good day at work and thanks for coming say hi. I'm sorry. I didn't I was like, you know
Somewhere and I had some stuff to work out and so I'm sorry like I was a little bit distracted
but you know
so it wasn't it wasn't nothing personal and
Yeah, a crystal Marie CV. We have oh my god. We have a great chat today
Yeah, I feel like a like a thousand times better after like, you know yesterday yesterday
I woke up at like 6 30 in the morning. Someone was banging on the door
I went down like hello, and they're like hey like oh can I get this crap?
Have any scrap metal and then throughout the day. I probably had a hundred knocks
looking for scrap metal and
I guess they the Craigslist egg up put my address in there by accident or something like that, but
I don't know if I should talk to you behind the scenes or not, but I had a
an idea I
Think what do you do on this Saturday? I think we should celebrate. You know you're feeling better
I'm feeling better. I think we should have an open panel celebration
It's it's it's it's it's Saturday is it it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's it's
Oh, James J.
The J&J
We're in an oil party. I think I had one guys. I've almost been on for about a year on the show
So what are you? What is it? I mean, it'll be a year. I think it's October. Oh my gosh
It's October like soon, so October
Sorry, yes. Yes, sir. It's like you and Natalie y'all both have your own channel where y'all both go live and stuff like that
It's off with other people. I have it. I have a new website Natalie
for the psyche verse and I don't do her IP two but IPT was like a little bit too mean and like
rude for me so I'm having like a nice community and I'm going to put you on my new website
it's just it shows when you're live and stuff like that and uh yeah I'll put you on there
and I don't have pages to here but page you're on there too and uh there's on there and I think
Yes, of course and and also traveling gypsies you
Little friendly guy
You got it you got a place there to go see it's gonna show when we're live and people can go there and see who's live
Because I know a lot of people like to
See this summer psyche hot mess summer. Yes. She's there
summer other channels like I'm a summer ish or on the on the on the channel DJ electors on the channel
So and anybody else that would like to be part of the community you have to let me know and so because
I will put you on the website.
It will say when you're live,
and then there's a couple of featured spots too,
and there's also a banner too.
And it's gonna help everybody,
and I hope it's gonna help your community.
We don't do anything like Mace homeless people or anything.
We're kind-hearted people.
I think we'll be a good change to what's available out there and there was a spot for it because
nobody's doing something positive in the community like you know as for like a community gathering
it's like IPT is not very positive and uh but it's I like some things about it but
I think it'd be good to have my own community and so
Whoever wants to sign all a part of your committee, of course you are you're when you get your channel. I'm gonna put you on there, too
What about things?
channel
You've court. Yeah, of course anybody that has a channel
If there's gonna be enough there's gonna be a you know add my link there or add my show and I will push you on there
It's gonna be really cool. It's already really cool. I have it all almost all done almost
getting there
So I hope you in Crystal's you have a channel. I got Crystal Marie there. Crystal if you want to come see her. It's like also Bita
Well if Bita
Yeah, if we make up
She of course she'll be on the channel
But I don't think she likes me very much anymore and she's had some kind of bad things about me yesterday. So I'm not like
Too hyped up about that, but if we do make up
Which I'm open. You're not friends with Bita. It's like you're not friends with Bita anymore
Well, I would be friends with Bita, but I don't think she wants to be friends with me and so but
Of course
if we make up and I would be happy to see but
not just for that but I
Just want to make up in general, but I
Don't know if that will happen. She seems like she's pretty decided that I'm just like the
scum of the earth so
That's okay. Not everyone's an understanding. I was gonna love you, you know
Sorry, Crystal Marie says she has no channel. She says I have no channel
Well crystal
You want a channel? She said she's just a viewer. It's like that's all she said about her. So she's just a viewer
Okay, well then she can then maybe she'll just she can go to the website
And then she can go to the shows that she wants to go to go on and stuff
It's for people that have channels and people that don't have channels people that have channels can be on there
People that don't have channels can go find out who they want to watch at the time. I see they can see who's live
And they can click on the person and I know a lot of people like to throughout the day
go to different places and, you know, so but I want to really like help the community out
and even if you don't like me, I'll put you on the website and stuff like that.
But if you if you hate me, I probably won't because I'm going to put people that.
Or at least have a good positive, you know relationship with everybody else on the I want I wanted to be like a
Pause like a good positive energy
I
Wanted to be a good positive energy. I love you to crystal
I love you as well.
Oh, I love you too, Natalie.
Thank you.
And yeah, I can show you what it looks like.
Let me see.
I just have a few people on there right now.
I don't think I have the updated one yet.
I do have the updated one with some people on there.
But I'll show you what it looks like.
Sorry.
Yeah?
Do you listen to George White?
My dream house.
It's my dream house.
You had a dream house?
Oh, let me see where he goes.
Let me see.
Is it in there?
Si, Si, you heard me?
Yeah, what'd you say?
Take it again.
Do you like George, do you like George Michaels?
Yeah, he's cool.
He's cool.
Here's the-
You know that song called Careless Whisper?
Si, the one that George Michaels sings?
I'm gonna have to listen to it.
So here's that you see it right here. This is like sticky first. See it's gonna look a lot better than this
This is just like that
Prototype there's more stuff already added to it, but I seem to have an update
So it says who's live how many are on there? How many viewers they have and then it will say see there's me
Alexandra
There's summer. There's talk your ish. There's traveling gypsy. There's money for 20
And I'll just I can add people to this or they can add themselves
And then it will say when does she go live though? What does summer go live?
Summer goes live every almost every day and especially on Wednesdays or Thursdays. I think that's on Thursdays
She does that she goes and does outreach for the
for the homeless and things like that and and goes and you know helps them out and
There's really nice things for the community. So I was really happy to be able to add her here and it will just have
The everyone listed here will say when they're live and so people can go and like
Then it you can like add yourself you see apply or there's a directory. I don't know if that the director's work
Yeah, there's a directory hotel. Everyone is there you can watch the stream. You know profile set up
See and it gives us a description of the channel. I'm working. I'm still working on it. I'm trying my best
It's like it is kind of expensive to try to like build it, but
You know, I think it's looking really good.
There's gonna be like news articles
and all kinds of stuff.
Directory, let me see what's built so far.
You're gonna be a part of it, Natalie.
He wants you to be a part of it.
Yeah.
And it's gonna be, yeah.
And it's just gonna be like a little,
a cool way to help promote.
And, oh, I hope that,
Everyone here wants to be a part of it, but what Christmas say let me see
Or
So
Let me see I know
Hold on wait wait psych. There's something that Jamie's cowboy said, but I know you want me to just ignore
Something the things he says, right?
It's a girl she is
Jamie's Cowboys is a girl. So I think she's a little mad because you keep saying he
Jamie's is a girl. Yeah, and so maybe it's just so you just say she and then she'll maybe react better. She
It's like I meant to say she about Jamie's cowboys. I'm saying yeah, she said something about me
But you told me if she says something that I don't agree with just ignore it, right?
Or something that hurts your feelings or anything, you know, but I don't think she's going to
Jamie come you know be a little be a little
Give give him a little be give him a little a little break, you know a little room. He's not a bad guy
Um, yeah, anchor is, uh, yeah.
So, but I do want to, and, but I was like, I have a vision for like, this is a community
and it's like, as for community, yeah, community doesn't mean everybody who means people that
we vibe with.
And so if I don't buy with somebody, you know, maybe I wouldn't put him there, but I'm a
You know
Natalie you look all serious
Yeah
Natalie's a boss, you know Natalie's a boss boss BITC H and now Lee I guess
Now they I guess you're just taking this all seriously, huh or taking it for for what it is
You know what she's she's like. She's really
like a really sweetheart and then also like really really smart and
observing and
No, Natalie. I know Natalie. I know that you like me though. I get that you think I'm cool, but you know I'm saying
Mason she's married. Yeah, she's married
Unless you like yeah, it's like I know that it's like yeah, I know that she's married
You have you have to convert to Mormonism and then and we don't want to do that
No
I'm just kidding. Yes. No, so there's times I explained to her that she's married to that. She's told her that herself
You know, no, she's married. She's a she's a she's a hotty husband
Like she's a really hot husband from Portugal Portugal
He's really cute
Not I won't hit. Oh, I'm sorry
I'm sorry, I'm just joking guys now. I'm getting drunk and I'm my third or fourth beer
No, no, I'm not serious
I'm listening to you guys. I'm listening to this music in the background
on my laptop
Just
Hey, Natalie, do you know who psyche is like that in mythology? There's there's somebody named psyche. Do you know who that is?
Yeah, it's a woman. Mm-hmm. Yeah, it's a woman
Exactly
Yes, keep it in psych
Do you have like a little I wish I had the video yeah, well, I'll play it later, but I do I have made songs about it
but I really do relate to
the site psyche she her name means butterfly or soul and
she was the most beautiful woman in the world and
So the goddess of love and beauty got really jealous and was like she's in her son Cupid, right or Eros to go
Shooter with an arrow make her fall in love with some ugly monster or whatever, but then he accidentally
Shot himself with the arrow, you know because he's she was so beautiful. He got kind of got you know a little bit flustered right? Yes
Did you know that at least from the UK though, and she's from like I think it's great Britain or something like that. I
Didn't know that I didn't know that
Mason
Yes, and those are beautiful accent Mason. Yes. I my brother
No, you're in Great Britain right now, right? Or is it England? Yes
Which one is it now they great Britain or England right there the same thing the same thing
Just English from Great Britain
And I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm like about 70% of the, that bloodline, um, you know, mostly, mostly, um, scottish.
Are you actually German you have German in you? I do have German in me too and Dutch and I have a lot of Europe in me
You know once Mason
Do you know once little old Britain conquered the whole world?
No I never heard about that
Have you ever heard of the British Empire?
No, I heard of the great I heard of the great wall or something like that, but that's has nothing to do with great and hot things
Search British Empire. They was those strongest in the world
psyche
Like you actually like you're actually laughing like about it. I'm smiling and smiling because yes, because great Britain is the most it was
I was thinking about Australia
And, you know, they took all the British prisoners and they took them to Australia and that's why Australia is so crazy.
During the Conqueror, he was from France, I think, and he conquered Britain.
He killed Henry, King Henry, I don't know if it was Scotland or England.
He killed this king. He got an arrow in his eyeball and oh and that was prophesied by Nostradamus, right?
Nostradamus
Didn't he?
Because Nostradamus had like all these like different quad trains, which are these four lines
predictions and he said oh
King will get no an arrow in the eye
And then it's like, so that was written a couple hundred years ago.
I don't know much about Nostradamus.
I haven't read his book, but I don't really know about him.
Yeah, I mean, he did make some predictions.
Like he said, you know, in the 20th century,
somebody named Hester, H-I-S-T-E-R,
which is like very close to another name we all know,
like would be ruling the world and stuff like that.
very close to what happened and
He would actually he would go into a trance in front of like a
map and stuff like that and
There's a ruler of Great Britain though. I think there was a ruler there
King is it the King Charles?
Very good king
Yep, it was good. I remember when they had the Queen mom did I went to England in about
And I was like
Mary old age right she lived on the Queen I thought the Queen was gonna go as long as
She did it and I used to watch I watched a video of Queen Elizabeth examining the gold like she has there's like basically a gold mine like I've just bought like
Thousands of feet of gold bars all stacked up on shelves and stuff like and she was going to this gold
They have a lot of goals. Wow
I think I think Prince William's born in 1981 is a year
1981 too. I'm born the same year
So I'm born in 1981
So I guess they're like somebody that was a prince there like Prince Wells
I think his name was or something like that and Prince Harry and Prince William, I think right in my rock
William or Prince Harry and who's the other one?
No, but who's the other of Prince Charles the Sons with Diana?
Harry and his brother
Erica she made American black black woman
they're a bit they're a bit neo-nazis they're all family they're very racist
for example prince harry went to a halloween party as a nazi
right i heard i don't know if it's true it's true i saw the pictures you know what they said about
meghan's child when she was pregnant what i wonder if it will be as dark as her
I don't know if maybe it will be black.
I mean, yeah, that's pretty true.
But she didn't even like Princess Diana,
and Princess Diana was white as snow.
She was like, such a beautiful,
are you a big Princess Diana fan or?
Yeah, I went to the Buckingham Palace
when it was a funeral, yeah.
When I was about 14 years old, yeah.
I remember when we heard on the radio we I was I was actually on a family vacation
We didn't have TVs and I heard on the radio
Princess Diana died and my family was like, you know, did you know they closed the whole motorway so?
This could go through the motorway
Wow
There was like I think at Prince or Queen Elizabeth's funeral or something. There was like a
these entities spotted a ghost or like there was like this
Grim Reaper kind of character that walked through. Did you see that part or no?
Yeah, I don't think Queen Elizabeth had any power though, you know, I think she was rolled up by people of all
Are they Windsors or they're Windsors right? Windsor? Yeah, they're German aren't they, they're Germans.
Adolf Hitler, you know, if you search Adolf Hitler's family tree, his tree is nowhere to be found.
His family tree. I think that Adolf Hitler is related to the Royal Family.
I know he had a Jewish grandmother or grandfather too and I know they are like Ashkenazi, I think the Windsors are Ashkenazi, I'm not sure.
Were one of the royals friends with our old people?
Were they friends?
And what was his name? Was it Pope Gregory?
It was what one of the popes, okay? I know yeah, but Gregory said the Jewish boys
Does the Jewish children deserve to be pursued? Oh, that's terrible
Even you guess LD what's up LD yo
Hi, I like your glasses. I have some more glasses. Let me see. I'll see what the hell you wear is those glasses look crazy
They're from London. They're Burberry
Oh
Your twins look I have a green glasses
Oh my Dahmer glass my Jeffrey Dahmer. Yeah, someone someone gave me these yesterday and I
Don't know my friend. Hi Tracy. What's up Tracy in the chat? How are you? I'm sorry to be I'm not being horrible
We're pretty honest here. We're pretty pretty close bunch though. I think I think we are I think we'll all get along
So yeah, yeah, look at that. Hey, so I guess you have your bong still. I thought you use a bong like the smoke
I do
LD's actually packing it me
Look at his dog. He's a greyhound look at his greyhound
Oh, yeah, well one time he came on wearing a leather
He was wearing like a leather halter
Oh, wow, it's a Phoenix. Have you ever thought about being a porn store because you're well packed
No, I haven't you'd make a good
I have I want to be a porn with LD
I don't know. I don't know.
Oh, look at the dog. Look at the
look at the smile. Look at the
look at the look at the look at
the look at the look at the
look at the look at the look at the
look at the look at the look at
A little bit. Yeah
What do you play LD like PlayStation 5 like resident evil?
Yeah, I played the remakes
Okay, I played the village. I played resident evil village. That was really good
it starts out in like a castle with like a
Giant vampire lady with like three vampire daughters had to go like get everyone in the castle
LD have you played the original resident evils like resident evil 2 original? Yeah, of course
Okay
He says you're a hottie LD LD is making all the women a little bit like
Alvaro's back. Oh my god, look at all the people back
What do you think about LD? Do you know Tracy LD?
Tracy X
Cool lady. Well, you should be here. So, you know, QQ is
the
No, he's a nurse, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you know, you want to get naughty with LD, huh?
Mason, she's a married woman. Stop it, Mason. Stop it.
Mason, calm down.
I want to get naughty with LD.
Yeah.
The LD LD how do you feel about that people get a body with?
Whatever man
He loves it. I gotta go to the store and get more beer. I'm off this weekend
Yeah, I had one more voodoo ranger my
I've got this stuff and it's 11 pounds. It's it's my first brandy
18 what is it about Bombay I don't know it says bonded do you make a hot toddy ever
no never in a hot toddy it's like warmed up brandy with some other stuff
CB is like hitting on everybody in the shit I would like not to LD but he's too far away
We can always, we can always just, you know, fantasize.
As long as you don't get too attached, LD, because I don't want marriage.
We never, never get too attached.
Good.
I think LD would be probably cool with that.
Hey, come on. Let me see. So, uh, net, uh, yeah, I'm, I'm a little bit drunk too. I'm, and I've been like, not drinking very much. And so my third
Rearranger, which is like first two, I drink or the first two drinks I drink for 8% alcohol. This was 9% alcohol
So, yes, yes
Like you and net
It's like you and Natalie are both drinking though. You'll both have alcohol. We are and it's also at Los Angeles. It is
1127 a.m. Is it 1127? Oh my god, I've been up for like 12 hours. What is going on?
We're 21 years old. We could do what we thought we wanted.
We're adults and so yeah, I'm gonna
I got the bong. I got the bong. Um, this was a gift from a chat, um, from easy in the chat.
He got me this bong. Let's see it. It's a cool, old zombie face.
Yeah, I picked it out. He also bought me the Speedo, but I'm not sure I'm going to show
the Speedo unless LD requests it, but I might show it to him.
LD, come on. Make the chat happy. Request it.
Brian.
I'm just kidding. Natalie, ask for the Speedo. I'll do it. I'll do it.
I
Just woke up like an hour like not even like half an hour ago, so it's got even though that LG
I didn't even know that
What does it say I can't read it Brooklyn Oh
What's it say? I like that you've got a nice hairy chest you know. Oh you want to see mine? I mean I, but LD, I'm just as a priest today but I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going
You got the Jezebel energy? Okay.
Okay.
I'm living here. That was beautiful, actually. Here. Look.
That's a nice dog, Eldie. Thank you. This is a sweet dog.
Oh my god, by the end of this stream, I'm probably going to pick you know
I wonder if if my dog and your dog had babies what would
What would a black and tan York's terrier and your dog look like what it calls out in a book a really fast
He's a greyhound he was he was rescued from a greyhound
What would a Grand Cross Yorkie look like?
A Gorky.
Gorky.
Gork-hound.
It would be like a little shaggy dog with a really long nose.
Well, there's an always beer. Okay. Yeah, I mean should I get out of my I think I think I'm my priest outfit is pretty
We'd be perfect for Halloween this year you would be
Sexy pirate that's always good
You're just gonna be drunk, you know
Oh my god
I don't know what that was
It's an American flag speedo that I wore for the
God let's America guys
You look like party boy from fucking a jackass
You got to get the you got to get the bow the American bowtie
A cat in a bikini
I don't know. What is this?
It's a Amnicole Smith, actually.
LD, it looks like you work out, man.
No.
I'm going to swap with LD. LD looks like a 70s porn star.
You do work in the bedroom default, LD.
He goes to work when it's time
Tell us what you like
LD are you are you are do you do like presents and like, you know, I don't do nothing
Loses his eyes it falls asleep half the time and
I'm a real floppy fish Natalie
all right. Come on dude. I like
my fish hard and fast. Hey hey
Lenore. Come here baby. Have you
been Lenore? LD. Look here's my
key. Now this is my little
pamphlet. Hey Mason you see you
see Lenore. Yeah I see it. Yeah
I see it. It's my baby. It's
Look at my pussy. Look at my
pussy on his shoulder.
Let her, let her, let her
let her, let her, let her
let her, let her
Yeah, I'll check with you later man. Send a video of you in the chat. Wow, okay
Oh, he's well parked, you know, like he's well parked
It's like psych you're wearing a speedo, right? I am I am I'm not ashamed of it at all
Nally what do you think about that that he's wearing a speedo?
I like it
Thank you. I like people living free and
Riz asks you is it cold up north Natalie
What does that mean? I mean, I think he thinks you live in Alaska. She's from Britain. Are you in northern England or southern England?
I mean
East Midlands, she's an East Midlands. Okay. I've been to Manchester. I've been to London. I don't think I went to like
The nor you're so sweet look to me
Isn't she cute yeah
It's like that's a nice looking cat it is she's beautiful
She's sitting on my yeah, he's just in my shoulder like this
Oh
Hi, what are you doing? It's not gonna show clothes
She does but you know I can take it
she's just digging my skin and the north you're hurting me
wow oh oh shit hey baby hey baby
she's on my chest too so you can see that's a little north
Right
What oh
Come up here
So I can check out your cat. Yeah, you can check out my cat
Baby
Psych so it's like so God doesn't come in until later on right like at night
Yeah, I think God he like God is like a night person. I think God he's always an awakened like three in the morning, but I
Like oh, he's cool. I like him too. You know what he's like a really
Accepting of other people person. He's like a he has a rough exterior, but he's a good person. He's
Yeah, it's like why would he laugh at last night though when somebody was making fun of him and he's saying same stuff about him
He's like he was just laughing it off though. So like he kept laughing. He's like
That's what you should do Mason because it's like he has a good sense of humor and it's like, you know
Sometimes I'm a little bit sensitive and it's like I take them too seriously. I wish I could just like
Be more like Gotti, right? And it's like just like laugh everything off and it's like
I was like was he just laughing at all because he didn't really want to put up with what people are saying and get argue back
And stuff like that. That's why he was just laughing. I'm sure he's heard he's heard every bad thing
You know, he's actually younger than me, but yeah, he's heard. He's heard it all and
He's just happy to be him and he doesn't care what people think, right?
That's we should all like not really care what people think about us because it's one of our business other people's opinions
All that matters is our own opinions, right?
You're talking about the way God he fills the stuff when people talk about him, right? It's a good attitude to have right?
Yeah, just like love yourself and then it's like, you know
What anybody else says if they say if they say the worst thing about you then you're just gonna like laugh about it and like
This is like lack of dumb they are that they don't see how like cool person you are
So I'm asking this question are you bisexual gay by any chance
I'm gay, but I did date a woman once. Hey, we have a somebody here. I mean, I'm gonna put the screen up real quick
I don't know this person. It's like so there's a guy named good times
That was in your channel last night or in your panel and the good guy was talking to him and stuff like that
Oh, I saw him. I know we know good times. Hello
Easy
Who is it this question man is this is on just somebody I don't like
Sike you still mad at me
I'm not mad. I'm not mad at you. I'm not mad at you. I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just, I'm just,
It's okay. You know, I know I'm an asshole sometimes and I did kick you off the panel and it's not I don't like to be kicked off panels
I get mad too and it's like but at the end of the day it was nothing personal
Sitting like what you were saying, and it's like I'm a forgiving person if you are truly
I'm your friend. I'll be your friend
You know, do you have a channel? I'll put you on my website and stuff. No, I know I know
Yeah. Who's this going on at home?
Oh, I know her. I know her.
She's from the other side. She's from the other side.
Yeah, are you okay? Are you half Italian?
No, I'm not Italian.
Mexican?
I remember you flashing your boobies.
Oh my gosh. Oh my gosh. Okay.
Oh my gosh. Okay. Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh. Okay.
You I can't say it. It's like you don't want me saying it when you just said it you can say it again
Oh my gosh. Okay. Oh my gosh.
It's fine. You told me to eat your butt. You told me to eat your butt
Well, what do you think?
My wife
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm I
I'm wearing big grunty panties right now.
What? What you said?
Did you like my Speedo and she said she's not wearing panties, I think.
Now I'm wearing grunty panties.
You're wearing grunty panties.
Grunty panties?
What the fuck?
I'm wearing...
Kind of like Big Brings.
Yo, I don't want to see that.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm gonna move the book.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
I got a big father. I got a big
father. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
Now 42. Oh, you too. Oh, you too old
Hey, you're well, you're Alexander's age Alexander
No, I'm not I'm not I'm not in the Sanjay age. Oh, no. No. Hey, I could still I could still do splits
Hey, can you guys do this though? Can you do this?
No
Yo yo psyche psyche it's a question. I want to ask you yeah, right that man that man was throwing kisses at you and backstage
Is that you?
He took the shirt off and he was throwing kisses at you. Who is that? Who is it? You know
What the fuck was you not not me not me
They turned it's a turn
Yeah, he was he like he went like this
And he took it. He took his tent shop. He took his shirt off, right? He started to and then I was like, okay
He's back on the show. Oh
I
Yo, you heard that guys
Don't tell Bronzeberg I said that. Come on. I know I can't get any more shows about
It was great
What you wait, what do you think you're gonna get when you come to my show?
No, no, you never you never I never saw you do that. I never saw you do that. I want to see you twerk
I want to see you. No, no, no, I don't do that. I don't do none of those
I don't know. I don't know.
So she's like that song says, she's a freak psych, she's a super freak, super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's a super freak, she's
What the fuck? She's like she'll
take it and look like she'll
take it in and talk about and
then rotate. Are you are you
are you married to David Beckham?
Are you talking to me? No,
that's Victoria. Oh, okay.
I'm so confused. I'm so drunk. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm gonna ask you. No, I mean
I'm going to ask you. I'm going to ask you. How much weight you weight?
You like maybe 250 pounds? You like 200? Yeah, you like 200? You like 250 pounds or 350 pounds?
Hey, say like it. What's up? What's up? You heard it. You heard that song I was telling you about right?
It's like that super freak song. Super freak. Super freak. Super freak.
If you want to be my lover, you got to get with me.
You got to be my friend. Make it last forever. Friends just never answer.
Yo. Yo, today's, today's funny, yo. Today is funny today.
I was happy with my big figure. I like being big.
What? What? You trying to put the one in my face? What do you say?
What do you say?
She loves her, she loves her big figure.
Yeah.
Oh no, I don't know. I don't know.
I just like having fun if you've got problem with that.
No, I'm not white. What are you? That's not my name. That's not my name
What what you said Latino in Spanish? I'm Latino. I'm Latino
Doesn't even pleasure is why
Nelly put on that song what the one I said there buddy plays the fool. Nelly put the fuck
There's no exception to the rules Nelly listen, baby
Your man's not working it your man's not working in right does you on this panel showing your ass and your booties
Yeah, you're here. Yeah. Well, you're boy. What are you? What are you? What are your husband at? What your husband at?
He's I think he's taking a nap. It's gone for a gig actually he's playing around
Why why you why you don't why you don't get the freaking on with your husband?
Now you should go
Why you don't love them no more
No, I just don't want to go with him to his gig
Why?
I've been there enough you used to go to them, right? She says she says she says she's tired
She says you tired of that wrinkle you tired of that wrinkle thing
You tired of that wrinkle thing, huh? You want something young and better, huh?
Yeah, but you showing you showing your butt you showing your butt like you shaking your butt
Yeah
I mean that means you that means you want something younger. Let's tell your husband. Your husband's an old man
Husband's young. He I saw him. He's young. He's an old man. He's an old man psyche
She said it
He's a ginger. He's a ginger. Oh shit ginger
He's a fit looking bloke he's 6-4 somewhere. He's wrinkled, right? He's wrinkled
No
No, now he's wrinkled now. He's not wrinkled
He's not wrinkled, right?
Well, it will it well is in the band unlike you Mason's don't start
How are you? How are you? How you met your gingerman? How you met your gingerman?
Mason, if you're going to act like a dickhead, I'm going to strike you hard.
Oh, well, you're going to strike me?
You're going to strike me?
Well, what kind of striking?
No, so I'm going to strike Mason.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Mason's acting more right now, and I'm not pulling up with him.
Don't get it.
It's fine.
It's okay.
She's not like she's being made to me and stuff like that now man. I don't want to put up with stuff like that
Stop whining me sir, stop whining
She's not saying that to you mason be nice
Yeah, but she started stuff with me though. I'm not gonna put up with stuff like that
She's not spot. I want you to say she does tell you the truth
I'm just I'm just trying to make me mad. I don't want people to make me mad, dude.
Are you gonna get mad? Why are you getting mad?
Mason, Mason, what are you gonna get mad for?
She wants some love. She wants some, she wants some love.
She want your love.
Mason is dumb bounded. Mason, come on.
We're not
Having a normal we have we have in a normal conversation
LES and I never get along
No, I never I never had a problem with you second
I'll tell you that I never had a problem to you that day you put you boot me off for no reason
Well, I wasn't for no reason it was because you were saying no no no ghost ghost ghost told you to take me off
Oh, he did. Well, he he paid though. Did you do? Yeah, but money money costs everything psyche. This is what I'm trying to tell you
when you have
This is what I'm a no psyche, but no no no, but psyche what I'm trying to tell you is
When you got people come up in your panel right and they support you and you know, they look out for you
You should not boot them off for money. You supported me and look out for me. When did you ever do that?
No, I never I never said that I was but I come to your panel and not salute
And it's not all about money.
It's all about a person liking your panel,
saying salute to you, saying hi to you, you know what I mean?
Right.
And have a conversation.
The first thing, like a ghost actually like
gave me like several hundred dollars.
No, no, no, I understand that.
I do understand that, you know what I mean?
No, you know, he's looking out. He's giving you money. You know, I mean, that's that's all
Actually, I was able to buy a computer a green screen
Like update my show get a webcam and like just get everything on and I really needed to update my show and it was no
No, no, I don't understand that I respect that I respect that I
Can't stay mad. I can't stay mad at you forever. I can't say mad at you forever
Yeah, that's the reason why I stopped I stopped coming this I thought you was mad
I'm not mad. I don't get mad at people. I just like get hurt sometimes when people are like mean
And like but you can't you can't let your feelings go you can't get your emotions
Involved for your
Because it's like I have you know, I love my cats and people are saying I'm I'm bad to my cats
You know, I love I love my dogs. I got two dogs. I got four cats
I love them
So I keep so I get easier to get along with you because nobody ever starts stuff with I mean you don't ever start anything
I yeah, but you're amazing. Amazing. Amazing. You cool people bro. You're cool people
Yeah, he is cool. We're all cool. I mean, it's like yeah, we everybody's cool here. We just having fun. That's all
Like yeah, so I never psyche you and I we never had to fight before but every time I talk with Nali
She wants to always start a fight with me. Well, you know, you're Mesa. She's drunk. That's what she do
When she get drunk
But I never did anything though. I was just chillin like everybody else wasn't yo
Yeah, she do that. She do it to me too. She do it to me too. It's fun to like not the you're not the only one
Yeah, I don't even know this Mexican guys. I ain't Mexican. I ain't Mexican
I'll show you I'll show you my color skin. Hold on. I'll show you
Give a shit
I'm your color skin. I'm your color skin. Yeah
You are a liar. I've never met you. You you you you you want that Mandingo you want that big Mandingo
Don't don't don't shake your ass no more
You got you got you got flat surface. You got flat surface. You got flat surface
I'll bend over. Yo, you don't
got no ass. You don't got no
ass. It's just flat. No, that's
it's not flat. Yeah, it's flat
like butter. How's that? Yes,
how's that? What the fuck?
Like that.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
You ever saw 250 pounds? You ever saw 250 pounds?
It's like I just get mad easily, man.
I didn't mean to do that though, but I just got mad.
I need some music. Do you know what I need?
Yo, what the fuck?
What the fuck?
We're still cool, right?
Like I didn't do anything, but I just rubbed you on the thing, right?
That's his flat, that's his flat.
You can't even shake it, you can't even clap it.
You can't even clap it, this is flat.
Flat surface.
Your flat surface.
This is not flat.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Yo, she's shot out.
Yo.
Natalia, Natalia.
Lisa zero seven says Natalie,
Natty the queen.
There you are.
And CB says, Natty, that's why I call.
You a whore and learn better. Oh, come on
What the fuck
Like like listen like listen man. I'm saying it's true. It's true psych. She was actually playing that song
She was actually playing that song called everybody plays the full like on her channel
Oh, she got a sandal. She got a channel
Who got a channel?
Oh this one right here the one shaking a bug
This one right here this one right here
You don't know you don't name sure the fuck you talking about flat surface. I'm gonna like listen to this
I'm just gonna listen to you guys. Yo your shit's like your shit's like flat and like you don't got no booty
It's just flat
My my my wife got a bigger ass than yours
Oh, that's not that's no ass. That's that's flat surface. That's man. Hey, man. Oh my god, you made me look skinny.
Look at that belly. Look at that belly. Rub your belly. You're not impressed, man. You're not impressed.
No, I'm not into that. It's one of those magic mirrors.
She don't even got no boobs. She don't even got no boobs. Her boobs match more and her belly's sticking out
That's all that beer. That's all beer
Yeah, you look like that you look like that out of family
Yeah, you know, you know look at yourself
What the fuck man, man, so what's wrong man like what what what what why don't you like it for there's not
There's something wrong with it. Yo, she had to have a tick body. How'd you want dance like that?
It's you don't got no ass and it's flat man. It's flat, right? Yeah, it's flat like a surface
That's flat surface
So there's nothing to it
Well, I wouldn't hit that I wouldn't not hit that hell no
Man, there's nothing to it, right? Like you can't do it. No, that's sloppy wappy. You don't know what's a sloppy wappy is
What are you talking about? What is that a sloppy wappy? You got to look before you hit
You know me she thinks she's hot she's not
She ain't hot
She's a floppy floppy
She laughs
Yeah, you know do some SSRs you use that belly you look like center close
What kind of woman do you like man?
I like I like thick girls. I like thick girls who got a you know a big butt big tits
They have to look they have to look proper not like that
Like that not that's not my style
Well, well show me what your style is man like let me see what man man if I have pictures here hold on
I'm gonna show you something
Can we change the way the screen looks I don't know this long thing
Did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did it did
Oh, CB is jealous because I've flashed Vader and Vader is not interested in him anymore.
Well, guys always say fuck this fat bitch, you know why? Because they mean it.
They've always want to fuck a fat bitch, you know?
Us fat bitches, we roll better and better.
Think that's true ladies fat women are more fun
That means
But Natalie you can't be serious when you play that song everybody plays the fool
Somebody told you to play that song last night Natalie and he played it though everybody plays the fool
What the fuck are you doing? Playing this song?
You were playing songs last night, Natalie. That was one of the songs you played.
Oh, it's my camera, old foggy.
I'm gonna get my wipes.
Is that better?
This is supposed to be a startling act and we all just chill and have some fun.
CB, I don't have to lose weight. I'm happy with the way I am.
Being a big mother for me. I'm quite comfortable.
Hey site
Are you ever just on the bigger the better the bigger
Sike, where are you man
No modern show is John Slinger.
A show that means being proud.
But never see it.
Sorry, can you share the song?
Natalie is a bulge.
That's what they turn it to you, Natalie, about the bulge.
The bigger the figure, the bigger the figure, the more I love.
The bigger the figure, the better I like it.
Sike. Sike, where'd you go?
Sike, I don't see you. It's just me. It's like I'm the only one here, man.
There's nobody else in here now, Sike.
Psyche, you like the songs, right? Psyche, you've been checking out the songs, man?
There's different songs, Psyche, that you could check out.
come on